Chapter 2291: Fang Yuan’s Admiration Towards Star Constellation

During this period of time, how many Gu Masters went through immortal ascension in sovereign immortal aperture?

Golden Fur Immortal Monarch, Hair Monster Grotto Lord, Lightning Lion Warrior, Dharma Lion Warrior, Solid Rock Warrior, Steel Rush Warrior, Frost Butterfly Warrior, An Chong, Ye Zhi, Crossing Heaven Immortal Monarch, Black Locust, Rainbow Rock Immortal Concubine, Great Wisdom Immortal Mother, Bing Yuan, Bing Zhuo, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch, Shi Zong, Ke Xin Hong, the six eggmen of Rotten Egg grotto-heaven, Xiao He Jian, Green Forest Great Sage, and now, Gu Yue Fang Xiang!

Most of the Gu Immortals who died in Crazed Demon Cave were already revived. This was excluding those who died during the chaotic disaster.

But Fang Yuan did not revive them as Gu Immortals, he only gave them Gu Master cultivation level.

One was to save resources and prevent Human Sea from getting expended, the other reason was for this opportunity!

Fang Yuan had always had a broad vision, he was also skilled at creating plans.

But in the past, his plans were often unable to keep up with changes.

Now, he had rank nine cultivation level, he was a refinement path venerable. With the destruction of fate Gu, there were few things in the world that could disrupt his plans!

Fang Yuan had purposely made accumulations in the past, now, during this trend of immortal ascension, he benefited immensely.

In just a few months, in just sovereign immortal aperture alone, more than thirty Gu Masters went through immortal ascension, this was excluding Fang Yuan’s subordinate super forces in Eastern Sea and the two heavens.

Wu clan who was extremely famous now could not compare with such results.

But Fang Yuan concealed them all, not a single bit of information was leaked.

As for the benefits of immortal ascension, only a very small portion was for those who became rank six Gu Immortals, the bulk of the gains went to Fang Yuan through stealing heavenly secret!

This was something that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could not dream of obtaining.

The truth was, even Fang Yuan did not think that his gains would be so huge!!

He obtained a large number of killer moves, Gu recipes, Immortal Gu Houses, immortal formations, blueprints to construct battlefield killer moves, countless ways to cultivate resources, as well as the most comprehensive map of the current five regions, and the location of various wild Immortal Gu.

After satisfying his needs, he looked into human path, pill path, painting path, star path, luck path, and others.

The outcome was extremely surprising to Fang Yuan, he was pleasantly stunned!

He had only given it a test but he obtained musician Immortal Gu’s recipe, thief Immortal Gu’s recipe, soldier Immortal Gu’s recipe, sergeant Immortal Gu’s recipe, and others, he even obtained a vast number of pill path and painting path Immortal Gu recipes.

He also gained various profundities of luck path, star path, and soul path that were very useful to him.

Now that Fang Yuan recalled it, the human path gains shocked him the most: ”To think that human path has already developed to this extent in the current world.”

Fang Yuan did not know of the existence of the derivation formation, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had hidden it too well.

However, the root issue was with the derivation formation.

The core of the derivation formation was rank nine derivation Gu, it was not refined by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable so it was still a wild Immortal Gu.

It was not that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not want to refine it, but it could only be used in this situation as a wild Gu.

Once derivation Gu was refined by a person, it would become useless.

Limitless Demon Venerable had given it a try, thus, the Crazed Demon formation still used a wild rank nine derivation Gu as the core.

However, the innermost layers of Crazed Demon Cave were isolated from the main world, thus, it did not matter if derivation Gu was wild or not.

This was not the case for Heavenly Court.

Heavenly Court had devoured too many nine heavens fragments, it was full of heaven’s will and was the largest heaven vein node in the two heavens.

When the two heavens were fusing, Heavenly Court had to mobilize all their rank eight experts and Immortal Gu Houses to survive the ordeal. In the end, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable personally took action after refining all of Heavenly Court’s wisdom path dao marks. She stabilized the situation and prevented Spectral Soul Demon Venerable from finding them.

The current derivation formation was situated inside Heavenly Court, it was observable by heaven’s will.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could not stop that as long as it was inside Heavenly Court

Heaven’s will was one of the foundations of Heavenly Court itself.

Other than Heavenly Court, where else could she safely put the derivation formation?

Nowhere.

At least, nowhere in Central Continent.

Thus, everything within the derivation formation was also known by heaven and earth.

This was a major flaw that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable knew.

But it did not matter.

Or rather, in her perspective, it did not matter.

The reason?

Heaven’s will did not like any of the venerables now.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had revived, how could heaven’s will allow people to revive?

Fang Yuan was even worse, he was a complete otherworldly demon, one of the main culprits who destroyed fate Gu.

Only Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was more favored by heaven’s will.

But he had lost his senses, even if he wanted to target Heavenly Court, with the door shut tight, he could not find his way in!

Even if he entered, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had the amplification of Heavenly Court’s wisdom path dao marks, would she fear him? It would be the best chance to kill him!

Like how Fang Yuan did not know of the derivation formation, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable also did not know that Fang Yuan had rank nine heavenly secret Gu.

And most importantly, Fang Yuan created stealing heavenly secret killer move!

Regardless of the inclination of heaven’s will, Fang Yuan could use natural inspiration to steal countless heavenly secrets.

The three qi surrounded Gu Yue Fang Xiang who was currently undergoing natural inspiration.

Seeing this, Fang Yuan restrained his scattered thoughts and focused: ”What heavenly secret should I steal this time?”

He thought about it: ”I can ask for Heavenly Court’s information directly, that seems fine. No matter how Star Constellation Immortal Venerable tries to hide things, my stealing heavenly secret is rank nine. If she wants to resist it, she needs to have a rank nine wisdom path Immortal Gu to achieve a qualitative change!

No matter how many wisdom path dao marks Heavenly Court had, it was only a quantitative amplification.

When Gu Yue Fang Xiang’s aperture exploded to create an immortal aperture, becoming a rank six Gu Immortal, Fang Yuan’s body shook.

“Derivation immortal formation?!”

“Star Constellation Immortal Venerable hid it too deeply, I only found out now.”

“So that’s it.”

“Incredible, as expected of the number one wisdom path expert throughout the past and present!”

At this moment, Fang Yuan felt deep admiration towards Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

She actually had such a method to rapidly promote the development of various paths.

The might of wisdom path was truly terrifying.

Such an enemy was worth admiring!

Northern Plains.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable stopped his action of refining Northern Plains’ luck path dao marks.

“It is about time.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable inspected the surroundings first. He had a unique way of refining Northern Plains’ luck path dao marks, he did not stay at the same place for long, moving to other places after fully refining all of the dao marks in one area.

Instead, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable refined dao marks broadly, after refining sixty percent of the luck path dao marks of a certain area in Northern Plains, he would move on to the next location and continue his refinement.

After the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable started to refine Northern Plains’ dao marks.

After various events like the Great Love declaration, Fang clan’s saga, Spectral Soul destroying the sun, the three venerables’ contest over light Gu, and the trend of immortal ascension, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable finally refined sixty percent of Northern Plains’ luck path dao marks.

He had already covered the entire Northern Plains.

At the same time, he did not forget to develop his own rank nine immortal aperture, he went through several tribulations and put in several resource points.

With the increased foundation of his rank nine immortal aperture, his immortal essence production speed also rose.

As time passed, the immortal aperture foundation of the venerables would rise rapidly, their immortal essence would become more abundant.

BUt now, Giant Sun’s immortal aperture was still far inferior to Longevity Heaven.

Longevity Heaven was the rank nine immortal aperture that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had in his previous life. Because it did not devour any nine heavens fragment, it had gone through many calamities and tribulations over the years, gaining a huge number of dao marks through them.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not have sovereign immortal aperture, he could not annex a larger immortal aperture, while he also had to cultivate blood path. Thus, if he wanted to annex Longevity Heaven and gain the maximum benefit, he still lacked a lot of accumulation.

In terms of foundation, Longevity Heaven was inferior to Heavenly Court.

Heavenly Court had the immortal aperture of three venerables, while Giant Sun Immortal Venerable only had his own rank nine aperture as the foundation of his previous life.

But Longevity Heaven had a huge advantage that Heavenly Court lacked.

In the future, after Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s blood path cultivation reach a certain level, he could annex Longevity Heaven to raise his strength to a terrifying level!

After some rest, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable started to prepare his killer move.

As the killer move activated, soon, with the amplification of sixty percent of Northern Plains’ luck path dao marks, a golden light appeared in the sky, dying the sky of the entire Northern Plains.

“Good, with this luck path killer move, in the future when my bloodline descendants undergo tribulation, they will receive some help!”

This was not just for immortal ascension, in the future, when Gu Immortals undergo calamities and tribulations, this luck path killer move would take effect and turn the tribulation into one that the Gu Immortal could easily deal with, at the same time, the power of the tribulation would also be adjusted accordingly.

If the Gu Immortal undergoing tribulation was strong, the luck path killer move would make the calamities and tribulations stronger, so that they could get more dao marks after succeeding.

Conversely, weakening the calamities and tribulations would allow the Gu Immortals to survive and pass the tribulation.

This luck path killer move was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s newest creation, it contained the profundity of heaven and earth luck and all living being’s luck, in the future, it could even fuse with self luck to form a mystical power.

After Giant Sun Immortal Venerable refined most of Northern Plains’ luck path dao marks, the Huang Jin tribes of the entire region benefited as a result.

The mystic power of luck path was starting to display itself on a wide scale.

In the future, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable planned to use other luck path killer moves to support the entire Northern Plains.

He would let himself, Longevity Heaven, and the various Huang Jin tribes to have positive variables in anything they did, not just tribulations, they would have good luck.

If the Gu cultivator was strong, they would have a tough time at first and be suppressed, eventually, they would experience a rebound and gain immense benefits.

“However, these luck path killer moves need to be modified and carefully chosen.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable pondered deeply.

He could not use too many of such killer moves.

Killer moves would carve dao marks upon use.

If he used them too much, the entire Northern Plains would turn into a luck path environment.

This had its flaws.

Because of conflicting dao marks, all other paths would be greatly suppressed. This was not beneficial to the growth of Gu Immortals.

Thus, this step was very important and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable needed to find a balance.

“There is no rush in doing this, I need to consider the benefits and costs more deeply.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable thought as he used his investigative killer move again.

This time, he was not inspecting the venerables but the region of Northern Plains instead.

Soon, a vague luck distribution map appeared in Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s mind.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable frowned slightly.

In his first life, there was great effect when he used this killer move. Now, the effect was more vague, especially towards the borders.

“Back then, the five regions were separated and independent, they were not tightly connected. Thus, it was easier to inspect the luck of one region.”

“But now, the five regions are united while the two heavens turned into spectral heaven. To achieve the same level of investigative power as my previous life, I will need to refine all of the luck path dao marks in the five regions.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable reached a conclusion and stopped using his killer move.

He had just used two immortal killer moves in succession, they used a lot of immortal killer move. His immortal killer move storage had reached an alarming level once again.

Next, he would need to rest for some time before refining Northern Plains’ dao marks again. Otherwise, he would be in danger if the venerables decide to fight.

Chapter 2292: Obtaining Wisdom Gu Again

Eastern Sea.

At the depths of the sea, in complete darkness.

Fang Yuan’s main body concealed his movements as he secretly arrived here.

A huge translucent bubble could be seen in front of him.

“This should be the place.” Fang Yuan realized, he stopped moving, closely inspecting it.

This bubble was formed in a special manner, it was a secret underwater world created from many elements, like an underwater volcano’s eruption, the surrounding sea water, and the qi tides that swept past previously.

Fire path, earth path, water path, and qi path, the dao marks of these four paths created this isolated utopia.

This place was very well hidden, unless any Gu Immortal saw it personally, it would be hard to detect.

“I’ll name this the four paths air bubble.” Fang Yuan activated his investigative method and observed the surroundings, before opening his immortal aperture’s entrance to let out a Gu Immortal.

This Gu Immortal had pink wavy hair, he was Fang Yuan’s dream path clone, Meng Qiu Zhen.

Meng Qiu Zhen’s cultivation level was still low, but he was a dream path cultivator.

Because the mission was quite special, Fang Yuan purposely dispatched him. Otherwise, he would stay inside the sovereign immortal aperture most of the time to research dream path, on rare occasions, he went on missions to stabilize and resolve the sovereign immortal aperture’s issues.

Fang Yuan used a method to carefully move Meng Qiu Zhen into the air bubble.

After fifteen minutes, Meng Qiu Zhen returned to the sovereign immortal aperture.

He succeeded.

He brought back a wild wisdom Gu!

Wisdom Gu was previously rank nine, but Giant Sun Immortal Venerable made arrangements and gave it to Fang Yuan.

During the fate war, in order to complete Red Lotus’ plan, wisdom Gu was used as one of the materials.

As a result, rank nine wisdom Gu ceased to exist.

But under the laws of the Heavenly Dao, life and death coexisted. Under the control of heaven’s will, a wild rank six wisdom Gu soon appeared in the five regions.

This wisdom Gu was hidden within the air bubble.

After Fang Yuan stole heavenly secrets, he found the location of many wild Immortal Gu, among them, wisdom Gu was his greatest gain.

Thus, he came here personally to prevent any accidents from happening, ensuring that wisdom Gu would be retrieved successfully.

Everything had happened according to the information in stealing heavenly secret.

Meng Qiu Zhen used his dream path method to easily suppress the rank six wisdom Gu.

Within the air bubble, although there was an underwater volcano and surrounding fish groups, none were able to threaten Meng Qiu Zhen.

As for Fang Yuan, he had too many dao marks, if he stretched his hand into the air bubble, it would likely burst.

Thus, only his clone could accomplish this.

Rank six wisdom Gu was soon refined by Fang Yuan.

Although it was wisdom Gu, Fang Yuan was a great refinement path venerable, refining a mere rank six Immortal Gu was simply too easy.

For a venerable, using rank nine essence to refine wild rank eight Immortal Gu posed no problems at all.

The difficult thing was refining rank nine Immortal Gu.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable took over a hundred years to refine rank nine wisdom Gu in her previous life, while Giant Sun Immortal Venerable failed to refine love Immortal Gu, these were all examples.

“After the fate war, wisdom Gu has returned to my possession again. And this time, it is not tampered with by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.”

“This is a wisdom Gu that belongs solely to me!”

Fang Yuan felt a faint feeling of joy internally.

As for raising wisdom Gu back to rank nine?

Fang Yuan felt that there was no urgency in this.

With stealing heavenly secret killer move, Fang Yuan could greatly improve his wisdom path deductions and modifications, he could also make up for his lack of information collecting methods.

After obtaining wisdom Gu, Fang Yuan returned to his original spot and showed that he was openly refining Eastern Sea’s refinement path dao marks. Furthermore, he took breaks quite often to show that his immortal essence was lacking, and that he was in a poor condition.

His divine sense entered the sovereign immortal aperture.

During this period of time, another major project in immortal aperture was completed!

For this project, Fang Yuan used all the immortal material reserves of his subordinates, among which, Eastern Sea’s Hua clan had the greatest contribution, they earned a lot of contribution points.

As for the construction of the splendid cloud cover, Fang Yuan succeeded after he chose to use stealing heavenly secret to get an answer from heaven’s will.

This splendid cloud cover covered a radius of over ten li, it flew slowly in the mini nine heavens.

Once in a while, it would go from one heaven to another.

The splendid cloud was an immortal material from rank six to nine.

The splendid cloud that Fang Yuan had now was a congregation of many different similar materials, most were rank six, thirty percent were rank seven, less than ten percent was rank eight, while there was barely any rank nine ones.

The food of rank nine heavenly secret Immortal Gu was a large field of splendid clouds.

Fang Yuan was still far from meeting the requirements of one feeding session.

But it was not a concern.

The higher tha Immortal Gu’s rank, the less frequent it needed to be fed. Looking at the current situation, there was still a lot of time until the next feeding session.

During this period of time, the splendid cloud cover could grow sufficiently.

There was ample time.

Gu cultivation involved nurture, use, and refinement. The feeding of rank nine Immortal Gu was a test that Fang Yuan had to pass.

He currently had three rank nine Immortal Gu, they were Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus, advance refinement Immortal Gu, and heavenly secret Immortal Gu. The former two were easier to feed, while heavenly secret Immortal Gu was comparatively more troublesome.

But Fang Yuan planned in advance, he had already started to resolve this problem.

In any case, the feeding of rank nine Immortal Gu was not Fang Yuan’s biggest problem.

He could settle it by just putting in some hard work.

He was already a venerable who owned Eastern Sea of the five regions, he also has super forces from the two heavens. Also, after his Great Love declaration, the most common business in treasure yellow heaven became his Immortal Gu refinement transactions.

And because the sovereign immortal aperture had immense foundation, even in the entire world, only Longevity Heaven and Heavenly Court could match or beat him.

Fang Yuan had already seen the blue dragon whale’s grotto-heaven immortal aperture.

Treasure yellow heaven was a special grotto-heaven meant for Gu Immortal transactions, its own foundation could not compare to the sovereign immortal aperture.

After this period of development, the sovereign immortal aperture was gradually undergoing a qualitative change.

In the past, the sovereign immortal aperture was like a dying patient, it was always close to destruction or breaking down entirely.

But now, the situation did not just stabilize, it was even improving.

There were two main reasons.

One was that the sovereign immortal aperture’s dao veins had already been established to a certain level, allowing it to reap the first wave of benefits.

There was already one ring of fire path, wind path, and water path dao veins.

The earth path dao vein that was established first already had three rings.

This had an immense effect to stabilize the sovereign immortal aperture, the effect was immediate.

The sovereign immortal aperture’s Gu Immortals could sense clearly that abnormal situations of earth path, fire path, wind path, and water path were decreasing rapidly, they became less common.

The second reason was that more than thirty of Fang Yuan’s Gu cultivator subordinates had passed their immortal ascension tribulation!

Immediately, the sovereign immortal aperture gained a huge supply of manpower!

With abundant people, Fang Yuan could easily dispatch Gu Immortals to various locations in the five regions secretly to collect the wild Immortal Gu.

Days later, Gu Immortals started to return. Some of them brought back undiscovered resource points while others brought back wild Immortal Gu.

Among which, there was one wild time path Immortal Gu — Month.

At this point, he had collected all three Immortal Gu, Year, Month, Day.

After getting the newest information, Fang Yuan’s subordinates took action with a high success rate.

The results of stealing heavenly secret did not end here.

While Fang Yuan refined dao marks, he also unsealed the truthful floating ice secretly while making modifications to various killer moves.

After stealing heavenly secrets, He obtained a large number of reference materials, his modification of killer moves became very aggressive, among which were compound killer moves.

Fang Yuan even started to construct his combat system on a large scale.

All along, he did not have much gains in this aspect, but with stealing heavenly secret, he obtained a lot of information that had immense value.

Next, as Gu Immortals continued to return, although many succeeded, some returned empty-handed.

Most of the secretive resource points were brought back, but some were damaged or destroyed by natural disasters like earthquakes or tsunamis, there was no point in relocating them.

As for wild Immortal Gu, they were also starting to move elsewhere!

Fang Yuan was not surprised.

Heaven’s will could influence people’s minds, it could also think. Fang Yuan had always been the target of heaven’s will, now that he collected all these secretive resource points and wild Immortal Gu, how could heaven’s will not make a response?

Heavenly Dao emphasized balance, it would naturally try to restrict Fang Yuan from getting even stronger.

Thus, this reaction was within Fang Yuan’s expectations.

Thus, Fang Yuan arranged for the most important Immortal Gu and resource points to be the ones that were targeted first, allowing him to have great gains.

As for the rest, they had lower value. In comparison, Fang Yuan could give up on them with no significant losses, but he could also try and see if any were salvageable.

Fang Yuan gradually digested his gains from using stealing heavenly secret, in this process, he gained a deeper understanding of this killer move.

“The information from stealing heavenly secret is extremely terrifying, it completely made up for my weakness in information path. However, if I use these information excessively, heaven’s will will make adjustments and cause them to become less valuable. Additionally, grotto-heavens like Longevity Heaven cannot be inspected through stealing heavenly secret.”

“The various killer moves and information about combat system that I steal are very useful if I want to modify killer moves and make my own combat system. But since heaven’s will knows about it, then this information must have already existed somewhere, others might know it too. Furthermore, there are many things that heaven’s will does not know, like the secret venerable true inheritances.”

“Heaven’s will can remember but not modify killer moves on its own. The painting path, human path, and pill path research results that I obtained were all produced through the derivation formation.”

Stealing heavenly secret could inspect and save Fang Yuan a lot of time and effort, it had an amazing effect. Regardless, it had its flaws.

Fang Yuan still had a need for information path and wisdom path development.

It was just that his needs were half satisfied now, he was no longer as urgent as before.

Stealing heavenly secret mainly relied on rank nine heavenly secret Gu, once heaven’s will found out about the Immortal Gu recipe, it would respond and cause the effect of stealing heavenly secret to become weaker.

Stealing heavenly secret was also dependent on natural inspiration, it could not be used freely.

Fang Yuan had already decided to nurture Gu cultivators in the immortal aperture, he would continue to accumulate more Gu Immortal seeds. Whenever it was necessary, he would make a bunch of time undergo immortal ascension.

Chapter 2293: Mental Domain

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

Within the secret room, an entire circle of Fang Yuan were sitting.

Or more accurately, a large number of Fang Yuan’s clones.

This cultivation secret room was huge, Fang Yuan’s clones were all newly formed using human path Gu worms.

Among them, the Gu Master level ones were doctor, pill refiner, constable, and craftsman. There were also rank six Gu Immortal level ones like shadow puppet, talented girl, soldier, sergeant, musician, thief, farmer, dancer, and blacksmith.

Indeed, the human path research results that the ten children of human path gained from entering the derivation formation were all obtained by Fang Yuan.

After that, he rushed to refine all these Gu!

As long as he had the recipe, with Fang Yuan’s refinement path attainment, refining these low ranked Immortal Gu was very easy.

This resulted in the ten children of human path failing to create their vital immortal Gu during their immortal ascension.

During this period of time, Fang Yuan’s clones had been in closed cultivation, comprehending human path and having their respective insights.

“Although these clones are low in rank, there are exceptional aspects when compared to Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s method.”

“For example, they only need a small investment to create. Spectral Soul’s Shadow Sect clones needed to cultivate themselves and start from zero. But these clones could instantly gain Gu master or Gu Immortal level strength by just using human path Gu worms.”

The clones formed from human path Gu worms had apertures and immortal apertures for Gu Masters and Gu Immortals respectively.

But be it aperture or immortal essence, neither could produce primeval essence or immortal essence, they could only store essence.

The human path clones were also unable to cultivate to increase their strength.

The rank of the Gu worm decided the strength of the clone.

But the human path clones would retain the main body’s attainment levels.

The human path clones mainly cultivated human path with other paths on the side. For example, musician clone cultivated human path with sound path on the side. Farmer clone cultivated human path with wood path and earth path on the side. Shadow puppet clone cultivated human path with transformation path and shadow path on the side...

All in all, these clones were not useful to Fang Yuan.

They were too weak, even the highest ranked one was only rank six.

The thing that both Fang Yuan and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable agreed with was that pill refiner clone had the greatest value.

This clone cultivated human path with refinement path and pill path on the side.

Although there were only rank one to five pill refiner Gu Masters, they would create a terrifying impact on the entire Gu Master world!

If Fang Yuan’s subordinates did not undergo immortal ascension at this time, these human path clones might still be useful. Now, they were of little value to Fang Yuan.

They were even an important evidence that could expose obscured heavenly secret!

Thinking about it, Fang Yuan turned these human path clones back into their respective Gu worms.

They were similar to Fang Yuan’s sovereign immortal body but quite different.

They could interchange between Gu worm and human forms, but Fang Yuan’s sovereign immortal body was fixed at human form with the requirement to eat the Gu worm’s food.

But in any case, a normal person needed to eat at set intervals as well.

“I’ll leave thief Gu behind.” Thinking so, Fang Yuan willed at the next moment as most of the Gu worms in the secret room self-detonated!

Central Continent.

In the deepest part of star array calculation formation.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was inspecting a secluded domain of heaven and earth that was inside.

This secluded domain looked like a cage or a lantern, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had used it in Crazed Demon Cave to fight against the other venerables.

This was the wisdom path secluded domain — Mental Domain!

It was recorded in <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable placed Mental Domain in the star array calculation formation and used the power of the formation to secretly absorb emotions.

All sorts of negative emotions in the Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects were absorbed into the Mental Domain.

With this method, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable managed to leave only positive emotions in the countless lifeforms of Central Continent towards Heavenly Court and the ten great ancient sects.

This caused Central Continent’s unity to rise to a new level!

“Mental Domain needs to store emotions, the more emotions there are, the stronger this secluded domain of heaven and earth becomes. But it needs to be controlled too.”

“If there are too much emotions stored, the Mental Domain will instead go too far and have a reverse effect.”

“Like what is recorded in <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>, it would be best to have calm Gu and fortitude Gu to suppress Mental Domain.”

“It is a pity that I only have calm Gu but not fortitude Gu. Thus, there is an obvious limit to the amount of emotions the Mental Domain can store.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable needed to be careful when activating it, she could not afford to expose this to the other venerables and end up with trouble.

At that time, even someone who lacked immortal essence like Fang Yuan would want to extort Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

This was the trick that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable played when creating the star array calculation formation, she managed to hide it from the two venerables. After all, they could only see the general information of the star array calculation formation.

After her inspection, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable received some good news.

“Oh? Among the ten children of human path, someone has already refined musician Gu to an Immortal Gu?”

“Good.”

“It seems that the failed attempts from earlier was due to the obstruction of heaven’s will. The refinement of Immortal Gu during the ascension tribulation is essentially using heaven’s will to help one refine Gu.”

“Heaven’s will was unwilling to help likely because these are human path Gu worms.”

“But afterwards, the refinement attempt done by a person succeeded!”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable put her heart at ease.

Earlier, when she found that the ten children of human path had all failed, she felt suspicious.

The possibilities included having traitors in Heavenly Court, a problem with the derivation formation, the hidden methods of the other venerables in Heavenly Court, or even because information was leaked by heaven’s will.

After learning of this success, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s suspicions were mostly lifted.

Half a day later, the first batch of Gu Immortals chosen from Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects gathered within the star array calculation formation.

Immortal killer move — Endless Learning!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable activated this killer move.

The killer move had a light-blue radiance that spread within the star array calculation formation.

In a certain space within the formation, the Gu Immortals were ready.

“It’s coming.” Someone muttered with an excited expression.

Everyone was stirred.

Soon, the immortals’ expressions turned solemn as they were immersed in the indescribable profundity of the Great Dao.

With the effect of the killer move, the immortals’ cultivation paths’ attainment level rose gradually!

As time passed, after reaching their limit, some Gu Immortals started to develop hallucinations.

At this time, the star array calculation formation would activate and send these Gu Immortals to another part of the formation to rest.

Endless learning was a human path killing intent, it used Book Mountain and learning Gu as the cores, allowing the Gu cultivator to produce true meaning and absorb it to raise their attainment levels.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had used this move in Crazed Demon Cave before, she was now using it on the Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects’ Gu Immortals. Her intention to nurture them was more sincere now.

The gains of the Gu Immortals would depend on their own talent, aptitude, comprehension, and personal experiences.

“Unimaginable, to think that there is such a method in the world to directly raise attainment level!”

“This move was used by Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable personally, of course it is amazing, she can achieve the impossible!”

“Rumor has it that dream realms can raise the Gu cultivator’s attainment level. In my opinion, Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s method has completely surpassed the dangerous method of dream path.”

“Dream realm explorations are very dangerous but the attainment level gained can potentially be endless. As for Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s human path killing move, our gains will depend on ourselves. It can only help us to produce true meaning, after using it once, we will need to accumulate a lot of experience and foundation, otherwise, we will not have much gains next time!”

The immortals slowly break out of the hallucinations and woke up as they started conversing.

Soon, the immortals flew out of the star array calculation formation.

Three stayed and did not leave yet.

Among them, there was Heaven’s Envy Manor’s Gu Immortal, Tan Ku, he went to find Ancient Soul Sect’s Yang Feng and Spirit Butterfly Valley’s Dian Pu.

After some discussion, Tan Ku used his own Immortal Gu to exchange for Yang Feng’s resources, he then used Yang Feng’s immortal materials to exchange for Dian Pu’s other Immortal Gu.

After the transaction, all three side got what they wanted, they were satisfied.

“Thanks to the star array calculation formation, it can understand what we need and help us to undergo optimal transactions. Otherwise, how can we know of each other’s needs so clearly?” Dian Pu sighed.

At this moment, all three immortals benefited from the star array calculation formation, they understood its usefulness.

Ever since the star array calculation formation collected information of the Gu Immortals, such situations became more common among the Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects’ Gu Immortals.

Thus, even the Gu Immortals of the smaller sects were interested, they wanted to report their own information to the star array calculation formation.

The formation had the ability to distribute overall resources more efficiently in Central Continent by just focusing on transaction between Gu Immortals.

Undeniably, this would promote the growth of Central Continent and raise its overall strength.

The three immortals did not have a close relationship before, but after the transaction, they became closer.

On the way back, they talked about the recently popular topic among Central Continent’s Gu Masters, human path.

During this period of time, human path cultivation had become a rising trend for the lower rank Gu Masters in Central Continent.

This was clearly backed by the ten great ancient sects who were tasked by Heavenly Court to support this trend.

“It seems that Heavenly Court has decided to develop human path.”

“That’s right, our sects chose the ten children of human path who have all become Gu Immortals now. Heavenly Court has the top tier research results of human path, now is the time for them to promote it widely.”

“I think that it is too rushed, but since Star Constellation Immortal Venerable made such a decision, there must be a flaw in my logic.”

“It is a pity that our path is already set, converting to human path is too costly.”

“Friend Tan Ku, you are smiling. Do you have a solution to this?”

“I only made the Gu Immortal seeds in my immortal aperture cultivate human path.”

“Haha, I did that too.”

Central Continent’s Gu Immortals were gradually feeling the advantages of the star array calculation formation, they also showed a consensus regarding the prospects of human path.

However, Tan Ku still did not know this now.

Although his action was the same as any other Gu Immortals, one small character who he supported would rise to become a legend in the future!

Chapter 2294: Finding Self Gu

“Quick, cultivate this!” Within Tan Ku’s immortal aperture, a middle aged rank five Gu Master was handing out a cultivation method to Wang Xiao Er.

“Foster father, what is this?” Wang Xiao Er asked in confusion.

Wang Xiao Er had his own secret.

He was not of Fang clan’s bloodline, he was a captive of Fang Dong Xi. But after Fang Dong Xi died in battle, his immortal aperture was invaded by Xiao Ye Hu, causing a huge commotion.

Using the opportunity, Wang Xiao Er escaped for his life and mixed in with this branch of Fang Dong Xi’s descendants.

Afterwards, they were sold in treasure yellow heaven.

Tan Ku was one of the Gu Immortals who bought these human slaves, within the batch of Fang clansmen that he bought, there was Wang Xiao Er.

Thus, Wang Xiao Er started his new life in Tan Ku’s immortal aperture.

Naturally, Tan Ku’s immortal aperture had Tan clan’s bloodline. Thus, the Fang clansmen all had low status, they were slaves.

But even among slaves, there was a difference in status.

For example, the middle aged Gu Master in front of Wang Xiao Er.

He had a rather pitiful life, when Fang Dong Xi’s immortal aperture was in a commotion, his whole family died. The middle aged Gu Master became disheartened and did not want to marry anyone else. After seeing the lonely Wang Xiao Er who was in the same plight as him, he felt that this young man resembled his son and took him in as a foster son.

After all, in the eyes of the middle aged Gu Master, Wang Xiao Er was also a Fang clan descendant.

The middle aged Gu Master knocked Wang Xiao Er’s head and laughed as he scolded: ”What are you suspicious about? Do you think I’ll harm you?”

“I’ll tell you the truth, the Gu Immortals who bought us are from Central Continent.”

“He bought us because he took an interest in our aptitude.”

“Now, he has handed down a human path cultivation method. If we can cultivate it successfully, we will be able to raise our status. In the future, we may even become Gu Immortals.”

Wang Xiao Er listened in a dumbfound manner.

But soon, he stated his suspicions: ”If this is such a precious cultivation method, why is the Central Continent Gu Immortal not cultivating it himself? Why isn’t he leaving it for his own descendants but us instead?”

The middle aged Gu Master clearly knew many Gu Immortal secrets, he had a broad vision. He explained: ”Gu Immortals cultivate their own path, with human path being one of the possibilities. Since this Gu Immortal has already become immortal, he cannot cultivate human path anymore.”

“Furthermore, not everyone has the aptitude to become an immortal.”

“Human path has just started developing, Central Continent’s Gu Immortals are handing out these methods as a trial. Thus, for his own genius descendants, he will definitely leave a portion of the essence of his own cultivation method for them. The remaining Tan clansmen and us will cultivate human path.”

“Human path is really underdeveloped, in our former blessed land, I’ve never even heard of it! But we have no choice now, if we don’t cultivate, we won’t even have any opportunity!”

“Xiao Er, you will live your life in here, those Tan clansmen will step on you and command you like a slave. Are you willing to live like this?”

Wang Xiao Er quickly shook his head and said solemn: ”Foster father, please teach me the method, I will cultivate!”

Wang Xiao Er obtained a large amount of human path information, it was helpful in raising his understanding of human path. There were also several human path Gu worms, they were the foundation for starting his human path cultivation.

After the middle aged Gu Master taught Wang Xiao Er some lessons, the latter started to cultivate on his own.

On this night, Wang Xiao Er was so excited he could not sleep, he decided to cultivate instead.

But an Immortal Gu was accidentally awakened by him in this situation!

The Immortal Gu’s will took the initiative and communicated with Wang Xiao Er as he felt very surprised: ”Self Gu?!”

Self Gu was so small and had hidden itself within Wang Xiao Er’s body, nobody else had sensed it.

He remembered that this was a famous legendary Gu in <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>, he became extremely happy and incredulous. Thus, he quickly flipped through <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>.

<<The Legends of Ren Zu>>, chapter five, section thirty-eight —

After falling into the water of the River of Time, Ren Zu and the other two woke up in shock.

The three immediately climb up to a nearby floating ice, although it was only a short time, they had already grown old.

“Time Gu is hidden within the River of Time, our lifespan will be washed away by the river water.” Great Strength True Martial sighed.

Ren Zu felt regretful: ”Constantly encountering good situations is actually a bad thing, it will create a huge problem! It is not good to be too happy or constantly happy, it can make people indulge in the present and forget about time as they get immersed entirely.”

But Carefree Wisdom Heart said with a tone of joy: ”Quick, look at your heart!”

The three of them inspected their inner heart, they saw that many accumulated emotions had been washed away earlier when they fell into the river.

This discovery made Ren Zu and the other two feel very happy.

Next, they continued to travel on the floating ice.

Whenever they encountered a bad situation and felt negative emotions, they would put their heart into the river water to wash it: ”These bad situations will pass eventually.”

Their negative emotions faded away with time.

Whenever they encountered a good situation and felt immersed in joy, they would put their heart into the river water to wash it: ”These good situations will pass eventually.”

Their positive emotions also weakened over time, preventing them from feeling indulgent.

Cognition Gu saw that the three of them were constantly washing their hearts, it could not help but remind them: ”Time has never healed the wounds of the heart, except that your hearts have grown old. The worst thing is not your body growing old but your hearts aging. Stop washing them.”

Ren Zu and the other two heard these words and quickly stopped their actions.

But without washing the hearts, their speed fell again.

“Let me help you.” At this time, a Gu worm flew over and landed on Ren Zu.

Ren Zu and the other two saw this Gu worm and became very happy.

It was familial emotion Gu.

With the help of familial emotion Gu, Ren Zu and the other two spread their emotions around, the joy of one person was split among three, the sorrow of one person was also split into three.

Using familial emotion, Ren Zu and the other two consoled each other and carried each other’s burden, they moved quickly and firmly.

But good times did not last.

More and more emotions accumulated in their hearts, their hearts became tired and gradually got hurt after being unable to sustain it any longer.

Deep emotions hurt the heart.

The situation soon aggravated, because their hearts were severely injured, they could not take in more emotions.

At this time, Carefree Wisdom Heart took out a cage and held it in her hand: ”This is the Mental Domain that I created, place all your emotions in here.”

Ren Zu and Great Strength True Martial did as she said.

They put their emotions into the Mental Domain.

Immediately, the truthful floating ice revealed its original appearance in front of the three.

They were simply pieces of floating ice, the three felt a different sensation towards it now.

The emotions of people did not concern others, only their own mental state mattered.

“What is this?” Carefree Wisdom Heart soon found a Gu worm in the floating ice.

The Gu worm answered: ”I am calm Gu.”

The truth was icy cold, this was the attitude that one should have when facing situations.

Ren Zu and the other two finally reached the center of the truthful floating ice.

But they did not find self Gu.

“So self Gu is not here.” Ren Zu was very disappointed.

Initially, people would often think that they were the center of all situations, but that was not true.

At the center of the truthful floating ice, there was no self Gu, but three other Gu instead.

They were rules Gu, regulation Gu, and practice Gu.

Rules and regulation Gu had been with Ren Zu for a long time, after Ren Zu’s heart was eaten by the Predicament, they thought that he died and left him.

They came here to create truthful floating ice along with practice Gu.

All sorts of situations were bound by the rules and regulation of heaven and earth.

The three Gu continued to create truthful floating ice like this, afterwards, under the effect of time Gu, these floating ice flowed away and sank.

Rules and regulation Gu saw Ren Zu and felt surprised: ”Oh human, so you did not die.”

Ren Zu quickly asked them on how he could find self Gu.

Rules and regulation Gu pointed at practice Gu and said in unison: ”It can help you!”

Practice Gu replied: ”Oh human, you have gone through too many situations. After such a long time, you have changed a lot. Self Gu is the same, even if it is right before you, it will feel very foreign now, you cannot recognize it.”

“What can I do?” Ren Zu was troubled.

“This is simple.” Practice Gu laughed: ”Can’t you just undergo the situation of ’recognizing yourself’?”

“That’s right!” Ren Zu and the other two realized at once.

Practice Gu continued: ”For a human, recognizing yourself is the most important and also most difficult thing in the world. Great Strength True Martial, you are strong and have ability, if we work together, the chance of success is very high.”

Ability Gu laughed and said: ”Undergoing situations can make me stronger.”

Carefree Wisdom Heart supported this, she gave serious Gu to Great Strength True Martial.

Great Strength True Martial started to undergo situations alongside practice Gu.

They first created a piece of floating ice that was as small as a ball. It surrounded Great Strength True Martial and practice Gu as a light membrane appeared around the ice ball.

Ren Zu and Carefree Wisdom Heart stood on top of the ice ball as they flowed away, eventually encountering year Gu.

“Is this self Gu?” Ren Zu asked.

Great Strength True Martial replied: ”No, self Gu is smaller than it.”

They continued to undergo situations within the ice ball as ability Gu got stronger, the floating ice also became larger as a water membrane appeared around the periphery.

While floating, Ren Zu saw month Gu.

“Is this self Gu?” Ren Zu asked.

Great Strength True Martial replied: ”No, self Gu is smaller than it.”

Great Strength True Martial and practice Gu continued working hard, ability Gu got stronger and made this floating ice even bigger, the periphery of the ice ball was covered in a stone membrane.

Ren Zu saw day Gu.

“Is this self Gu?” Ren Zu asked.

Great Strength True Martial replied: ”No, self Gu is smaller than it.”

The stronger the ability, the more one would find that they were small and insignificant.

Eventually, the floating ice reached its biggest size, the periphery was covered by a crystal membrane. Ren Zu and the other two floated on the ice ball and eventually found self Gu.

“Self Gu is actually so small.” Ren Zu was internally shaken.

Cognition Gu sighed: ”In the eyes of heaven and earth, in the eyes of mankind, a single self Gu is very small and insignificant.”

Chapter 2295: Fang Yuan Wants More Twins

Late at night.

Wang Xiao Er looked at the <<The Legends of Ren Zu>> as his eyes turned bloodshot from excitement, his nose was also blowing out steam.

“Foster father’s human path cultivation method is not wrong at all. <<The Legends of Ren Zu>> is truly a human path classic!”

“I’ve just noticed that in the section regarding self Gu, it actually hints the different levels of each Gu Master cultivation rank. Light membrane, water membrane, stone membrane, and crystal membrane!”

“Ren Zu and the other two met the time path Gu, Year, Month, and Day, in the River of Time. Does this mean that Gu Master cultivation takes a long time to gradually accumulate accomplishments?”

“I am still too ignorant now, this is all that I can see.”

“The human path cultivation method states that the most outstanding cultivators in history,the venerables, have all comprehended something from <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>. Thus, there are many human path killer moves created as their research results.”

“Even though I cannot match them now, I still have an extraordinary hope!”

“Self Gu...”

“It has been hiding in my body all along, the moment I started my human path cultivation, I found it. This must be a human path Immortal Gu!”

“Among the various Gu worms mentioned in <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>, in my eyes, self Gu is the most special and unique one.”

“Hahaha, with this Immortal Gu, human path is truly the most suitable path for me!”

“It is definitely the right choice to cultivate human path.”

At almost the same time.

In the sovereign immortal aperture, Mini Eastern Sea.

“Haha.” Mermaid Gu Immortal Tang Qiong could not help but laugh: ”It was definitely the right choice for our entire race to join Fang Yuan and live in the sovereign immortal aperture.”

Her excitement could not be concealed.

There was a total of three merman female immortals, Fang Yuan had brought them in earlier. After bringing a group of mermen to settle down here, they started to live in the sovereign immortal aperture.

The three merman female immortals had a clear distribution of jobs, Yu Zi was mostly in charge of completing missions and earning contribution points. Lian Ke Xin was in charge of external relations, she communicated with the other races and forces. Tang Qiong was in charge of defending the merman tribe’s territory.

After all, abnormal situations often occurred in the sovereign immortal aperture. The territory of the various forces had at least one Gu Immortal defending it at all times for safety.

Tang Qiong had just received orders from Fang Yuan, there was a piece of information that was rather outstanding.

From now on, Fang Yuan would put in more effort to support the well-performing descendants of the various tribes and forces. He would spent a huge sum to aid their cultivation and promote them to become Gu Immortal seeds.

To achieve this, Fang Yuan even gave orders to the Gu Immortals in charge of the various factions.

Each other, the respective forces had to nurture a certain number of Gu Immortal seeds.

If they reached the target, they would receive contribution points.

Otherwise, they would be punished.

“Lord Alliance Leader is not just impartial and fair, he also has a heart of benevolence. He is helping us variant humans to nurture more Gu Masters by investing such a huge sum of resources. Even among the past venerables, none had ever shown such love to us variant humans like Lord Fang Yuan! Even Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable only helped some of our tribes, it cannot compare to Lord Fang Yuan.”

Thinking of this, tears appeared in Tang Qiong’s eyes.

The reason why Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable helped the variant humans was because he could not bear seeing them face the threat of extinction.

But Fang Yuan was different.

Fang Yuan did not just give the variant humans a fair and relatively safe environment to live in without ostracism, he even gave them aid in the form of resources so that they could grow stronger.

This was an unprecedented situation.

Tang Qiong had gone through a lot of ordeals when she managed the Merman Imperial Court, they were ostracized and suppressed by various forces. As a merman Gu Immortal, she had lived a life of being bullied and overwhelmed with pressure.

Now, inside the sovereign immortal aperture, she felt truly free and happy.

The work she did in the sovereign immortal aperture was far more tiring than being in Eastern Sea, she often had to work her hardest and not rest for more than ten days in a row, along with the threat of her liver exploding.

But now, Tang Qiong was feeling increasingly fond of this place, she loved this world and treasured this sea area!

Because here, there was fairness and equality that the five regions lacked.

Because here, there was abundant hope.

because here, as long as one worked hard and was willing to undergo hardship, they will be rewarded based on effort.

Because here, one could feel that they were growing and improving at an observable rate, their own tribe or force was also developing rapidly.

Tang Qiong’s divine sense Gu entered the information path mortal Gu again, she reread the information that she had already looked through several times.

Fang Yuan’s orders greatly encouraged the procreation of the various forces. The more children they had, the more rewards they would receive.

Regarding the increase in population, Fang Yuan had a clear direction.

The vast amount of cultivation resources would be handed down to the Gu Immortals of the various factions and forces in the next few days.

Among which, there were large quantities of relic Gu, unprocessed jade Gu, wood origin Gu, water source Gu, man triumphing heaven Gu and others.

Relic Gu could raise the cultivation of a Gu Master by a small realm, while precious mortal Gu like unprocessed jade Gu could raise the Gu Master’s aptitude!

In essence, they were just carving a certain path’s dao marks on the Gu Master’s bodies.

Unprocessed jade Gu carved earth path dao marks, it was suitable for raising the aptitude of rockman Gu Masters.

Wood origin Gu suited minimen, water source Gu suited mermen, while man triumphing heaven Gu suited purebred humans without Gu Master aptitude, it could forcefully awaken their aperture.

“With these resources, our tribe can finally see hope in a bright future.”

“There has never been a venerable like Lord Fang Yuan, he truly cares about his people. No matter how ordinary or common these people are, his love is boundless like the sun while soothing like the wind, enveloping everyone.”

“He is truly worthy of being Great Love Immortal Venerable! It is my greatest fortune to be on his side.”

Thinking of this, Tang Qiong felt very excited as tears flowed down her face.

Fang Yuan, who was idolized by Tang Qiong, had just used obscured heavenly secret once again.

It could not be helped.

The gains from stealing heavenly secret were too bountiful.

Even now, there were still Gu Immortals who were returning from Eastern Sea, Western Desert, and Southern Border, bringing back cultivation resources secretly.

The most valuable things were the information of the five regions, Fang Yuan’s modified killer moves, and the establishment of his combat system.

Everything caused his luck to grow immensely again.

Thus, Fang Yuan had to activate obscured heavenly secret again to fortify the concealment effect.

During this period of time, Fang Yuan did not refine his fourth rank nine Immortal Gu.

On the surface, he was refining Eastern Sea’s refinement path dao marks intermittently, but in secret, he was digesting the gains of stealing heavenly secret and deducing many things. As for the truthful floating ice, although it was the most important thing earlier, it was no longer his focus now.

The initial benefit of unsealing the truthful floating ice was already obtained, now, the gains had evidently fallen.

This was reflected upon Fang Yuan’s own luck as well.

Fang Yuan used luck inspection and only managed to see a portion of it, but from this portion, he could see many things that were useful to his deductions.

Everything involving rank nine heavenly secret Gu was Fang Yuan’s greatest secret. This involved obscured heavenly secret, stealing heavenly secret, and others.

Because of stealing heavenly secret, Fang Yuan started to target those mortals in the immortal aperture.

He worked at lightning speed, after understanding the value of these mortals, he decided to nurture them with his full support.

Tang Qiong and the rest did not know the truth.

Fang Yuan had abundant immortal materials in his storage, mortal materials were more lacking in comparison.

The sovereign immortal aperture itself produced a lot of mortal materials on a large scale, but there were a lot of materials needed to nurture mortals. The sovereign immortal aperture had to use treasure yellow heaven to undergo various transactions and satisfy this need.

The plan was already established while cultivation resources were not an issue, but Fang Yuan wanted to make this even better.

He calculated and found that he had many methods that could be used to nurture these mortal Gu Masters.

For example, blood skull Gu, bone flesh unity Gu, and guts Gu, as well as the rank one to six version of second aperture Gu.

Aptitude was very important to a Gu Master.

Back then, Fang Yuan had used blood skull Gu to slaughter his clan and obtained A grade aptitude.

The A grade aptitude gave him immense help in his future cultivation journey.

At the same time, A grade aptitude meant a higher chance at becoming a Gu Immortal seed than B or C grade aptitude. If one had poor aptitude, rank three or four would be their limit, how could they even reach rank five?

“Blood skull Gu’s ability to raise aptitude is even more outstanding than unprocessed jade Gu, wood origin Gu, water source Gu, and polished gold Gu. Maybe I can use blood skull Gu to undergo a massive slaughter before reviving them using Human Sea and slaughtering them again. In that case, I can create a large number of A grade aptitude Gu Masters.”

A terrifying cultivation plan emerged in Fang Yuan’s mind.

He thought of bone flesh unity Gu.

This Gu was very useful to Fang Yuan when he was still a Gu Master.

It could help to elevate primeval essence for cultivation, not only could Fang Yuan use it to advance a small realm, he could even tackle the boundaries to cross a cultivation rank!

It was truly useful.

“But to refine this Gu, I will need twins.”

“This is a little troublesome.”

Fang Yuan not only needed a few hundred bone flesh unity Gu, he needed a vast number of them and scattered them across the sovereign immortal aperture. In that case, in the future, there would be many new Gu Immortal seeds.

“I do not have the time to focus on my current human soul cultivation method, my previous attempt has also bore little fruit. Thus, I can use guts Gu to nurture Gu Immortal seeds, a stronger soul is very useful to them.”

“As for second aperture Gu, it is only icing on the cake.”

Fang Yuan would not use rank six second aperture Immortal Gu to nurture them, at most, he would use rank one to five versions of them.

Right now, second aperture Gu was confirmed to be a heaven path Gu worm.

Rank six second aperture Gu used lifespan Gu as the material, while lifespan Gu was the most classic heaven path Gu worm, it contained heaven path dao marks.

Rank nine sovereign immortal fetus Gu used the ten extreme physiques as the Gu material, it was ’immortal fetus’ instead of ’immortal aperture’, thus it was a human path Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan made a conclusion, he needed to amass Gu Immortal seeds by first increasing the population.

Whether they were variant humans or humans did not matter.

Fang Yuan did not intend to take in external people, as for Gu Immortal seeds, it would be better for the sovereign immortal aperture to nurture them, they were more loyal after all. Variant humans were the most loyal to him.

Fang Yuan felt more assured with these variant humans.

With a higher population, the number of Gu Masters would also rise. But to create Gu Immortal seeds, one needed to raise the Gu Master’s aptitude first.

This meant that mortals did not just need to give birth more often, they also needed to create more siblings and blood-related kin for Fang Yuan to slaughter in the future.

It would be best if they were twins.

That way, while slaughtering them, he could also refine them into bone flesh unity Gu.

“I need more twins...” Fang Yuan thought about it and muttered: ”I need to look for Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. Among the venerables, he is most skilled at having children!”

Chapter 2296: Fei Wu Revives

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had a strange expression.

Just earlier, a transaction between him and Heaven Refining Demon Venerable was held.

Both sides obtained what they wanted.

But...

“Fang Yuan has needs for childbirth, what is he planning?”

This transaction made Giant Sun Immortal Venerable quite suspicious.

But he knew that because of dao marks, Gu Immortal found it hard to give birth. And in terms of having children, among the venerables, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was the most experienced.

Among the venerables, which other person had more children than Giant Sun Immortal Venerable?

Back then, to raise more children, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable searched the world for countless beauties, creating his five harem palaces!

“If Fang Yuan did not suddenly have this need, we would not have done this transaction. Sigh... to think that I would benefit now because of you, Zhu Zhu.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable muttered a name as the memories of a scene emerged in the depths of his heart.

Northern Plains.

In a temporary tribe, tents were set up.

The flap of an old and tattered tent was pulled side as middle-aged Giant Sun barged in, shouting: ”Zhu Zhu, what Gu did you secretly use on me again?”

Middle-aged Giant Sun had a bare chest that exposed his manly stature, but there was a pig head resting on his shoulders.

Zhu Zhu saw him and laughed: ”It worked!”

Middle-aged Giant Sun was furious: ”Zhu Zhu, I was discussing matters with the tribe elders earlier when this happened. You will turn me into the laughing stock of the tribe.”

Zhu Zhu sighed: ”Husband, I apologize. But I just want a child.”

Middle-aged Giant Sun was stunned before becoming dejected, his anger faded away: ”It’s my fault for being useless.”

“No, it is my issue. Technically, I have half a Gu Immortal’s body. It is my fault!” Zhu Zhu stood before Giant Sun as she held his pig head, saying with love and affection: ”This time, I used transformation path Gu.”

“Do you know? This is called sowing pig. It is an amazing wild beast that has gone extinct. The male pig would eat in autumn and get fat to spit out a type of crystal flower. When spring arrives, the crystal flower will bloom and the female pig will eat it to nurture new life in its body.”

Middle-aged Giant Sun’s eyes shone: ”It is so effective?”

Zhu Zhu smiled and pulled his hand, dragging him into bed: ”Let’s go.”

Middle-aged Giant Sun laughed loudly as he pounced at Zhu Zhu.

At the top of their tent, there was a flag.

At this moment, the flag started waving around intensely like the wind was blowing.

But after just a few breaths of time, the flag went motionless.

Within the tent, Giant Sun spoke in a guilty tone: ”Sorry, Zhu Zhu, I can’t continue anymore.”

Zhu Zhu smiled: ”Don’t worry, I have my methods.”

Next, Giant Sun let out a soft growl as the tent started to shake again like a hurricane was blowing.

This time, he lasted for over ten breaths of time.

The commotion in the tent stopped again.

Giant Sun sighed: ”Sorry, I can’t continue anymore.”

Zhu Zhu smiled and said: ”Don’t worry, watch this.”

For the third time, the tent shook intensely like there was a storm.

But this storm only lasted for around twenty breaths of time before stopping.

Giant Sun breathed roughly as he said: ”Sorry, I really can’t continue anymore.”

Zhu Zhu was still smiling: ”Don’t worry, I still have some methods left.”

“Wait, wait.” Giant Sun said weakly: ”I am amazed that you have so many methods, but let me rest, let me rest...”

Zhu Zhu replied humbly: ”Although I have many methods, the results are not good. Sigh... the most useful method can only come from Ren Zu, all of the humans of the five regions and two heavens are descendants of Ren Zu!”

Giant Sun immediately patted his chest and assured: ”Don’t worry, one day, I will comprehend Ren Zu’s method and we will have countless descendants!”

His recollection ended here.

A deep feeling of disappointment lingered in Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s heart.

In his previous life, he had already grasped such a method, otherwise, how could he have so many descendants?

It was just that he could not use this method with Zhu Zhu anymore.

He could never see her again.

His children were also not of her bloodline.

After collecting his thoughts, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s expression turned calm and cool again.

He inspected the gains from this transaction, he had obtained a lot of blood path research results from Fang Yuan.

Although he had been been secretly making deductions on blood path, Fang Yuan’s research results still saved him a lot of time and energy.

Other than that, there were five blood path Immortal Gu!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable refined them into his own and tossed them into Blood Sea.

“Blood Sea...” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s gaze pierced through the ground of Longevity Heaven, gazing into Blood Sea.

Even if rank nine light Gu was repaired, it was not suitable for Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

However, although he had no rank nine Immortal Gu, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could use Blood Sea as a replacement temporarily.

There were four different levels when it came to dao mark density: dao marks that were scattered all over the world, resource points that were created when dao marks were arranged in a certain manner, the apex of resource points—secluded domains of heaven and earth, as well as the essence of heaven and earth—Gu.

A secluded domain of heaven and earth was considered half a rank nine Immortal Gu.

When Gu Immortals use immortal materials to form killer moves or immortal formations, the materials were consumable and could not have a stable form, thus, the dao marks were lost after usage.

But a secluded domain of heaven and earth could be used as a long term stable core to form killer moves.

Fang Yuan’s reverse flow protection seal and Dang Hun Luo Po Seal were such examples.

“Star Constellation Immortal Venerable has Mental Domain, while Fang Yuan may have Refinement Sea, this Blood Sea is the foundation that I need to resist them!”

Back then, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had worked with Long Hair Ancestor to refine Gu, he knew about this grand plan of Long Hair Ancestor’s.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable felt that for this period of time, refining natural dao marks of heaven and earth was the most important thing. Trying to get a rank nine Immortal Gu that was suitable for himself was not realistic. In this case, a secluded domain of heaven and earth was the best substitute.

“Among the venerables, the one who has the highest hope of getting a rank nine Immortal Gu is Fang Yuan. In terms of potential, he is also the highest.”

“Thankfully, he has insufficient immortal essence and is unable to refine rank nine Immortal Gu.”

“Once he starts refining Gu, he will expose his greatest weakness. At that time, I will work with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to stop him!”

“If Fang Yuan is able to refine any refinement path rank nine Immortal Gu, then he will have an easier time refining other rank nine Immortal Gu in the future. This will snowball into an unstoppable advantage at an increasing speed.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable reminded himself of the fact.

Blood Sea surged with huge waves that ebbed and flowed, it was gradually expanding in size.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable nodded to himself: ”With five more blood path Immortal Gu, the rate at which Blood Sea is forming is increasing. In half a year, it will be completed!”

Blood Sea was currently incomplete.

Although a secluded domain of heaven and earth could be used as the core of a killer move, it was quite a wasteful thing to do as the secluded domain itself would be expended to a huge extent.

For example, Fang Yuan’s previously incomplete Refinement Sea and Human Sea (although Human Sea was complete, only the whole Human Mountain and Sea was considered a secluded domain).

“Oh?” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s expression changed, an intense luck path intuition emerged in his heart.

The last time he had such a feeling, he revived Light Emperor.

The revival of Light Emperor caused him to gain rank nine light Gu.

Now?

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was feeling expectant.

Although reviving another person now would expend the incomplete Blood Sea, he did not hesitate as he used the immortal killer move once again — Destined Birth Through Luck.

Swish swish swish!

Blood Sea surged and created a huge wave that was tens of feet tall.

Blood Sea was rapidly expended as a huge whirlpool was formed again.

After the flickering of shadow and light, a rank seven Gu Immortal emerged from within.

“Who is this?” Yao Huang did not recognize the person.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s expectations rose again. The reason was that this Gu Immortal’s revival expended even more immortal essence and portion of the Blood Sea than Light Emperor.

But he was just a rank seven water path Gu Immortal.

“Oh, are you Fei Wu?” Yao Huang stared for some time before shouting out loud.

“Fei tribe’s final first supreme elder — Fei Wu[1. Same pronunciation as trash/worthless.]?” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable frowned.

He remembered now.

Fei tribe was once a super force in Northern Plains, it had genuine Huang Jin bloodline.

Fei tribe’s first generation ancestor was not Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s son but someone who was many generations below. But Fei tribe was still very famous in history.

Or rather, infamous.

Fei tribe was a Huang Jin super tribe that ruined itself.

Fei Wu was their final first supreme elder, he was undeniably responsible for their destruction.

Many people felt that he was incapable and too greedy, he let down the entire Fei tribe and caused their destruction.

When he was the first supreme elder, he expended Fei tribe’s vast amount of resources and almost caused them to go broke. As a result, the other Fei tribe Gu Immortals lacked cultivation resources and grew slowly, this resulted in their internal conflict.

The external world also gave Fei tribe a lot of pressure.

But Fei Wu did not handle this well, he had always shown a weak attitude to the outside world.

In order to satisfy his own needs, Fei Wu even gave up many resource points that Fei tribe owned. The result was that his battle did not seem to rise.

Fei Wu’s performance disappointed everyone, in the end, he even led Fei tribe to excavate and develop in one of Northern Plains’ ten great fierce areas. In the end, he triggered a terrifying beast tide and caused Fei tribe’s territory to be engulfed, even their headquarters was taken down. Most of their Gu Immortals died in the beast tide, while the remaining ones were quickly annexed and taken in by the other Huang Jin tribes.

After the beast tide was over, Fei tribe was wiped out while Fei Wu died pitifully inside the fierce area. Their remaining territory was also taken by the various tribes.

Fei tribe became a laughingstock and the prime negative example for people to learn from.

“How can such a useless person who harmed his entire tribe appear now?” Yao Huang felt confused and suspicious.

After realizing his revival, Fei Wu reacted and paid his respects to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable: ”Unfilial descendant, Fei Wu, greets Lord Ancestor!”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had already used his luck inspection method to observe Fei Wu’s foundation.

He was shocked to find out that Fei Wu’s luck was actually quite sizable, far surpassing most rank sevens while being lower than an average rank eight. More importantly, Fei Wu’s luck had a close connection to a certain existence far away, this existence’s luck had an influence on Giant Sun Immortal Venerable himself.

But Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was a rank nine venerable, to think that there was actually an entity whose luck could affect him so intensely.

Soon, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s voice penetrated the ground and reached Blood Sea: ”The truth is often buried deep in history. Fei Wu, my descendant, tell me the truth.”

Chapter 2297: Unified Essence, Yi Qi Zi

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s words made Fei Wu shook intensely as he showed an expression of gratitude: ”Ancestor is wise! The so-called Fei tribe’s internal conflict was just our disguise to the outside world. The truth is, if not for that beast tide, how could our united Fei tribe be wiped out?”

“Back then, I expended countless immortal material resources but I did not use up Fei tribe’s foundation. Afterwards, when we developed in the fierce area, I even took away Yi Qi Zi which was deep within it!”

“However, legendary immemorial beast Yi Qi Zi had already recovered to a great extent, it was not unconscious. We fell for its ploy and ended up being exterminated by the beast tide.”

“But in the end, our Fei tribe did our best to retaliate, Yi Qi Zi did not succeed after all. Its will was completely eradicated by us!”

“It is a huge pity!”

“If Yi Qi Zi did not ruin our plan, my Fei tribe would have dominated Northern Plains with an unceasing quantity of immortal essence stones. We will become the number one Huang Jin tribe and to a certain extent, rival Heavenly Court!!”

After hearing this, Yao Huang stared with wide eyes as he asked consecutive questions.

“Yi Qi Zi?”

“Isn’t that a legendary immemorial desolate beast which appeared in the earliest history of humanity? Legend says that it was killed by Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, how can it still be alive?”

“An unceasing source of immortal essence stones? Senior, did you unravel the mystery behind Heavenly Court’s production of immortal essence stones?”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was silent as he listened. If reviving Fei Wu would get him immortal essence stones, it was not significant enough. However, his luck inspection showed that Fei Wu was very useful to him.

Within Blood Sea, Yao Huang was getting more excited, he clasped his fist with his palm and said: ”Good, Senior Fei Wu has woken up right on time. As long as we have this way to produce immortal essence stones, we can raise our reputation and catch up to Heavenly Court. This is definitely a great chance now that Heavenly Court has stopped distributing immortal essence stones. Once we take over, it will cause everyone to have a deep impression of Longevity Heaven beyond Heavenly Court!”

The more Yao Huang spoke, the happier he got.

“Heavenly Court stopped distributing immortal essence stones? That’s because they can’t produce it anymore.” Fei Wu was still kneeling on the ground, but he raised his upper body and said with a snicker, he was certain about the reason.

“Oh? Get up and talk, tell me about it clearly.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable descended upon Blood Sea, he arrived before Fei Wu.

“Yes.” Fei Wu bowed deeply again before getting up: ”I will explain from the start.”

Fei Wu explained slowly: ”Everyone knows that in this world, primeval energy is infinite, spirit springs produce primeval stones, but nobody has never found an immortal spring that can produce immortal essence stones.”

“Wild Gu, be it mortal or immortal, can absorb primeval energy to activate their abilities. But once they are refined, the Gu worm will be someone’s possession, they will lose the ability to use primeval energy. They will only be able to use primeval essence or immortal essence.”

“This primeval essence and immortal essence includes both the owner and others. If a Gu worm is lent out, the Gu worm can still use others’ primeval essence or immortal essence. For example, an Immortal Gu House can use the stored immortal essence of Gu Immortals inside.”

“What is the root cause of all these?”

“According to my research, the reason is that be it primeval essence or immortal essence, both contain our human will. Wild Gu contain heaven’s will, they are a product of heaven and earth, thus, we say that Gu is the essence of heaven and earth. Once we refine Gu worms, the heaven’s will inside will be purged, replaced by our human will.”

“As a result, the Gu worm becomes privately owned and the human will does not get acknowledged by the heaven’s will of the outside world. Thus, the Gu can no longer absorb external primeval energy.”

“If lent to others, the human will inside the Gu worm will acknowledge others so they can use their own primeval essence or immortal essence to activate it.”

“Different immortal essence contain different human, thus, they can cancel each other out. This is why many rank six Gu Immortals fail to succeed when they invade blessed lands that are already owned.”

Yao Huang was confused: ”What does this have to do with immortal essence stone production?”

“Don’t be anxious, listen to what I am saying, it will make sense soon.” Fei Wu waved his hand and smiled.

“Our aperture produces primeval essence while our immortal aperture produces immortal essence, they all contain our human will. Then, do primeval stones and immortal essence stones not have a will in them?”

“They do!”

The primeval stones that spirit springs produce are essentially reinforced primeval essence that contains heaven’s will. It is just that the primeval stones contain too little heaven’s will, it is common to ignore it. However, the heaven’s will often sneaks into our minds while we absorb primeval stones to influence our thoughts. This is one way that heaven’s will use to control us!”

“It is a pity that most Gu cultivators in the world are attracted to the effect of restoring primeval essence through primeval stones, they do not notice this issue.”

“Even if they do, they don’t care about it. Heaven’s will is just like air, it is everywhere, so it is quite normal to have some in primeval stones.”

“The immortal essence stones that Heavenly Court gives out are the same as primeval stones in that they also contain heaven’s will.”

“Why does Heavenly Court give out rank six immortal essence stones?”

“It is actually a huge scheme by Heavenly Court!”

“During Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s era, Heavenly Court purposely gave out immortal essence stones. These immortal essence stones reached the hands of the variant human Gu Immortals and were used by them. This allowed heaven’s will to infiltrate them.”

“Back then, heaven’s will sided with humanity which would rise to take the position of the variant humans.”

“By Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s era, she became one with the Dao and gained the ability to distort heaven’s will, greatly influencing it. The distribution of immortal essence stones became even more widespread. When Gu Immortals use these immortal essence stones, they will be infiltrated by heaven’s will, allowing Heavenly Court to influence and control them!”

Yao Huang heard his words as his mouth opened slightly: ”So that’s it? Can we copy Heavenly Court to distribute immortal essence stones and achieve the same effect for our Longevity Heaven?”

Fei Wu shook his head: ”Unless we can assimilate with the Dao like Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to alter heaven’s will.”

Yao Huang was anxious now: ”Even if we can’t achieve the same effect, as long as we have an unceasing supply of immortal essence stones, we can still use it to Longevity Heaven’s benefit. Senior Fei, how can we produce immortal essence stones?”

Fei Wu waved his hand again: ”No rush, no rush, listen to my story.”

“When we produce primeval essence, our human will and aperture are needed. When we produce immortal essence, our human will and immortal aperture are needed. To produce primeval stones, we need heaven’s will and spirit springs. What about immortal essence stones?”

Yao Huang blinked: ”Do we also need heaven’s will and immortal apertures or immortal springs to create immortal essence stones?”

Fei Wu shook his head: ”Many rank eight Gu Immortals who are not confident of passing a tribulation will annex an immemorial nine heavens fragment. From then on, the immortal aperture will turn into a grotto-heaven, it will be located at one place while the rank eight Gu Immortal will be like a caged bird unable to leave the immortal aperture again. These grotto-heavens contain heaven’s will, there is also an immortal aperture, so why can’t immortal essence stones be produced?”

“As for heaven’s will and immortal springs? This is something that people have been speculating about Heavenly Court, they think that Heavenly Court obtained the only immortal spring in the world. But the truth is, this is not true. There is no such thing as an immortal spring in the world.”

Yao Huang sighed: ”Senior Fei, stop beating about the bush.”

Even Giant Sun Immortal Venerable commented: ”Tell us directly.”

Fei Wu did not dare to defy Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, he sighed regrettably and said: ”Then I’ll cut to the chase.”

“According to my research, the essence of a spirit spring is just an ordinary heaven path resource point. Within it, there are heaven path, water path, and earth path dao marks, because of the heaven’s will, the spring water can produce solid primeval stones.”

“The Heavenly Dao seeks balance of the myriad beings, it will not produce a resource like immortal essence stones naturally. Immortal essence is the most fundamental resource, without it, no Immortal Gu can be used by people. Meanwhile, the widespread distribution of immortal essence stones has greatly raised the chances of surviving calamities and tribulations, this can only be caused by people.”

“However, the process cannot avoid heaven’s will. Only through the injecting of heaven’s will can there be immortal essence stones produced. This is an impossible loop.”

Fei Wu accurately pointed out that heaven’s will was the most crucial element in producing immortal essence stones.

But it was impossible to make heaven’s will do this voluntarily as it violated the rules of the Heavenly Dao.

But nothing was absolute.

In history, Heavenly Court succeeded.

During Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s era, he used the special trait of Yi Qi Zi to produce immortal essence stones.

During Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s era, Yi Qi Zi suicided but she assimilated with the Dao and altered heaven’s will, allowing it to work with Heavenly Court to produce immortal essence stones.

“So, what is the special trait of Yi Qi Zi? Since it suicided, how did it revive?” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable asked the most important question.

Fei Wu immediately answered: ”Yi Qi Zi is not its full name, its actual name is Unified Essence Yi Qi Zi. It is a very special legendary immemorial desolate beast, somewhat similar to Di Zang Sheng which appeared later in the future.”

“When a Gu Master undergoes immortal ascension, there is a crucial step to draw in heaven and earth qi to mix with one’s human qi and balance all three.”

“If the balancing of three qi succeeds, the qi lump will condense and become smaller until it reaches the limit. This qi lump is known as the Qi of Unified Essence.”

“This is the root cause of the creation of Unified Essence Yi Qi Zi! As long as there are Gu Masters undergoing immortal ascension in the world, they will produce the Qi of Unified Essence, even if it is destroyed, it can be reborn!”

“Initially, during the immemorial era, it was granted intelligence by a beastman great expert. Thus, it gained an immortal aperture and rose in strength, becoming a legendary immemorial beast.”

“When Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable challenged the various variant human races, Yi Qi Zi fought against the Immortal Venerable and lost, getting captured. But to the outside world, Primordial Origin declared that it was killed.”

“Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable held Yi Qi Zi captive and used it to produce immortal essence stones.”

“Yi Qi Zi lost its freedom, unwilling to give in, it tried all ways to escape. No matter what it tried to do, Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable still foiled its plans. After him, Star Constellation took over. She was even more skilled at planning and was extremely perceptive, Yi Qi Zi had no choice but to suicide out of despair.”

“This is the reason why he suicided in Heavenly Court.”

Yao Huang did not understand it: ”So how are they still producing immortal essence stones?”

Brilliance shone in Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s eyes, he muttered: ”So that’s it.”

At this moment, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable finally understood why destined birth through luck revived Fei Wu.

This was because his revival would give Giant Sun Immortal Venerable a way to replenish his immortal essence!

This was more useful and beneficial to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable than rank nine light Gu.

But luck path itself was an uncertainty.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could ensure that positive variables happened to benefit him, but he could not control the exact situation as that would involve controlling certainty.

Chapter 2298: Yin-Yang Path, Multiple Pregnancy Gu

Fei Wu saw Yao Huang’s expression of confusion and laughed, he explained happily: ”When a Gu Master undergoes immortal ascension, they will have a fortuitous encounter known as natural inspiration.”

“What is the cause of it?”

“Heaven and earth qi contain heaven’s will while human qi contains human will, at this crucial moment, the three qi fuse together, meaning heaven’s will and human will congregate, allowing the person to ask heaven and earth for answers regarding the profundities and truths of the world.”

“This is because heaven’s will acknowledged the human will.”

“Why?”

“From what I see, once an aperture undergoes qualitative change, it will become an immortal aperture. This is an achievement that grants benefit to the world. The Heavenly Dao wants to see this happen, thus, it rewards the human will.”

“The specialty of Unified Essence Yi Qi Zi lies here, its body is made of the Qi of Unified Essence, which is the fusion of three qi, thus, it is able to receive the acknowledgment and reward of heaven’s will at all times.”

Yao Huang stared with wide eyes: ”That means it is able to undergo natural inspiration at all times?!”

Fei Wu shook his head: ”Strictly speaking, yes! But the truth is different. We all know that the three qi create the Unified Essence, it needs to be balanced carefully. If the lump of three qi loses balance, the Gu cultivator will die. This is not true for Yi Qi Zi, failure to balance the three qi will not cause it to be in fatal danger, instead, it will lose its rationality.”

“Continuously controlling and balancing the three qi is too difficult.”

“We have all undergone immortal ascension, it is already too tough for us to sustain the state of balancing the three qi for half a day. But Unified Essence Yi Qi Zi has to undergo it at all times.”

“Thus, after it expends all its effort or gets sick of balancing the three qi, its body will lose control of the three qi. This causes heaven’s will and the human will to intertwine and result in chaos, causing it to lose its rationality.”

“In this condition, it cannot even think normally, how can it make use of the natural inspiration?”

“Regardless, as long as the Qi of Unified Essence exists, heaven’s will still favors the human will, it will be willing to help.”

“If this is an ordinary Gu Master who has not created the immortal aperture yet, they will only be able to interact with heaven’s will and undergo natural inspiration. But Yi Qi Zi is different, it has an immortal aperture already. Thus, when it is sane and clearheaded, its immortal aperture will produce immortal essence. When it is irrational and insane, its immortal aperture will produce immortal essence stones that contain heaven’s will.”

Yao Huang finally understood everything.

Unified Essence Yi Qi Zi was too special, because of its unique physique, Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable gained immortal essence stones. But he only distributed rank six immortal essence stones.

After Unified Essence Yi Qi Zi died, Star Constellation assimilated with the Dao, although she could control heaven’s will to some extent, there was a limit to it. Thus, from then on, Heavenly Court could only produce rank six immortal essence stones.

Fei Wu continued: ” Back then, I accidentally found Unified Essence Yi Qi Zi in the fierce area, it was in a state of insanity, buried deep underground and unable to move. I spoke with it but it could not respond clearly, its answer was jumbled but it cursed Heavenly Court’s two venerables with deep hatred. After some time, I pieced together the story and deduced many truths behind the situation.”

“I mobilized the entire Fei tribe and wanted to obtain Unified Essence Yi Qi Zi. I expended immortal materials and modified killer moves to try and manipulate it. After completing my preparations, I went into the fierce area and execute my plan. But to think that Unified Essence Yi Qi Zi actually had its sanity, at that time, I could not back out anymore, I had to continue my plan forcefully. Fei tribe was wiped out while Unified Essence Yi Qi Zi was also sealed by our Fei tribe’s method!”

“Without any accidents, it should still be trapped at the original spot, Ancestor, you only need to go retrieve it.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable nodded, he brought Fei Wu to the Jade Ring fierce area.

Northern Plains had ten great fierce areas, within them were countless desolate beast groups, immemorial desolate beast and plants were also not rare.

Super forces had the ability to develop in them, but if a mistake happened, they would trigger a huge beast tide. Fei tribe’s failure was one of the examples.

Jade Ring fierce area had more than ten different rings of huge ancient trees.

As one entered deeper into each ring, they would face more danger and threat.

Unified Essence Yi Qi Zi was hidden in the sixth ring.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable personally took action, he quickly arrived at it. Fei Wu had just revived and had no Gu worms but he was only giving directions.

Towards his ancestor, he did not hide anything but only said the truth.

After Giant Sun Immortal Venerable made his deductions, he used a newly modified luck path killer move, it triggered the arrangements of Fei tribe.

After doing that, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable extracted a huge black pearl from deep underground.

The black pearl was large as an elephant, it had a smooth surface and a deeply hidden aura.

“This is the result that our Fei tribe created, even a legendary immemorial beast was sealed by us!” Fei Wu looked at Yi Qi Zi as he sighed with deep emotions.

He had grand ambitions that ended in failure and the entire Fei tribe was wiped out. But thankfully, he was able to revive and use the arrangements they made to help their ancestor, this was all worth it!

After inspecting for some time, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable saw through the information of Yi Qi Zi using the intel from Fei Wu.

Unified Essence Yi Qi Zi was a lump of the Qi of Unified Essence. When it was sane, it would be in human form, the appearance would be hard to differentiate from actual people.

When it stops balancing the three qi and they go into chaos, it would turn into a lump of the Qi of Unified Essence.

If there was more heaven qi, it would float higher, if there was more earth qi, it would sink into the ground.

When Fei tribe fought against it, it had not regained its sanity fully, thus, it could not use its full strength.

Fei Wu and the rest made ample preparations, they deduced a killer move that countered Unified Essence Yi Qi Zi, eventually sealing it here.

Although Fei Wu was only rank seven, Fei tribe had many rank eights in the past, they also had Immortal Gu Houses that were the foundation of a super force. Most importantly, Unified Essence Yi Qi Zi was not sane so its strength could not be used properly.

Without rationality, even Spectral Soul Demon Venerable could not take down Fairy Zi Wei and Ying Wu Xie.

A long time had passed, by now, Fei tribe’s killer move was already greatly weakened, the sealing effect had reached its limit.

But even if Yi Qi Zi regained freely, in its current condition, it would remain on the spot without regaining its senses.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable looked through the Qi of Unified Essence and inspected that deep within its immortal aperture, there were many rank eight immortal essence stones.

The production of immortal essence was as natural as breathing to the immortal aperture origin core, with heaven’s will suppressing the human will the entire time, legendary immemorial beast Yi Qi Zi’s immortal aperture had a large number of rank eight immortal essence stones!

Rank six immortal essence stones had little significance to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, but rank eight immortal essence stones were different.

While happy, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable also found a problem.

There was a lot of heaven’s will inside these rank eight immortal essence stones, if he wanted to absorb them, he would need to get rid of the heaven’s will.

It was troublesome.

If he handled it poorly, it would affect the conversion rate of the immortal essence stones.

For example, one rank eight immortal essence stone might only be able to produce half a bead of rank eight immortal essence after getting rid of the heaven’s will.

Rank six immortal essence stones had no such problem because the heaven’s will inside was too little.

After considering it for a while, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable thought: ”Back then, Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable made use of Yi Qi Zi, he also had rank eight immortal essence stones but only distributed the rank six version, he was not likely trying not to alert the variant human Gu Immortals. By Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s era, Yi Qi Zi suicided and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable altered heaven’s will, by fusing it with Heavenly Court’s origin core, they could only produce rank six immortal essence stones.”

“However, where did the storage of rank eight immortal essence stones go? Are they use dup or hidden somewhere?”

“If they are hidden, why did I not find them when I attacked Heavenly Court? Did Spectral Soul Demon Venerable obtain them after ransacking Heavenly Court’s treasury?”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable shook his head.

Afterwards, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was captured by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable made turned into her puppet.

If he had obtained those valuable rank eight immortal essence stones, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would have retrieved them.

But the situation was clear, she had always been lacking immortal essence the entire time!

“No, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable cultivates wisdom path, what if she is hiding it the entire time?” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable frowned, his expression turned slightly solemn.

“If she has an abundant supply of immortal essence, why does she still lack it? In what area did she use the essence?”

Ever since Star Constellation Immortal Venerable refined Heavenly Court’s wisdom path dao marks, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had not inspected her situation anymore.

As for Fang Yuan, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could inspect him easily each time.

“If that is the situation, then Star Constellation Immortal Venerable... How much are you hiding? How deep are your secrets?” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable looked in the direction of Central Continent.

Eastern Sea.

“Any venerable has talent that is unimaginable to the average genius.” Fang Yuan had already comprehended the information that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable handed to him in their transaction.

He obtained what he wanted.

Fang Yuan had already refined rank five blood skull Gu.

Earlier, he was only using rank four blood skull Gu, but Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had a newly developed rank five version.

Although it was a mortal Gu recipe, it had developed beyond the original limit of the world, this showed Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s immense talent.

Rank five blood skull Gu only needed to extract a certain amount of bloodline from the target’s kin, there was no need to slaughter the entire clan.

There was also a method to produce twins.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had no choice but to hand over the research results of yin-yang path that he was secretly looking into.

Back then, in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, there was the inheritance of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable regarding yin-yang path. The content was a method, to use it, a male and female Gu Immortal had to cooperate, using copulation to extend the lifespan of one of them.

But there was a flaw in this.

If one gains lifespan, the other must lose lifespan.

In other words, it was to transfer the lifespan of one person to the other.

Right now, the yin-yang path research result that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable handed to Fang Yuan was much more complete and comprehensive than the one hidden in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had grand ambitions in creating this path, he wanted to use yin-yang to describe all beings in the world.

This was the same as Feng Jiu Ge’s desire to use sound path to express all life in this world.

But as Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s strength and knowledge increased, he recognized that his former ideology of yin-yang was very shallow, he eventually gave up on creating it.

Although there were some research results in yin-yang path, it could not achieve a qualitative change to become a brand new path. At most, it could be used with other paths to occasionally create some unorthodox small gains.

Yin-yang life extension method was one of such results.

Another of such small gains were abortion Gu, safe pregnancy Gu, multiple pregnancy Gu, become pregnant Gu, reincarnation Gu, dead fetus Gu, and others.

Multiple pregnancy Gu was what Fang Yuan wanted.

Rank one could be used to produce one child, rank two produced twins. Rank three produced triplets, rank four produced quadruplets, and rank five produced quintuplets.

Chapter 2299: Floating Refinement Hive

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

“So, can you tell me anything about my father?” Gu Yue Fang Xiang looked at the hairy man Gu Immortal in front of him.

Beside him, there was a female immortal.

The hairy man Gu Immortal Twelfth Hair took a look at the female immortal before casting his gaze at Gu Yue Fang Xiang.

This female immortal was mermaid Lian Ke Xin.

It turned out that after Gu Yue Fang Xiang passed the tribulation to become a Gu Immortal and returned to the hairy man continent, he saw his mother—Steel Thread City Lord—who was in an unconscious state.

Lian Ke Xin had been helping him with his tribulation, she explained the truth of this world to him, Gu Yue Fang Xiang realized that to save his mother, he needed to make sufficient contributions to the Great Love Immortal Venerable of this world. In that case, he could use contribution points that he earned to issue a mission for those healing Gu Immortals to heal his mother.

Moreover, Lian Ke Xin told Fang Xiang that this hairy man continent was governed by a hairy man Gu Immortal, if he wanted to find his father, he could go and ask him.

Under Lian Ke Xin’s lead, Gu Yue Fang Xiang met Twelfth Hair for the first time, he asked about the information regarding his father.

Twelfth Hair nodded: ”I do know something... about your father. But that is from long ago, if you want to know, help me with something.”

Gu Yue Fang Xiang was a little hesitant, he did not agree immediately.

Lian Ke Xin saw this and immediately said: ”Friend Twelfth Hair, Fang Xiang has just become an immortal, if you want to request a difficult task, we will have to decline.”

Gu Yue Fang Xiang casted a grateful gaze at Lian Ke Xin.

Twelfth Hair laughed loudly: ”Friend Fang Xiang has half of our hairy man bloodline, why will I bully him? Don’t worry, this matter involves the arrangement of Floating Refinement Hive.”

“Oh? You have already refined this hive?” Lian Ke Xin was really surprised.

Twelfth Hair answered: ”With the method that our master created personally, we hairy man Gu Immortals only had to follow the instructions to achieve success.”

Next, Twelfth Hair looked at Fang Xiang: ”Floating Refinement Hive has already been created, you only need to place it inside Refinement Sea. This is much easier than creating it, if you can complete the mission, I will tell you things about your father.”

Gu Yue Fang Xiang could not decide, he looked towards Lian Ke Xin subconsciously.

Lian Ke Xin smiled at him and nodded.

“Alright, I’ll do it.” Gu Yue Fang Xiang immediately decided.

Thus, Twelfth Hair transferred the Floating Refinement Hive into Gu Yue Fang Xiang’s immortal aperture.

Gu Yue Fang Xiang saw the Floating Refinement Hive for the first time, this structure was quite peculiar, it was large as a mountain but had the appearance and structure of a beehive, there were many small spaces of various sizes inside.

Floating Refinement Hive had a narrow top and a broad bottom which was the base of the hive, it could float on the sea and resist huge waves with great stability.

“This is amazing!” Fang Xiang used investigative methods and observed, his eyes stared wide in amazement.

Twelfth Hair laughed and said in a proud tone: ”This is invented by our master, of course it is amazing. Each Floating Refinement Hive can be considered an incomplete secluded domain of heaven and earth. It contains countless refinement path dao marks, if one refined Gu inside, not only will the success rate be much higher, they can even save on the cost of Gu refinement.”

“Floating Refinement Hive can not only accommodate countless refinement path Gu Masters, it can also hold ten refinement path Gu Immortals at most. With refinement path Gu Immortals stationed here, the hive can continuously produce Immortal Gu! Each Floating Refinement Hive can be seen as a refinement path super resource point.”

“Alright, there is no time, get going now.”

Fang Xiang nodded and immediately set off to Refinement Sea with Lian Ke Xin.

Refinement Sea was at the center of Mini Eastern Sea, it was not large compared to the other sea areas but it had extraordinary value.

“This is a genuine secluded domain of heaven and earth!” After hearing Lian Ke Xin’s explanation, Fang Yuan understood the value of Refinement Sea.

“Master is really amazing! His methods are unfathomable like true immortal deities, he can even create his own secluded domain of heaven and earth.” Fang Xiang praised continuously.

The current Refinement Sea had already been completed by Fang Yuan, it was a genuine secluded domain of heaven and earth!

Back then, Lang Ya land spirit used calamities and tribulations to collect water path dao marks and painstakingly built the incomplete Refinement Sea. After Fang Yuan obtained it, his speed of building it was many times faster.

Firstly, Fang Yuan was a venerable, he was even stronger than Long Hair Ancestor, not to mention Lang Ya land spirit.

Secondly, Fang Yuan was a supreme grandmaster in refinement path. The current supreme grandmaster was far superior to the supreme grandmaster of the past.

Thirdly, Fang Yuan had sovereign immortal body with non-conflicting dao marks, he could use methods of any path. He directly used water path methods that were far more efficient than Lang Ya land spirit’s idea.

Fang Xiang soon found his destination, but there was a need to create an immortal formation here. The content was much more difficult that he imagined.

That was because there was more than one Floating Refinement Hive, in the current Refinement Sea, there were many other hives.

Arranging the Floating Refinement Hive was not as simple as dumping it here. It needed a stable location to form a certain connection with the surrounding Floating Refinement Hives.

After the Floating Refinement Hives reached a certain number, the immortal formation would activate and cause all the hives to float around with the waves of Refinement Sea.

They were like ink pens that drew a painting on this Refinement Sea as the canvas. Refinement Sea helped the Refinement Hives to refine Gu while the Refinement Hives replenished the Refinement Sea after it was expended greatly.

This was a grand system that was established!

Under Lian Ke Xin’s guidance and cooperation, Fang Xiang started arranging the immortal formation.

Three days later, they only completed ten percent of it.

“This will not do, it is too slow.” Lian Ke Xin immediately decided as she used some contribution points to post a mission to recruit helpers.

Not long after, a Gu Immortal came.

“I am a newly advanced formation path Gu Immortal, Ni Lao Shi.” This Ni clan Gu Immortal was a purebred human, he accepted Lian Ke Xin’s mission.

With his help, there was rapid progress.

Three days passed, the arrangement of Refinement Hive was finally completed.

Fang Xiang and Ni Lao Shi left with lingering reluctance, they became good friends after three days.

Fang Xiang had spent his entire life on the hairy man continent, he rarely interacted with humans. He knew that his father was a human, so he bore curiosity and good feelings for them.

Ni Lao Shi was honest and loyal, it was natural that they became good friends.

Fang Xiang’s perspective of the humans improved again.

After completing Twelfth Hair’s mission, he returned to the hairy man continent and asked about his father.

As for Ni Lao Shi, he took a sum of contribution points from Lian Ke Xin and immediately went back to his clan.

After returning to Ni clan’s territory, he was welcomed by the entire clan’s cheers.

Ni clan was originally situated in Southern Border, it was moved into the sovereign immortal aperture by Fang Yuan to research the human path Gu refinement method.

Right now, Fang Yuan became a refinement path venerable, Ni clan lost its value but still remained in the sovereign immortal aperture to develop.

Ni clan had several Gu Immortal seeds, but the least outstanding Ni Lao Shi actually succeeded in the immortal ascension.

With a Gu Immortal, Ni clan became a super force.

Ni Lao Shi assembled the higher-ups of Ni clan and expressed his thoughts to them.

“One of master’s clones has some gains from researching dream path, he is able to create a dream path formation to raise the aptitude of an entire clan. I already have sufficient contribution points, I’ll bring you to the formation now, what do you think?”

Seeing that Ni Lao Shi had become an immortal but did not forget his roots, the higher-ups were very moved that he still cared about their development, they nodded their heads in agreement.

Ni Lao Shi placed the clansmen into his immortal aperture as he set off to find Meng Qiu Zhen.

After Ni Lao Shi paid his respects and stated his intention, Meng Qiu Zhen brought him to a dream path formation.

Ni Lao Shi paid the necessary contribution points as Meng Qiu Zhen activated the formation. The former opened his immortal aperture door and let out his clansmen who walked into the dream path formation.

“Will there be any issues?” Ni Lao Shi stared with a fixed gaze until the final Ni clansman walked into the formation.

He had an expression of worry as he said that, especially when his parents were among them.

Meng Qiu Zhen smiled lightly as he shook his head: ”How can that be? Don’t worry.”

Saying so, he activated the formation.

At the next moment, all the Ni clansmen who entered the formation fell onto the ground as some started snoring, they had all fallen asleep.

However, there was a chain of explosions that soon followed.

These Ni clansmen had all self-detonated and died in their dreams.

Their blood was extracted by the formation and pumped into the sole surviving Ni clansman.

After completing everything, Human Sea who was deep within the formation also activated.

Thus, the self-detonated Ni clansmen were revived but they remained asleep.

“How many clans have already come to this place?” Ni Lao Shi asked.

“There were four, you are the fifth clan.” Meng Qiu Zhen said: ”Don’t worry, this formation is very safe.”

At the same time, the Ni clansmen started the second round of self-detonation, but this time, the final survivor was switched to another person.

Like this, they were revived and slaughtered continuously until all the Ni clan members’ aptitude rose.

Meng Qiu Zhen stopped the formation and woke them up.

Immediately, waves of astonishment hit the Ni clansmen as they cheered and shouted with loud voices.

“Amazing, my aptitude improved!”

“What method is this? It is so strong, so strong!”

“Ni Lao Shi is a really good child, he did not forget us even after immortal ascension, he repaid us fully.”

Ni Lao Shi inspected everyone, almost all of them had A grade aptitude.

“This is truly a miracle. I guess only someone like master can perform such legendary acts.” Ni Lao Shi was very shocked, his admiration towards Fang Yuan grew deeper.

But he did not know the truth.

Dream path formation? No, this was clearly a blood path formation!

But dream path was a great cover that could convince many Gu Immortals. After all, they had all fallen asleep, it was quite similar to dream path methods, so this seemed quite normal on the surface.

Chapter 2300: Born with a Rank Five Gu

Fang Yuan’s divine sense spread rapidly in the sovereign immortal aperture.

“Maybe I should build some small wisdom path formations so my divine sense can spread here more easily?” Fang Yuan thought.

His divine sense was moving at a rapid speed but the sovereign immortal aperture was just too big. It was too troublesome for Fang Yuan to look into his immortal aperture closely each time he entered.

Ordinary Gu Immortals had no such issue. Although their immortal aperture was called a small world, it could not compare to Fang Yuan’s sovereign immortal aperture.

Not long after, Fang Yuan’s divine sense reached the destination.

Mini Western Desert, Inkman City.

There was a family at an unassuming corner of the city.

The man of the family was a young inkman Gu Master, he had limited aptitude and only had rank two cultivation. Currently, he had a nervous expression as he paced outside the room.

Waaaa—!

The crying of a baby could be heard coming from within the room.

The man immediately showed an expression of joy.

He rushed into the room and saw his wife and the female doctor who he had hired at a high price.

The female doctor was hiding a male inkman baby.

He was very small and ugly but was healthy.

“Everything is normal, except...” The female doctor smiled at the man and directed her gaze to the baby’s arm.

In his hands, there were a pair of Gu worms.

They were bone flesh unity Gu!

The female doctor had an expression of shock, because she was the doctor here, she saw that this pair of Gu worms were born alongside the baby.

“If I had not been here the entire time, I would not have believed this. Is this... the effect of the Pregnancy Temple?” The female doctor asked the male inkman.

The male inkman saw this immediately.

His eyes turned red after seeing the Gu worms.

With his strength and wealth, he would need to expend a vast amount of time and effort to get such Gu worms.

But now, this pair of rare Gu worms was born alongside his son!

This was such a huge surprise.

The male inkman nodded, he said chokingly: ”Yes, after the Pregnancy Temple was built, my wife and I went to give it a try. To think that it really worked!”

The female doctor sighed and said: ”You must not be the only one. This Pregnancy Temple really works as they said, it can help you to rapidly have children, and if lucky, they will be born with Gu worms.”

The male inkman wanted to speak but hesitated.

The female doctor casted him a gaze of suspicion.

On the bed, the weak female inkman spoke now, she wanted the doctor to test their bloodline.

The female doctor was stunned, she realized that they were worried this baby was not their own.

Immediately after, the test was completed.

It was a joyful ending.

“This is my son, I finally have a son. Oh goodness, I finally have a son!” The male inkman had no hesitation anymore, he held the baby and cried tears of joy.

Fang Yuan’s divine sense observed the scene and left quietly.

This Pregnancy Temple was his arrangement.

There were many of such mortal Gu Houses, after Fang Yuan built them, he placed them all over the sovereign immortal aperture for the people to use.

Pregnancy Temple was a human path Immortal Gu House, the core human path Gu worms it used included: become pregnant Gu, triplet Gu, dead fetus Gu, multiple pregnancy Gu, and safe pregnancy Gu.

It even used a large number of time path and refinement path Gu worms.

The actual effect of Pregnancy Temple was to extract the yin-yang qi of the male and female to activate become pregnant Gu and make the female pregnant.

After that, it would use triplet Gu to turn the fetus into triplets.

After that, two of the fetuses would be used as Gu materials after dead fetus Gu activated, while the final one would be protected by safe pregnancy Gu.

The two dead fetuses would be refined as bone flesh unity Gu, born together with the final fetus.

The entire process of the pregnancy to childbirth would not take more than seven days, this was the effect of time path Gu worms.

In that case, the sovereign immortal aperture’s population would rise rapidly. Once the population went up, more clans would be created, and under the effect of the ’dream path method’, their aptitudes would rise together and produce more Gu Immortal seeds.

Throughout the process, the citizens of the sovereign immortal aperture would feel more admiration and love towards their great leader Fang Yuan, they would feel indebted to him!

It was clear that they would become increasingly loyal to him.

“The bone flesh unity Gu that comes with the baby act as the vital Gu and is refined naturally. Once these babies are born, they will have a rank five vital Gu. After bone flesh unity Gu reaches a certain level, they will switch to other Gu worms. In that case, the growth of these babies will be accelerated!”

Fang Yuan planned inwardly.

It was not hard for the current him to achieve this, it was completely a breeze.

He used the human body Gu refinement method, which was one of the peak profundities of refinement path, originating from Ni clan.

When Ni clan’s bloodline reach a certain density, the current generation Ni Xiang would be born with an Immortal Gu appearing in their body.

Fang Yuan was only producing mortal Gu now.

“When Giant Sun Immortal Venerable created yin-yang path, the essence was in Gu worms like abortion Gu, safe pregnancy Gu, and multiple pregnancy Gu. All the past venerables have comprehended some human path killer moves from <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>, but these methods are too profound and not suited for the masses. Thus, Heavenly Court arranged for Divine Emperor City to develop the foundation of human path.”

“The truth is, there is a very special man among the venerables, he had actually created many foundational mortal Gu of human path, but had always kept them to himself and did not popularize them.”

“The prospect and development of human path is truly great.” Fang Yuan sighed.

Higher level human path killer moves were able to easily turn the situation of the fate war around, while lower level methods had incredible use.

Fang Yuan was certain that human path was not inferior to heaven path!

Most importantly, human path had not developed yet.

“Human path is suppressed by the Heavenly Dao. Just these human path mortal Gu that are created by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable have such a terrifying effect. How can the Heavenly Dao that emphasizes balance allow such a qualitative change in the growth of humanity?”

Fang Yuan was increasingly understanding why Heavenly Court was focusing on developing human path.

Heavenly Court had always been tampering with heaven’s will using fate Gu as their pillar.

After fate Gu was destroyed, Heavenly Court became the number one super force that heaven’s will disliked.

Being unable to use heaven’s will, Heavenly Court decided to develop human path instead.

“But why would Star Constellation Immortal Venerable not know about the weakness of the derivation formation?” Fang Yuan had a deep and eerie gaze.

Derivation formation was situated in Heavenly Court, any research results that it produced would be known by heaven’s will.

This meant that as those Gu cultivators who entered the derivation formation grew, the Heavenly Dao also grew together with them!

But even if the Heavenly Dao gained from this, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable still had benefits to gain from using the derivation formation.

She could develop herself to surpass the other venerables.

It was possible that in her plan, she would first eliminate the other venerables and make Heavenly Court the dominating force before dealing with heaven’s will.

“Thus, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable has not entered the derivation formation herself, or is she waiting for a chance?” Fang Yuan guessed to himself.

At least, Fang Yuan knew that Crazed Demon Cave was the most suitable place to put the derivation formation.

The first seven layers of Crazed Demon Cave could not isolate heaven’s will, but the eighth and ninth layers were safe.

Other than that, Fang Yuan could not see any other possibilities.

It would not work if one placed the derivation formation into a venerable aperture.

Because the wild derivation Gu was rank nine, it contained too much heaven’s will. If placed into the venerable’s immortal aperture, the heaven’s will within would connect with the heaven’s will of the five regions, allowing the venerable to be detected by heaven’s will.

Fang Yuan had once suffered a loss from this.

“Limitless Demon Venerable created the Crazed Demon formation, but Star Constellation Immortal Venerable must have been a part of it. After all, the formation needs wisdom path’s help. This is also why Star Constellation Immortal Venerable held the initiative in Crazed Demon Cave, after returning to Heavenly Court, she easily created the derivation formation. But Crazed Demon Cave itself must have been made by Limitless Demon Venerable alone. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable does not know of its profundity, otherwise, it will be the first thing she constructs.”

Fang Yuan’s divine sense continued to search.

There were many families in Inkman City that had given birth to children.

The situation was quite successful, each newborn had a bone flesh unity Gu as their vital Gu.

Come to speak of it, bone flesh unity Gu’s recipe was modified by Fang Yuan.

Rank eight wisdom Gu was of some help to Fang Yuan.

During this period of time, he easily raised wisdom Gu to rank eight.

In addition, Refinement Sea and Human Sea were completed.

It was just that Human Sea lacked Human Mountain, it was not a complete secluded domain now and could still be expended.

The cost of reviving mortals was much cheaper than Gu Immortals, it could last for a very long time.

Other than Human Sea and Refinement Sea, Fang Yuan had also collected many fragments of the Qian Kun Crystal Wall.

Most of the Qian Kun Crystal Wall fragments scattered in Eastern Sea, Southern Border, and Western Desert were currently in Fang Yuan’s hands.

As for the other two regions, because of the existence of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, Fang Yuan did not ask about them when he used stealing heavenly secret.

The complete Qian Kun Crystal Wall was even stronger than stealing heavenly secret, it contained the information of all situations that happened in the world.

If stealing heavenly secret was said to be a ladle that was drawing water from the vat, then the Qian Kun Crystal Wall was the vat itself!

According to Fang Yuan’s understanding after using stealing heavenly secret, the complete Qian Kun Crystal Wall could create Primordial Domain!!

Moving his divine sense, Fang Yuan left Inkman City and came to Mini Eastern Sea to inspect the Floating Refinement Hives.

These Floating Refinement Hives were arranged appropriately, there were no issues.

They were originally derived from the Fang Yuan stone nest.

Back then, Fang Yuan had the concept of a production line, he created these stone nests and arranged for many hairy man Gu Masters to refine Gu.

Right now, each of the Floating Refinement Hives were an incomplete secluded domain of heaven and earth, they were far superior to the Fang Yuan stone nest back then.

There were already many hairy man Gu Masters in some of the Floating Refinement Hives.

The first batch of Gu worms to refine were relic Gu and connecting heaven Gu.

After Fang Yuan’s divine sense looked around for a while, he left again.

After a while, under the control of his divine sense, countless Gu worms expended his rich reserves of rank nine immortal essence to activate an immortal killer move — Endless Trouble.

The core Immortal Gu of this move was rank eight After, it could delay the current calamity or tribulation to the next time, and face them together.

Fang Yuan had already modified this killer move and used it many times.

He adjusted the sovereign immortal aperture’s time flow to make it much faster, this caused calamities and tribulations to occur more frequently, but each time, Fang Yuan used endless trouble killer move to delay them to the next tribulation.

Such an action infuriated heaven’s will, when the actual tribulation occurs, it would be extremely strong.

For this was a flaw that Fang Yuan could benefit from.

Even if the tribulations erupted with the anger of heaven’s will and became more powerful, Fang Yuan was confident of passing them and getting a large number of dao marks!

Chapter 2301: Heaven Path Dream Realm

The truth was, Fang Yuan had no choice but to use endless trouble killer move.

If he had to undergo tribulation, he would need to place the sovereign immortal aperture in the five regions and draw in heaven and earth qi. At that time, heaven’s will would control them and form tribulations.

The calamities and tribulations were not scary, Fang Yuan was confident of dealing with them.

But during his tribulation, the other venerables would definitely come to probe and suppress him.

But at that time, his sovereign immortal aperture would not be movable, because of the deep involvement of heaven’s will, if the venerables attacked too fiercely, obscured heavenly secret might not be able to conceal Fang Yuan anymore.

Fang Yuan would be exposed.

“Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable must also be using methods to delay their tribulations.” Fang Yuan was certain about this.

In this contest of three venerables, nobody wanted to be the first to undergo tribulation. Whoever did that would expose a flaw first and face suppression.

If they were targeted too badly, it would be hard to catch up to the other venerables anymore.

There would be a danger of dying.

This was true for grand tribulations and myriad tribulations, while the chaotic disaster was a huge flaw of the venerables!

“After using endless trouble this time, I am not far from the next chaotic disaster.” Fang Yuan thought.

Venerables faced a grand tribulation every ten years, a myriad tribulation every fifty years, and a chaotic disaster every one hundred years.

That was to say, after eight grand tribulations and one myriad tribulation, they would face one chaotic disaster.

Fang Yuan had already used endless trouble many times, he was two grand tribulations away from the chaotic disaster.

In this aspect, Fang Yuan was the venerable with the biggest problem.

“Oh?” After endless trouble was used successfully, Fang Yuan’s expression changed slightly.

Although endless trouble succeeded like many of the previous attempts, there was a difference now.

Fang Yuan felt a faint sense of hunger.

After gaining sovereign immortal body, it needed to consume food or it would get hungry. But this hunger was not like the normal feeling of hunger — it originated from his origin!

Fang Yuan’s expression gradually turned solemn.

He knew why.

This was the sovereign immortal aperture’s desire to eat a venerable immortal aperture.

Sovereign immortal body originally had this flaw, or rather, weakness. But in Fang Yuan’s estimations, there was still some time left after becoming rank nine.

To think that he was already feeling faint hunger that could not be ignored.

This was much earlier than he had expected.

“Is it because the sovereign immortal aperture has grown too big and annexed too many grotto-heavens, since even now, I am still bringing in resource points?”

Fang Yuan vaguely felt that this was the truth.

He had developed the sovereign immortal aperture too well.

The greatest weakness and also advantage of the sovereign immortal aperture were the non-conflicting dao marks.

But because the sovereign immortal aperture’s development was too good, and because of the non-conflicting dao marks, its foundation was unstable.

“But before, even with rank eight cultivation level, I have never felt such hunger.”

“After becoming venerable, this feeling emerged, what is the reason?”

“No matter what, the four paths of refinement path, food path, heaven path, and human path hold the possibility of resolving sovereign immortal body’s problem of requiring food.”

Fang Yuan analyzed continuously in his mind.

He was most skilled in refinement path, there was no need to explain it. As long as he raised the sovereign immortal body to rank ten, the problem would be resolved.

Food path could replenish the expenditure and promote growth. Children need to eat food to have enough nourishment to grow. Sovereign immortal body held the same logic.

As for human path and heaven path...

Sovereign immortal fetus Gu was made using the ten extreme physiques as the main materials, it was a pure human path Gu worm. But in the end, it transformed into sovereign immortal body that had the sovereign immortal aperture. In this aspect, it contained heaven path profundity.

And the effect of having non-conflicting dao marks was also part of heaven path.

Now, the problem was that these four paths were theoretically capable of resolving the issue of sovereign immortal body’s food requirement. The issue was that Fang Yuan did not know which path was the most feasible and possible one.

Fang Yuan knew most about refinement path, he needed to modify and innovate to resolve sovereign immortal body’s issue.

Food path and human path were not developed yet.

Heaven path was uncertain too, there might not be any solution available, Fang Yuan might have to create his own method. After all, rank nine sovereign immortal fetus Gu had already broken the balance of the Heavenly Dao, it was a grand feat achieved by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

It was very difficult for Fang Yuan to resolve the root issue of sovereign immortal body’s food requirement.

Even though he was a venerable, he was not confident of doing it, he needed to invest resources and effort to make deductions. After all, rank nine sovereign immortal fetus Gu was an unprecedented creation.

Other than solving the root cause, there were also methods to alleviate it.

That was to satisfy the hunger and devour a venerable immortal aperture!

This difficulty was quite high.

It meant that Fang Yuan would have to defeat a venerable.

If there was just one venerable, Fang Yuan might have an easier time. The issue was that many venerables existed now, if one person was too outstanding, there would be a huge chain reaction. Fang Yuan did not have the strength to suppress all the venerables at once, if he was exposed, the situation would be troublesome for him.

“But if I can annex a venerable’s aperture, there is also a good aspect in that I can skip tribulations.”

“This means that if I plan properly, I will not need to take a risk and undergo the chaotic disaster, I can directly skip this huge problem!”

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan was moved internally.

He thought of Paradise Earth.

Paradise Earth was killed by him in Crazed Demon Cave, his soul dissipated but his immortal body and aperture remained.

Because he cultivated heaven path, the immortal aperture was very stable unlike other paths. Thus, Fang Yuan was able to preserve it until now.

Although Paradise Earth’s immortal aperture was only rank eight, it was merely a step away from venerable level.

Paradise Earth’s immortal body had enough heaven path dao marks, he only lacked heaven path attainment level to become a heaven path venerable.

That was to say, as long as Fang Yuan used split soul to take over Paradise Earth’s immortal aperture and body, he would gain a heaven path clone.

“A heaven path clone with rank eight cultivation level, but it is only a step away from venerable level.” Fang Yuan was moved.

If his heaven path attainment level could reach supreme grandmaster, he would immediately be able to create a heaven path venerable clone!

At that time, be it to fight against other venerables or to annex this venerable immortal aperture, it would be very useful to Fang Yuan!

“It is a pity there is only a bit of truthful floating ice left, I’ve used most of it. The remaining part cannot allow me to become a supreme grandmaster in heaven path.”

Spectral heaven.

“Zi Wei, you can’t escape.” Duke Tong quickly shortened the distance between him and Fairy Zi Wei.

Fairy Zi Wei’s expression was quite pale, Ying Wu Xie who was in her arms said: ”Let me block them, you should escape.”

Heavenly Court had countless methods, Duke Tong and the rest were revived Gu Immortal seniors, even as a wisdom path great expert, Fairy Zi Wei could not hide for long.

Most importantly, the environment in spectral heaven changed, the previous black-white overturning clouds had completely vanished, Fairy Zi Wei could not use them anymore. Thus, even though she could escape from them temporarily, she would be found by them after a short

period of time and they would catch up in no time.

Seeing that Duke Tong was reaching her again, Fairy Zi Wei felt despair in her heart.

It was not easy to last this long, she was already at her wits’ end.

“Feng Jiu Ge, when are you going to take action?” Fairy Zi Wei shouted.

Duke Tong snickered in disdain: ”Zi Wei, how long are you going to keep up this act?”

Feng Jiu Ge did not appear after all, he was not Shadow Sect’s savior.

But another change occurred.

A pink beast growled and charged at them while covered in an illusory halo.

“What is this?!” Duke Tong stared with wide eyes.

“Dream realm?” Fairy Zi Wei gritted her teeth, she flew towards the pink beast and got devoured in one mouthful without dodging it.

After devouring Fairy Zi Wei and Ying Wu Xie, the beast was not satisfied, it charged towards Duke Tong instead of stopping.

Facing the intense dream path aura, Duke Tong had no choice but to dodge.

“Dream realm? Why is it in a beast form?!” Duke Tong was helpless, he could not enter or leave the dream realm at will.

Moreover, this dream realm was different from what was described in their intel, it could move around and hunt prey.

“Compared to the dream realm that we are used to, this current one fits the description in <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>, what is going on?”

Duke Tong was bewildered.

While reporting to Heavenly Court, he chased after the dream realm.

When the dream realm attacked, he retreated, after it left, he followed it from afar.

Afterwards, he discovered even more dream realms.

These dream realms had various forms but they were all beasts.

“Dream realms that have gathered into a group! This is a new transformation in spectral heaven!!” Duke Tong was increasingly suspicious, he watched as the dream realm that devoured Fairy Zi Wei and Ying Wu Xie mixed into the group.

Duke Tong’s investigative methods were ineffective on dream realms, and because they were constantly changing forms, he soon lost all traces of that particular dream realm, he could not tell which one was it.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable soon received Duke Tong’s information.

She sighed as her gaze flickered with uncertainty: ”Heaven path dream realms... they finally appeared. One of them even devoured Fairy Zi Wei and Ying Wu Xie, this is all the ploy of heaven’s will.”

In Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s plan, Ying Wu Xie was crucial. If she could capture it, she would have the best pawn to use against Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

But now, although Duke Tong chased after him, heaven path dream realms appeared at the crucial moment and destroyed her plan.

“In that case...” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable immediately used her backup plan, she contacted and gave orders to Fairy Maiden Soul.

This soul path great expert received the orders and immediately showed an incredulous expression.

Afterwards, she returned to Heavenly Court and entered the treasury, taking out a soul.

Next, she placed this soul into her immortal aperture and used her method to nourish the soul while altering its memories.

Time passed quickly in the immortal aperture.

Several days later in the immortal aperture, Fairy Maiden Soul’s modification was completed.

She immediately contacted Star Constellation Immortal Venerable: ”Bo Qing’s soul has already been modified.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable received the news and nodded.

Now, all they needed was the body of a sword path Gu Immortal.

Chapter 2302: Contest of the Three Venerables Again

“Where am I?”

“Who... who am I?”

Fairy Zi Wei woke up in a dream, but she forgot about herself.

As she scanned her surroundings in a daze, she saw that she was in a vast desolate yellow plain with no signs of life.

She lowered her head to look at herself, but her body was that of a mudman. She had short hands and feet, her body was also hard and dry.

“I feel like I have forgotten something important.”

Fairy Zi Wei frowned, but she could not remember no matter how hard she tried.

She even forgot if that important thing was a situation or a person.

She could not figure it out.

However, this bleak yellow land gave her a warm feeling of closeness.

“Home?” This word emerged in Fairy Zi Wei’s mind.

But this desolate home made her feel sad as well.

Wind blew over at this time.

The wind got increasingly stronger, blowing the soil into the air.

Splash splash splash.

There were no clouds in the sky, but heavy rain started to fall.

Countless bean-sized raindrops smashed on the yellow soil.

Soon, a large marshy land was formed.

Fairy Zi Wei was in the marsh, her whole body got drenched as she ended up in a miserable state.

But despite the wild storm, her head was always raised and her vision was not blocked even a bit.

She discovered that she knew everything about this yellow land.

She also had a feeling that she could control this storm, it seemed to be as simple as moving her fingers.

Hence, she thought to herself: ”This storm is too big, make it smaller.”

At the next moment, the storm really became smaller.

Hints of greenery appeared in the marsh and spread everywhere.

These were the young shoots of weeds.

Fairy Zi Wei felt endless joy at the sight of these weeds.

This was life.

Finally, she stopped feeling alone.

“Such a pity that they grow too slowly, it will be better if they grew faster.”

The weeds began to grow faster.

With a speed visible to the naked eye, the emerging greenery began to flourish and spread. The grass became taller and covered her feet, and this bleak yellow land turned into a grassland.

Some sunken areas were filled with rainwater and became clear ponds.

Fairy Zi Wei moved across the lush grass and stood beside a pond. Her image was reflected on the water surface as she finally saw her appearance.

She was a clay doll made of purple clay. Her eyes, nose and mouth were drawn with golden lines.

Fairy Zi Wei suddenly realized her identity.

“That’s right, I am this blessed land’s... land spirit.”

Central Continent.

Below star array calculation formation, outside of Embroidered Tower.

“Bai Qing (Feng Jin Huang) pays respect to Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.” A pair of mother and daughter greeted respectfully.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s main body was staying inside Embroidered Tower.

She did not invite this pair of mother and daughter inside Embroidered Tower, instead she used an information path mortal Gu to show a video in the space outside Embroidered Tower.

After the video showed the scene of those heaven path dream realms, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable spoke: ”Feng Jin Huang, have you seen this kind of dream realm before?”

Feng Jin Huang had been watching with concentration, she replied: ”Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, junior has never seen this kind of dream realm. But, from my speculations, the present dream realms can be divided into three types according to their sources. They are human path, beasts and plants, as well as heaven path dream realms.”

“The source of human path dream realms are the humans or variant humans, these are their dreams. The source of beast and plant dream realms are those beasts and plants that once existed or are still living now. As for heaven path dream realms, the source is heaven and earth itself.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable nodded slightly: ”Good, make your preparations. I will need you to go to spectral heaven to explore these heaven path dream realms in due time.”

Feng Jin Huang, however, shook her head, refusing firmly: ”Please excuse junior for being unable to do it. Junior is only a mortal, I have no confidence in exploring such a level of dream realms, and also have no way to guarantee my own safety.”

“Hmm?” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s brows rose slightly as she had not expected Feng Jin Huang to reject her so directly.

At this time, everyone went silent.

Fairy Bai Qing was stressed out, she wanted to speak but could not say anything in the end.

She felt increasingly suffocated.

Feng Jin Huang still had an indifferent expression, seemingly not feeling any pressure.

“Alright. You may both leave.” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable spoke after a long while.

“Junior takes her leave.” Feng Jin Huang bowed towards Embroidered Tower and left.

Looking at the receding figures of the two, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable sighed lightly with a complicated gaze.

Ying Wu Xie was swallowed by a heaven path dream realm, this was really unfortunate.

He was a great pawn to deal with Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, but was gotten rid of by heaven’s will.

The dream realm could not be explored, that meant that Ying Wu Xie was done for.

Feng Jin Huang’s opinion about heaven path and human path dream realms verified Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s own ideas. But Feng Jin Huang was indeed only a Gu Master and not a Gu Immortal, it was natural for her to be unable to do anything to these dream realms.

“I cannot conceal these heaven path dream realms, it is only a matter of time for the other two venerables to know of them. The contest of three venerables may start once again.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was worried.

Because this was much more complicated than before.

Black and white heaven were gone, only spectral heaven remained.

Spectral heaven was the territory of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

What would Spectral Soul Demon Venerable do if venerables were to barge into his territory?

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had lost his sanity and was filled with heaven’s will, the heaven path dream realms were also the same. What connection did these two have? Would they help each other?

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was weak before; Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had no worries.

But now was different.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had resonated with rank nine fire Gu, and his soul foundation had surged to a terrifying level after slaughtering billions of living beings in the two heavens.

If a conflict occurred between the venerables because of the heaven path dream realms, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was likely to participate and would be an opponent that could not be neglected.

After pondering over it, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable decided to slow down in refining Central Continent’s wisdom path dao marks, she had to save her immortal essence for the battle.

Her intention to get rid of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable became firmer as time passed.

“Since Ying Wu Xie is gone, I need to make proper use of Bo Qing.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable decided to create a powerful Spectral Soul clone.

The risk was high though, after all, tampering with the soul was Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s forte.

Fairy Maiden Soul’s action was tantamount to showing off in front of an expert.

But the situation forced Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s hand, she could not afford to care about this.

Bo Qing’s soul was filled with sword path dao marks which must be paired with a sword path Gu Immortal body. This body should contain an immortal aperture, and the higher its cultivation level, the better.

However, even looking at the whole world, there were not many Gu Immortals who cultivated sword path.

There were a few in Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects, but they were all at rank seven.

In the whole five regions, there was no rank eight lone and demonic cultivator who cultivated sword path. In fact, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s deductions showed that there was only one rank eight sword path Gu Immortal currently.

“Western Desert Lin clan’s first supreme elder?” Prince Feng Xian, Red Heart Traveler, and Nine Spiritual Fairy showed strange expressions.

“Heavenly Court needs his immortal aperture and body, this is related to the contest of venerables and the safety of the world.” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s voice was clear and cold.

The three immortals looked at each other before responding resolutely: ”Please give us your command.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable transmitted her instructions to them, as well as how they should cooperate with Wan Zi Hong and Zhou Xiong Xin.

The three immortals’ gaze shone sharply as they heard the plan and left with great confidence.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was silent for a while, she then contacted the Genesis Lotus’ will in Heavenly Court.

Genesis Lotus’ will had been overseeing Divine Emperor City, but through Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s method, it expanded and split a portion to stay in Heavenly Court.

This portion of Genesis Lotus’ will in Heavenly Court had one main task, that was to nourish Cang Xuan Zi.

Cang Xuan Zi was a legendary immemorial beast, it was a huge vine that connected heaven and earth.

It sprouted in three hundred years, blossomed in three hundred years, and bore fruits in three hundred years. The fruits that it created were called vast heaven fruits, if used in a grotto-heaven, it could expand the size of the immortal aperture’s sky. Thus, this vast heaven vine was also known as the tenth heaven of this world!

It entered Heavenly Court after an agreement with Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable. It was an unique existence in Heavenly Court, it did not need to follow orders, and only had to provide a batch of vast heaven fruits every thousand years.

But in the fate war, it was killed by Fang Yuan’s time cutting edge.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not have any methods to revive it, but Genesis Lotus’ will that originated from Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable had methods to revive Cang Xuan Zi!

“Cang Xuan Zi’s death is actually beneficial to Heavenly Court.” Genesis Lotus’ will communicated with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

“In a hundred or so days, Cang Xuan Zi’s body will be restored. At that time, I will enter and control this body, supplying a legendary immemorial beast’s battle strength to Heavenly Court!”

“An even more amazing thing is that the fruits produced by Cang Xuan Zi will contain my will. Using these fruits to reforge Heavenly Court will isolate us from heaven’s will.”

“There will be a new Heavenly Court in the future, our gains from the derivation formation will belong to us and not be known by heaven’s will.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable nodded: ”This is a long-term plan and not an urgent matter. Have you remembered anything else regarding the revival of Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable?”

Genesis Lotus’ will shook its head: ”I know very little about the revival plan set by my main body. I only know that he left behind a self-portrait from which he can revive. But I have no idea where this self-portrait is.”

“How about you, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable? You are Senior Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s disciple, don’t you know his revival plan?”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable heaved a sigh: ”Truth be said, master told me he left behind two revival methods just in case. The first revival method was Heavenly Court’s qi harvest fruit. However, that Fang Yuan took it before this fruit could ripen. The second method involves the Primordial Origin Treasury.”

“Primordial Origin Treasury?”

“Primordial Origin Treasury was secretly created by master to store the large number of rank eight immortal essence stones produced by Yi Qi Zi back then. The treasury also has master’s arrangements for revival. But I have no way to look for it.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable said that she has no way to look for it, and not that she had no clues.

In fact, she had related clues of both Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable and Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable’s revival methods. Moreover, she already knew they were in Central Continent.

But she could not inspect or probe it.

Because it would then be discovered by other venerables.

With the revival of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, the other venerables were definitely on guard against the revival of other Heavenly Court venerables.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable needed to refine all the wisdom path dao marks in Central Continent before she could conceal these revival plans and not be afraid of other venerables’ inspection.

Even if other venerables saw through it, she could use her terrain advantage in Central Continent to resist the attacks of the venerables and protect Heavenly Court venerables’ revival methods.

Only after Star Constellation Immortal Venerable refined all the wisdom path dao marks in Central Continent could she start reviving other Heavenly Court venerables.

Heavenly Court’s foundation was unfathomably deep.

Once the two venerables revived, they would rule the world once again.

After all, the combined strength of three venerables was unthinkable. They would easily surpass the individual strength of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Fang Yuan.

Even if Giant Sun, Fang Yuan, and Spectral Soul Demon Venerable allied, they would be weaker than Heavenly Court’s three venerables.

It was because of the difference in their ideals!

But the heaven path dream realms appeared which delayed Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s plan once again.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable needed to slow down on refining dao marks, and save her immortal essence to prepare for the battle between venerables!

Northern Plains.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable sighed.

He did his best, but after absorbing rank eight immortal essence stones, the converted immortal essence was only seventy percent of the immortal essence stones.

And this seventy percent immortal essence was only rank eight immortal essence.

“I need to get rid of the heaven’s will, but I don’t cultivate wisdom path. I also lack crucial luck path Immortal Gu.”

“Maybe I can transact with Fang Yuan?”

“No, I can’t reveal any clues about this.”

Eastern Sea.

“Heaven path dream realms? Good! Very good.”

Fang Yuan had been planning to create a heaven path venerable clone not long ago, he was just worried about his lacking heaven path attainment level when heaven path dream realms appeared!

It was just that seizing the heaven path dream realms would probably incite another battle between venerables.

“It is better to refine another rank nine Immortal Gu to help me raise my direct combat strength.”

Fang Yuan began to secretly refine rank nine Immortal Gu.

He had a lot of immortal essence.

Even after refining this rank nine Immortal Gu, he would still have a lot remaining to use in the battle of venerables.

Chapter 2303: Besieging Lin clan’s First Supreme Elder

Back in Western Desert.

Lin Lun Zhou suddenly opened his eyes.

The immortal formation sounded an alarm; someone had intruded!

“Such guts, you dare to invade my Lin clan’s Skeleton Mountain.” Lin Lun Zhou was surprised and furious, checking immediately.

He saw that an Immortal Gu House was violently colliding with the defensive formation.

“Inquiry Dock! Fang clan!!” Lin Lun Zhou’s expression turned serious as he sent request for reinforcements to Lin clan while fully activating the defensive formation.

Ever since Fang clan started the commotion, Lin clan had reinforced the immortal formations in many resource points, and almost all the formations had the ability to transport people.

So, Lin Lun Zhou was not panicked.

As his battle intent rose, he frowned: ”Since Fang clan attacked after remaining in hiding for so many days, they definitely made sufficient preparations. I definitely am not Fang clan’s match by myself, but I can use this immortal formation to stall for time. Once the anti-Fang alliance army arrives, Fang clan will definitely suffer consequences.”

“Of course, if the situation turns bad, I will immediately use the formation to get out... What?!”

Lin Lun Zhou had been controlling the formation when his eyes suddenly opened wide and panic filled him.

To his horror, he found that the formation was restricted.

Although the formation could still operate, its transportation effect was nullified.

“They targeted this after all!!” Lin Lun Zhou clenched his teeth as he forcibly calmed himself, thinking of a way to get out of this predicament.

He felt that not all hope was lost.

He was a rank seven bone path Gu Immortal defending Lin clan’s Skeleton Mountain. This was a bone path resource point and he had a huge territorial advantage here.

Moreover, Lin Lun Zhou was stationed here all year round, he knew this place like the back of his hand.

After thinking for a while, Lin Lun Zhou arranged a portion of his will with some immortal essence while he left quietly.

The defensive formation was still defending with all its strength under the control of his will.

Fang clan’s Immortal Gu House collided again, creating thunderous sounds.

Lin Lun Zhou’s will was shrinking rapidly, but it could still last for some time.

Lin Lun Zhou entered the depths of Skeleton Mountain.

The rocks on Skeleton Mountain were dark and let out soul smoke from time to time. Once in a while, the mountain rocks would produce a skeleton. Some skeletons were like humans, some had animal shapes, there were countless possibilities.

Besides these bone armors, dark mist crows flew above Skeleton Mountain and fed on the soul smoke.

Fang clan’s Immortal Gu House’s attack shook the whole Skeleton Mountain.

The countless skeletons that were among the rocks were originally motionless. But as the mountain started shaking, these skeletons propped themselves up and ran wildly on the mountain.

The skeletons collided and killed each other, creating chaos.

At this moment, Lin Lun Zhou activated a killer move. He transformed into a large mammoth skeleton and started running on the mountain.

He was mixed in among the countless skeletons, becoming inconspicuous.

But not long later, threads of water vapor bound him.

“Friend of Lin clan, why be in a hurry to leave?” Shortly after, a voice entered Lin Lun Zhou’s ears.

Lin Lun Zhou immediately fell into despair: ”Rank eight Gu Immortal? You are not from Fang clan!”

At the next moment, the water vapor ropes moved and bound Lin Lun Zhou tightly.

Lin Lun Zhou struggled madly, but soon, his vision turned black as he lost his consciousness.

News of Fang clan’s attack on Lin clan’s peripheral resource point Skeleton Mountain soon reached Lin clan’s headquarters.

Shortly after, Lin clan contacted the anti-Fang alliance.

By the time the anti-Fang alliance reached Skeleton Mountain, there were only ruins. The whole Skeleton Mountain was gone.

“This is indeed Fang clan’s style!”

“Lin Lun Zhou was the Gu Immortal stationed here, he cultivates bone path and is quite strong, I did not expect him to go missing as well.”

“Sigh, it bodes ill for him.”

“Fang clan came to make trouble again, their sins are unforgivable! Once we catch them, we will rip their skin and cut their tendons to relieve our hatred!!”

Just as the anti-Fang alliance members were cursing Fang clan, another astonishing news arrived.

Dong clan’s peripheral territory, Dragon Roar Volcano, was also attacked by Fang clan.

Dragon Roar Volcano was a fire path resource point, but whenever the volcano erupts, it would produce dragon roars; at that time, a sizable amount of sound path resources could be harvested.

When athe nti-Fang alliance reached Dragon Roar Volcano’s site, they did not see any volcano.

“Heavens, even the underground magma has been taken away.”

“It seems like Fang clan wants to make a big commotion this time!”

“They went into hiding for some time; it was probably to exchange for Immortal Gu or killer moves from Heaven Refining Demon Venerable, and increase their strength. Otherwise, would they dare come out?”

“That’s right. Be it Dragon Roar Volcano or Skeleton Mountain, they are important areas that Fang clan would not have rashly invaded before. But now, both were attacked and taken, Fang clan’s strength has definitely increased greatly.”

“The important thing is, will Fang clan continue their actions? Where is their next target?”

“Where is the closest resource point to Dragon Roar Volcano?”

“It is clear water grassland.”

Clear water grassland was a rarely seen grassland in Western Desert. There was plenty of water and lush grasses here, and it produced water path and wood path cultivation resources.

But just as the anti-Fang alliance was discussing, they received the news of Fang clan capturing clear water grassland.

The anti-Fang alliance was in an uproar.

Fang clan’s action this time shows extremely sharp offensive ability that was several times more powerful than before.

“Skeleton Mountain, Dragon Roar Volcano, clear water grassland... please take a look, Fang clan’s path is already marked, their next target is probably Dong clan’s ascending heavenly pit!”

“Then what are we still waiting for?!”

“Let’s go reinforce them immediately. Dong clan sent a message, ascending heavenly pit is in Dong clan blessed land so it is not heavily guarded.”

“More importantly, Dong clan has not sent any Gu Immortal to guard ascending heavenly pit!”

Gu Immortals were much fewer than resource points. In general, Gu Immortals were stationed in peripheral resource points. And resource points in blessed land would have fewer manpower.

The anti-Fang alliance rushed to ascending heavenly pit without stopping. But when they arrived, the immortal formation was already broken, there was noise coming from the depths of ascending heavenly pit as if Fang clan immortals were still plundering resources.

“We finally caught them!”

“Kill them!”

“We must eradicate Fang clan, otherwise our Western Desert will have no peace.”

The anti-Fang alliance attacked with a bellyful of anger.

But not long later, an immortal formation rose from the heavenly pit, and trapped all of the anti-Fang alliance members.

“We were tricked!”

“Such a powerful immortal formation, I can’t even connect to treasure yellow heaven or send a message.”

“This immortal formation prioritizes in trapping and doesn’t have much offensive power. Crap! Fang clan intentionally arranged this, they don’t want to fight us, they are only trying to plunder resource points.”

“Sigh, what should we do? I wonder which resource point of Dong clan’s will be attacked next.”

Anti-Fang alliance members were trapped by the formation and lost their means to communicate.

At the same time, an emergency news reached Lin clan headquarters: Fang clan’s main force suddenly appeared in evil spirit desert and were attacking giant spirit oasis.

Giant spirit oasis was Lin clan’s super resource point, it was heavily protected and could not be lost.

Lin clan’s first supreme elder was still in closed cultivation, the second elder thought for a while before deciding to make a move personally. He controlled the two Immortal Gu Houses of Lin clan and mobilized as much Gu Immortals as he could towards giant spirit oasis.

At the same time, he also asked for reinforcements from the anti-Fang alliance.

Lin clan’s second supreme elder mobilized their full strength, this was because he had no choice.

Since Fang clan lost their territories, they could easily mobilize all their members. It was extremely difficult for other super forces to resist them.

Lin clan’s second supreme elder had to mobilize enough troops to match Fang clan’s crazed attacks. If the mobilized troops were too few, they would just be asking for defeat against Fang clan.

But with this, Lin clan headquarters naturally became empty.

Bam.

Several figures suddenly landed and roughly killed their way into Lin clan’s headquarters.

They were Prince Feng Xian, Red Heart Traveler, Nine Spiritual Fairy, as well as Wan Zi Hong and Zhou Xiong Xin who just arrived from ascending heavenly pit.

Five rank eight experts attacked Lin clan headquarters.

“Lin clan’s first supreme elder, we came for you.” Red Heart Traveler said loudly.

“If you don’t resist, you will be able to live.” Nine Spiritual Fairy added.

Inside a secret room, Lin clan’s first supreme elder slowly opened his eyes and sighed: ”What has my Lin clan done to provoke such a grand action from Heavenly Court? Heavenly Court is the leader of the righteous path, why are you sneakily attacking a righteous path super force? My Lin clan has never colluded with the demonic path.”

Wan Zi Hong sneered: ”Lin clan’s first supreme elder, stop pretending. You act differently from what you say, you secretly protected Fang clan while colluding with Fang Yuan. Otherwise, how can Fang clan be still at large?”

Zhou Xiong Xin nodded: ”I have already gathered sufficient evidence.”

Lin clan’s first supreme elder was silent for a bit before laughing: ”Heavenly Court? Haha, you are truly Heavenly Court.”

Chapter 2304: Sword Qi Takes Form

Immortal battlefield killer move — Rumor Cage!

Zhou Xiong Xin clapped; in an instant, countless silver text characters emerged and circled Lin clan’s public blessed land.

These characters were large as horse carriages or small as ants, they weaved together into a huge ball, enveloping Heavenly Court five great Gu Immortals and Lin clan’s first supreme elder.

“Success.” Zhou Xiong Xin said with excitement, letting out a breath of relief.

A good start was half the success!

The other four Heavenly Court immortals also looked relieved.

What they were most worried about was Lin clan’s first supreme elder running away.

They were all rank eight Gu Immortals, Heavenly Court was fighting five versus one, but it was very hard to catch a rank eight Gu Immortal who wanted to flee.

With the conflict between dao marks, Gu Immortals could not easily show the advantage of numbers. These five Heavenly Court immortals separately cultivated wood path, information path, fire path, blood path, and transformation path which conflicted with each other.

“Rumor cage really deserves the title of the battlefield killer move with the fastest activation time.”

“But I did not expect Lin clan’s first supreme elder to not dodge or flee.”

“Did he see through it?”

The five Heavenly Court immortals conversed with each other through mental transmission.

They appeared grandly because they had already arranged a temporary formation outside Lin clan’s public blessed land headquarters.

Once Lin clan’s first supreme elder escaped or flew out of the public blessed land, the formation would be triggered and attack him, reducing his speed.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had personally instructed them regarding the requirement of a sword immortal’s immortal aperture and body. These five Heavenly Court members naturally made ample preparations.

Although this formation did not have much offensive power, it was modified by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable herself to target Lin clan’s first supreme elder’s escape methods.

Moreover, public blessed lands always had weaker defense than an individual’s blessed land.

As an information path expert, Zhou Xiong Xin had already gathered relevant information when he moved around in Western Desert.

Lin clan’s first supreme elder was already trapped in rumor cage battlefield!

Prince Feng Xian gave a shout and charged forward.

He flew to the sky and opened his mouth towards the palace.

Whoosh—!

Flames gushed out of his mouth and landed on the ground, growing rapidly into a blazing inferno.

The palace was only a mortal Gu House, it crumbled apart rapidly in the inferno.

Lin clan’s first supreme elder was forced to come out of his seclusion, he flew to the sky and faced the enemies.

Prince Feng Xian, however, retreated slowly.

“Lin clan’s first supreme elder, Lin Jian Xing, have a taste of my attack!” Wan Zi Hong chuckled charmingly as she took the place of Prince Feng Xian.

She activated a wood path killer move. Instantly, flower petals fluttered and covered the battlefield, a fragrant smell spreading along with it.

All the five Heavenly Court immortals held their breath.

Lin Jian Xing had a solemn expression as he pushed forward with his hands. In an instant, sword qi rampaged and formed into a giant wave.

The wave surged and billowed, washing away the poisonous flower petals.

Wan Zi Hong disappeared amidst the petals and appeared behind Lin Jian Xing.

She raised her left little finger that had a sharp purplish nail as she stabbed at Lin Jian Xing.

Immortal killer move — Flower Thorn Stab.

Lin Jian Xing was struck, his figure paused before sword qi rose violently, sealing Wan Zi Hong within!

At the next moment, his previously activated sword qi wave moved backwards.

The surging giant wave drowned Lin Jian Xing and Wan Zi Hong.

The other four Heavenly Court immortals did not do anything to avoid hurting Wan Zi Hong.

The sword qi wave disappeared shortly afterwards, leaving only Lin Jian Xing while Wan Zi Hong disappeared once again.

Flower petals fluttered beside Prince Feng Xian, turning into Wan Zi Hong.

Wan Zi Hong was injured but had a satisfied smile on her face: ”Stall him, he is struck by my method. The longer time goes by, the more thorns will grow in his body, hindering his movement and even stabbing him to death.”

Wan Zi Hong made her contribution, she retreated and began to heal her wounds.

The other Heavenly Court immortals continued to surround Lin Jian Xing, not giving him any time to rest.

Heavenly Court made full use of their numerical advantage.

The silver characters that formed rumor cage began to let out dazzling light. The dense light flowed like water, moving in the air as it gathered and swirled. Next, from the silvery light, silver tigers emerged.

The tigers roared and pounced on Lin Jian Xing.

It was Zhou Xiong Xin’s killer move — Rumors Become Tigers.

Prince Feng Xian made his move next; countless beautiful fire birds appeared out of thin air.

The fire birds burned intensely while having deep intelligence. They formed into groups and followed the tigers.

Red Heart Traveler also made his move.

Blood light pillars crashed down.

Tigers, fire birds, and blood pillars formed three waves of continuous attacks!

Lin Jian Xing was surrounded by the attacks but he did not evade.

Against the incoming attacks, he shouted grandly as sword qi surged out violently and charged towards the tigers.

Sword qi condensed into vines beside the countless tigers and bound them. The vines had countless sword path thorns that pierced deep into the tigers.

Painful roars of tigers resounded as most of them crumbled apart like balloons being popped.

At this time, the fire birds entered the battlefield.

Lin Jian Xing transferred his immortal essence as the sword qi in the battlefield were replenished, turning into fierce wind.

The fierce wind killed all the remaining tigers and blew away countless fire birds, the remaining few fire birds were unsteady and unable to gather into a formation again.

The blood light pillars smashed down, rapidly suppressing the fierce wind.

Lin Jian Xing was forced to move backwards. After pulling some distance, he release a large amount of sword qi.

Sword qi turned into ice walls that confined the blood light pillars and ground them constantly.

Lin Jian Xing neutralized three waves of attacks consecutively, showing his extremely profound sword path attainment.

Nine Spiritual Fairy did not stint on her praise: ”Lin clan’s first supreme elder’s methods have a unique style and are truly extraordinary. I can’t wait anymore, take this!”

Nine Spiritual Fairy turned into an immemorial desolate beast, her roars were like lightning as they shook even the rumor cage.

Nine Spiritual Fairy clashed with Lin Jian Xing, her attacks were filled with great strength, forcing Lin Jian Xing to move back again and again.

Lin Jian Xing continued to retreat, unable to ward off Nine Spiritual Fairy’s charge.

Transformation path and strength path Gu cultivators had a unique advantage when they were vanguards in the battlefield.

The five Heavenly Court immortals continued to attack in turns, suppressing Lin Jian Xing since the start of the fight.

Although their dao marks conflicted, they had an extremely tacit coordination.

Their attacks were like tidal waves, continuing without stopping. On one hand, they suppressed Lin Jian Xing, not giving him any chance or time to study rumor cage battlefield. On the other hand, they were weakening and wearing him down, creating a chance to capture him.

Lin Jian Xing’s sword qi were exquisite and profound, transforming into all kinds of shapes. His extraordinary sword path attainment made even the five Heavenly Court immortals sigh in awe.

But he was just one person after all, two fists cannot rival four hands, let alone when Heavenly Court had five people!

As time passed, the situation got increasingly disadvantageous for Lin Jian Xing.

“Strange, what method did he use to suppress my flower thorn stab?” Wan Zi Hong was inwardly surprised at seeing Lin Jian Xing moving so freely.

Right at this time, Prince Feng Xian suddenly used a killer move.

After Lin Jian Xing was struck, grey flames burned all over his body.

The flames constantly produced fire birds. Lin Jian Xing’s momentum decreased rapidly as his speed also had an obvious reduction.

Seeing the chance, Red Heart Traveler immediately used his killer move, blood sun seal!

He coughed out a mouthful of blood.

The fragrant blood flew to the air and started rotating. Like a miniature blood sun, it emitted endless blood red light as it rushed towards Lin Jian Xing.

Lin Jian Xing was surrounded by sword qi; at this moment, the sword qi flew and turned into a giant python that tried to stop the blood sun.

But this blood sun seemed to be illusory, it passed through the obstruction and struck Lin Jian Xing’s chest, turning into a red sun insignia.

Lin Jian Xing’s expression changed slightly.

The blood sun insignia showed its effect quickly, it formed into blood red lines.

The blood lines covered Lin Jian Xing, gradually forming a blood cocoon.

It seemed like Lin Jian Xing was about to be captured alive; but at the next moment, Lin Jian Xing’s body crumbled apart, turning into a powerful wave of sword qi that slipped out of the blood cocoon.

After flying outside, these sword qi condensed back into Lin Jian Xing.

“He can even do this?”

“No, something is not right!”

“This is not Lin clan’s first supreme elder.”

The five Heavenly Court immortals’ expressions’ changed as they noticed an issue after seeing the situation.

They shockingly found that the trapped Lin Jian Xing was not the Gu Immortal himself, but only a killer move.

All along, the five immortals had been toyed around until now when they discovered it.

“He is only a lump of sword qi, no wonder my flower thorn stab had no effect.”

“So that’s it, this was not Lin clan’s first supreme elder, that’s why he did not try to evade when I used rumor cage.”

Zhou Xiong Xin’s expression was unsightly as he canceled the battlefield killer move.

The five immortals once again appeared in Lin clan’s public blessed land.

The true Lin clan’s first supreme elder Lin Jian Xing was standing in the air with his hands behind his back, showing a smile as he looked at the five immortals: ”You finally came out.”

“Lin Jian Xing, truly formidable. I wonder what the name of this move is called?” Red Heart Traveler smiled warmly as he asked.

Lin Jian Xing nodded slightly and explained: ”This move is called sword qi takes form.”

“Sword qi takes form, truly a great move!” Prince Feng Xian praised sincerely.

“After this battle, no matter what happens to you, this move will definitely be renowned throughout the five regions.” Zhou Xiong Xin commented.

Although they were played, the five Heavenly Court immortals only looked grim-faced but had no loss in confidence or battle intent.

In the battle inside rumor cage, they were also suppressed.

After all, rumor cage created an information path environment which suppressed four of the Heavenly Court immortals. They did not dare to use all their strength in fear of breaking the rumor cage.

Even if it was not destroyed, if there were great impacts, the battlefield would still be broken and reveal gaps from which Lin Jian Xing could escape.

Lin Jian Xing stretched out his palm and showed several Immortal Gu that were bound by sword qi: ”Heavenly Court’s immortal formation is truly amazing, it seemed to have been modified to specifically target my clan’s public blessed land. Is this Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s method?”

The five Heavenly Court immortals could not conceal their serious expressions.

The formation they had secretly arranged outside of Lin clan’s public blessed land was already taken down by Lin Jian Xing.

But at the next moment, Lin Jian Xing waved his hand, throwing the Immortal Gu to the Heavenly Court immortals: ”The Immortal Gu have been returned to you. This is my clan’s headquarters, it won’t be nice if we destroy it, let’s change the location of our fight.”

The five Heavenly Court immortals quietly received the Immortal Gu and looked at each other. Finally, Red Heart Traveler nodded: ”You have unparalleled grace, I am in admiration.”

“There is a desolate area three thousand li from here, please follow me.” Lin Jian Xing flew out of the blessed land, moving at a slow speed with an indifferent attitude.

The Heavenly Court immortals followed closely after.

Chapter 2305: Heavenly Court’s Crushing Defeat

“How do we deal with this?”

“Since the formation is already broken, we can only rely on rumor cage.”

“What is Lin Jian Xing planning?”

“If he is thinking of waiting for the anti-Fang alliance or Western Desert righteous paths’ reinforcements, he will be disappointed.”

Wan Zi Hong, Prince Feng Xian, Zhou Xiong Xin, Red Heart Traveler, and Nine Spiritual Fairy followed Lin Jian Xing while secretly conversing.

Lin Jian Xing’s methods were exceptionally exquisite, ruining the five immortals’ plan.

With just sword qi takes form killer move, he fooled them for so long, making these Heavenly Court immortals feel ashamed of themselves.

Lin Jian Xing’s main body used that time to destroy Heavenly Court’s formation.

This made the Heavenly Court immortals realize that their battle plan had a mistake, they should have designated one person to guard the formation.

In fact, the formation had a certain amount of defensive capability and also had the ability to convey messages. If it was attacked, the message should have been sent. Even if the five Heavenly Court immortals were inside rumor cage, they could still obtain the reminder.

Rumor cage battlefield isolated the inside and outside, the ones inside could not even connect to treasure yellow heaven.

But this message would directly rush to rumor cage, creating subtle vibrations in rumor cage as a warning.

At that time, the five immortals would know that the formation was being destroyed, they would react to the specific situation and send a few people to deal with it.

However, Lin Jian Xing’s methods were exceptional, he quietly dismantled the whole formation without alerting the five Heavenly Court immortals.

However, he still returned the obtained Immortal Gu to these five immortals openly.

Such magnanimity captivated even these Heavenly Court immortals.

Under this situation, when Lin Jian Xing mentioned changing the battlefield, the Heavenly Court immortals were too ashamed to continue fighting in Lin clan’s public blessed land headquarters.

“This is the place.” Lin Jian Xing slowly stopped in the air and turned around to face the Heavenly Court immortals.

The five Heavenly Court immortals looked around, this desert was indeed like Lin Jian Xing said; it was extremely poor with no sign of life and was suitable for the battle.

“Lin Jian Xing, if you don’t resist, I will guarantee with my life that your life will be preserved.” Red Heart Traveler said with a sigh.

Lin Jian Xing scoffed: ”If someone suddenly intrudes your home and frames you for something you did not do, even going as far as to attack you; and afterwards, say that they are going to preserve your life, what will you do?”

“Why talk so much!” Red Heart Traveler was about to reply, when Wan Zi Hong suddenly attacked.

She disappeared and appeared behind Lin Jian Xing in an instant.

She stabbed at Lin Jian Xing’s back with her ten sharp, purplish-black nails that were extremely sharp!

Wan Zi Hong was a demonic immortal recruited by Heavenly Court, she did not lack viciousness and also had her own arrogance.

Lin Jian Xing toyed with her for so long with sword qi takes form, she was already disgruntled.

Right now, she still used flower thorn stab, but with ten times the power!

‘You have a body made of flesh and blood, let me see how long you can resist this.’ Wan Zi Hong’s eyes shone with a ferocious light.

However, at the next moment, there was a thunderous explosion.

By the time Wan Zi Hong reacted, she found she had already flown far away. She could only see the back figure of Lin Jian Xing who had been so close to her, and because of the long distance, he was as small as her palm.

“What happened? What killer move is this?” Wan Zi Hong just had this thought when an intense pain assaulted her.

Guh.

She coughed out blood and found to her horror that her defense killer move was almost destroyed completely.

“What in the world was that move?!” The other Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were also extremely shocked.

Lin Jian Xing’s method was too fast, the Heavenly Court immortals did not see it clearly.

Zhou Xiong Xin quickly retreated and pulled some distance apart.

Nine Spiritual Fairy, however, transformed into an immemorial desolate beast once again and attacked Lin Jian Xing.

Under this situation, the sturdy and tough transformation path Gu Immortal was the best choice to probe the enemy.

Boom!

However, with a thunderous explosion, Nine Spiritual Fairy was also sent flying.

Three of her ribs were broken at the very least.

This time, the other Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were able to barely see the killer move. This was a sword path killer move, it was formed from sword qi and was so fast that it was almost impossible to catch it with naked eyes.

Even with investigative methods, they were only able to barely see it.

“This move is called sword qi lightning roar, please appraise it.” Lin Jian Xing said before counterattacking.

Bam bam bam...

Thunderous explosions rang again and again, the five Heavenly Court immortals were actually forced back.

Naturally, Lin Jian Xing did not use just his sword qi lightning roar killer move, he occasionally used sword qi takes form as well.

Sword qi takes form killer move was exquisite and profound, while sword qi lightning roar was fast, it was extremely fast!

So fast that the five Heavenly Court immortals could not even see it properly; for a while, they could only use defensive methods to resist.

“Lin Jian Xing actually had such methods! Protect me.” Zhou Xiong Xin secretly transmitted his voice.

Red Heart Traveler immediately flew in front of him and activated majestic blood light.

The blood light was like a sphere that completely covered Red Heart Traveler and Zhou Xiong Xin.

Zhou Xiong Xin had just prepared his method for a few breaths of time when Lin Jian Xing sensed it.

Lin Jian Xing pointed at the blood sphere; in an instant, at least three sword qi lightning roar attacked, rapidly destroying the blood sphere.

But Zhou Xiong Xin laughed loudly: ”You fell for it.”

He had already finished preparing and was only intentionally delaying to create a deception of activating a powerful killer move that needed a long period of time to activate.

After all, a killer move with longer activation time was often more powerful.

Zhou Xiong Xin cultivated information path, he activated the move but it could not attack actively. However, if the enemy used a killer move and was blocked by this move, it could capture the information about the enemy’s killer move and give a warning to Zhou Xiong Xin.

Zhou Xiong Xin received early warnings, he quickly used information path methods to share the effect with the other four immortals.

The battle situation had a clear change.

The five Heavenly Court immortals finally stabilized their footing and began to exchange attacks with Lin Jian Xing.

Lin Jian Xing’s sword qi lightning roar killer move was extremely fast, it would hit the target before they could even react.

But Lin Jian Xing still required time to activate this killer move.Zhou Xiong Xin’s information path killer move would give early warnings to Zhou Xiong Xin and the rest when Lin Jian Xing started preparing sword qi lightning roar killer move.

Adding on this little time, the five Heavenly Court immortals were barely able to react.

Both sides fought intensely but the Heavenly Court immortals were actually unable to grasp the control of the situation and were still being suppressed by Lin Jian Xing.

“How is this possible?”

“He is actually so strong? This does not match the intel we have.”

“Sword qi lightning roar and sword qi takes form are already brilliant moves, his combat awareness is even better, far surpassing mine.”

The Heavenly Court immortals were inwardly shaken.

Lin Jian Xing did not just rely on the two moves to dominate them, he showed his terrifying strength as well.

There was no strongest Gu worm, there was no most powerful killer move, but there was always a strongest Gu Immortal.

Lin Jian Xing was nowhere near number one but he vaguely surpassed the five Heavenly Court immortals.

“Our paths are different and impede each other. This will not do!”

“Lin Jian Xing has such battle strength, he needs to be weakened for us to have the chance of using rumor cage killer move.”

“Let me try!”

The five Heavenly Court immortals discussed quickly as Prince Feng Xian stood up.

He sent out lumps of sparks which covered the battlefield in just a few moments.

Lin Jian Xing’s surging sword qi were actually burned by the sparks and whittled down rapidly.

Lin Jian Xing was momentarily stunned, his vital Immortal Gu was rank eight Immortal Gu Sword Qi. Be it sword qi takes form or sword qi lightning roar, they both used Sword Qi as the foundation.

Prince Feng Xian’s move actually burned his sword qi which broke his battle foundation.

At least half of Lin Jian Xing’s sword qi were burned; in an instant, his strength fell rapidly.

The Heavenly Court immortals used this chance to counterattack.

After several exchanges, an opportunity appeared which was grasped by Nine Spiritual Fairy.

Nine Spiritual Fairy turned into a willow tree, its branches coiled around Lin Jian Xing like a python and bound him to the trunk.

Using this chance, Zhou Xiong Xin quickly used rumor cage battlefield killer move.

Seeing that Lin Jian Xing had fallen into the battlefield killer move once again, the five immortals’ spirits rose.

But at the next moment, Nine Spiritual Fairy let out a painful cry. Her willow tree immemorial desolate beast form disappeared as she returned to her human form. She retreated in panic with her whole body covered in blood.

“What happened this time?!” The other four Heavenly Court immortals were astonished.

“Careful!!” Nine Spiritual Fairy was shielded by Zhou Xiong Xin, her expression was still full of shock along with a trace of fear.

Lin Jian Xing got rid of the bindings and smiled, his aura rising slowly.

The Heavenly Court immortals turned pale when they sensed this aura.

Pseudo venerable!

“He concealed it really well.”

“He is actually a pseudo venerable!”

At this point, Lin Jian Xing finally showed his full strength.

Translucent milky white strings emerged around him.

The strings flew towards Heavenly Court immortals with an extremely fast speed.

Sword path killer move — Sword Qi Threads!

“It was this move!” Nine Spiritual Fairy reminded.

The other four Heavenly Court immortals were solemn, transformation path Nine Spiritual Fairy transformed into an immemorial desolate plant but was beaten miserably by this move, they naturally could not treat this lightly.

Red Heart Traveler activated all of his defensive methods as he took the lead in facing these threads.

The threads had extreme sharpness that could not be expressed in words. They directly cut straight through, Red Heart Traveler might have been cut into pieces by the threads if he had not reacted fast enough and pulled apart some distance immediately.

“This move cannot be blocked!” The other three Heavenly Court immortals also probed the power of this move and reached a consensus.

The threads’ sharpness was unimaginable, even the powerful Heavenly Court immortals could only flee and evade.

Lin Jian Xing did not move, he sent out more and more threads that gradually filled the whole battlefield.

The five Heavenly Court immortals made an awkward discovery, the battlefield they wanted to trap Lin Jian Xing in became an obstruction for their own dodging attempts.

They finally realized now that Lin Jian Xing changed the battlefield not to stall for time. The reason why he returned the Immortal Gu was because he believed he could fight all five of them alone, he fight the five Heavenly Court immortals head-on!

“Lin Jian Xing! You are really underestimating us!”

“Cancel rumor cage, let me activate my strongest method!”

“No, let me go first.”

Facing such a powerful Lin Jian Xing, the five Heavenly Court immortals decisively canceled rumor cage and used their strongest killer moves.

Lin Jian Xing’s smile did not go away as he activated another method.

In an instant, sword light flew everywhere.

Sword path killer move — Sword Light Disintegration!

Bam bam bam...

In this battle, Lin Jian Xing won against five opponents alone. He killed Wan Zi Hong, severely injured Zhou Xiong Xin, Prince Feng Xian, and Red Heart Traveler, while Nine Spiritual Fairy who shielded their retreat was captured.

After this battle, Lin Jian Xing’s name shook the five regions.

Chapter 2306: Yet Another Rank Nine Immortal Gu

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

Mini Eastern Sea.

Refinement Sea’s sea area.

Sea breeze blew and sound of the waves could be heard constantly.

An elderly rank five hairy man was lying on a dinghy in an unconscious state.

The dinghy moved along with the waves, if no changes occurred, this elderly hairy man was going to face death by drowning.

But a towered ship was moving past here, and the people on the ship started shouting when they noticed the dingy.

When the elderly hairy man woke up, he found he was already on the towered ship.

“Elder, are you also going to the refinement path sacred land to compete for the qualifications to enter Floating Refinement Hive?” A hairy man Gu Master on the ship asked.

The elder nodded: ”I live in Mini Northern Plains, I heard about Floating Refinement Hive and learned that it was forged by the orders of our Supreme Lord Great Love Immortal Venerable. This refinement path sacred land might be my final hope to make a breakthrough.”

The hairy man Gu Masters on the ship exclaimed in surprise: ”Senior, it is really not easy for you to make such a long trip from Mini Northern Plains to here, you have our respect!”

The elderly hairy man shook his head, smiling bitterly: ”At first, it was not just me, there were three others as well. But on the dangerous journey, two died in succession, while the remaining one did not dare to continue and returned. So, only I arrived here.”

Sovereign immortal aperture was not safe.

Especially when abnormal situations occurred frequently, the stable living habitats were the areas where clans or large groups settled; those areas were usually protected by immortal formations or Gu Immortals.

Even rank five Gu Masters would have to face huge risks if they were to make a long journey.

The elderly hairy man also asked about the origins of the hairy man Gu Masters on the ship.

Like what he had expected, these hairy man Gu Masters came from Mini Eastern Sea’s three hairy man continents.

Back then, Lang Ya blessed land’s Yellow Hair Continent, Black Hair Continent, and White Hair Continent were jointly called three hairy man continents.

These hairy man Gu Masters had different cultivation levels; rank four were the majority, there were few rank fives, and there were also rank threes but they were rare.

“I am really envious of you, you all live so close to the refinement path sacred land!” The elderly hairy man let out his inner sigh.

“What’s the point of being close? We are forbidden from entering during normal times.”

“How can we be allowed to enter the sacred land so casually?”

“From what I know, many Gu Immortals’ descendants can enter casually. Sigh, we can’t compare to them. They have Gu Immortal seniors, they enter or leave this area through flying boats which are extremely fast!”

“As long as this test is not difficult and I pass it, I will have the qualifications to enter and leave here freely.”

The hairy man Gu Masters discussed.

Several days later, the elderly hairy man and the hairy man Gu Masters arrived above a Floating Refinement Hive.

The Floating Refinement Hive was enormous and towering, making all the Gu Masters exclaim in shock.

A voice entered every person’s ears, instructing the correct path to enter the Floating Refinement Hive.

The Floating Refinement Hive’s structure was even more complex, there were countless rooms and corridors which made it easy to get lost.

With the guidance of that voice, the hairy man Gu Masters found their rooms one after the other.

There were all kinds of living amenities in the rooms but they were extremely simple, clearly showing the style of asceticism.

That night, the newly arrived hairy man Gu Masters slept well.

The second day began, Gu materials were sent to the separate Gu refinement chamber in the room.

The hairy man Gu Masters began their Gu refinement.

According to the explanation of that mysterious voice, this was the initial test; the Gu Masters were required to use their most proficient methods to process Gu materials or refine Gu worms.

This test lasted for three days in which time Gu Masters could display their attainment to their heart’s content.

After the test, Gu Masters would be shifted to different rooms; some moved to higher floors while some were dropped to lower floors.

Floating Refinement Hive did not restrict interaction between Gu Masters, all kinds of small-scale meetings were held during night frequently.

The rank five elderly hairy man Gu Master saw many excellent Gu Master. Among them, hairy men were the most numerous, but there were also humans, and even some other variant human Gu Masters.

He also heard many news. One day, according to everyone’s speculation, they concluded that the Gu Masters on higher floors had better results.

Because the higher the floor, the better the environment of the room, and the more exquisite the food served.

Gu Masters began to compete intensely based on this standard.

Floating Refinement Hive never lacked tasks to process Gu materials, refine Gu worms, or create new Gu.

If the Gu Masters passed with good results, they could request guidance from the mysterious voice, learning exquisite Gu refinement knowledge and techniques.

After living here for a couple of weeks, all the Gu Masters felt their strength rising rapidly.

Like this, fourteen days passed and the Gu Masters faced the mid-term test.

A top tier Gu material needed to be processed by many Gu Masters together.

The Gu Masters were distributed in their respective rooms, they watched the real-time video and processed the material together at separate locations. The video was lifelike and even had vivid temperature and smell like it truly existed. The real Gu materials were in a refinement path Gu formation in a secret area and were not placed before the Gu Masters.

Such a method was unimaginable, shocking and awing the Gu Masters.

The mid-term test soon ended. Ten or so days passed again before it was time for the final test.

This time, the test was to process immortal materials.

Naturally, the main lead were Gu Immortals, every Floating Refinement Hive had at least one refinement path Gu Immortal. The Gu Masters were in charge of doing some supplementary tasks like processing a part of the immortal material, and so on.

After passing the final test, the Gu Masters possessed the qualifications to enter and leave Refinement Sea freely.

But this qualification had a time limit of fifty years. Once this time limit was up, they had to retake the test.

Most of Fang Yuan’s Floating Refinement Hives were packed with Gu Masters.

The earlier stage did not have a high standard, most of the Gu Masters could pass and obtain this qualification.

But in the future, as the population increases explosively, there would be intense competition in every field. This was even more so for the qualification to enter Refinement Sea.

Every Floating Refinement Hive could borrow the help of Refinement Sea and greatly raise the success rate of Gu refinement. At the same time, the wasted Gu materials from refining in these refinement hives were melted by the Floating Refinement Hives and sent to Refinement Sea.

Both components complemented each other.

If there was no replenishment from the Floating Refinement Hives, the current Refinement Sea’s water level would have already fallen by a lot.

After all, Fang Yuan had been trying to advance an Immortal Gu for many days.

The central area of Refinement Sea was an absolute forbidden ground, only the Gu Immortals permitted by Fang Yuan could enter.

It was because Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool was there!

Suddenly, a rumbling sound spread from Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool, a light pillar suddenly took shape and soared towards the sky.

The light pillar slowly dissipated and a rank nine Immortal Gu revealed itself.

This heaven path Immortal Gu looked like a crystal spider, it was clear and transparent with no flaws on the body. The spider’s eight legs were slim and long, its body was also small and raised high by the eight legs.

It was heavenly web Gu.

And on the back of heavenly web Gu, there was a cobweb-like white insignia.

This was unique to rank nine heavenly web Gu, rank eight heavenly web Gu did not have it.

“Success, master gained yet another rank nine Immortal Gu!”

“Goodness, it is our utmost glory to be able to participate in this whole process.”

“As long as this continues, master will definitely trample on all the venerables one day!!”

There were other Gu Immortals who took part in the advance refinement process in Four Elements Square Regret Blood Refinement Pool, most of them were hairy men. They looked at the sky and sighed with emotions.

Under the control of Fang Yuan’s divine sense, rank nine heavenly web Gu disappeared shortly after.

“Rank nine heavenly web Gu is also refined.”

Fang Yuan’s mood was tranquil.

He had refined several rank nine Immortal Gu, he was becoming used to it and did not feel excitement.

Although the Gu refinement failed twice, there was no setbacks after that and it finished smoothly.

Fang Yuan had pondered over this before finally choosing to advance heavenly web Gu.

He needed an Immortal Gu that could help him in frontal offense and defense. And among the two main aspects of offense and defense, Fang Yuan unhesitatingly chose the latter.

Because of non-conflicting dao marks of sovereign immortal body, its defense was extremely weak and was Fang Yuan’s shortcoming.

If other venerables used this point, Fang Yuan would have almost no place in a frontal combat and the consequences would be extremely severe.

When heavenly web Gu was activated by itself, it could release a giant web to trap the target.

Strictly speaking, it was not a defensive Gu, it belonged to the offensive aspect.

But it was the core of a defensive killer move —Heavenly Web Protection Veil.

Heavenly web protection veil’s power increased massively and was even stronger than reverse flow protection seal now.

Moreover, heavenly web Gu could be used in obscured heavenly secret, increasing the power of this move as well.

Fang Yuan chose heaven path and gave up on refinement path because refinement path did not specialize in offense; moreover, it was too widely spread.

Heaven path had extremely wide future prospects, and when developed well, was far better than human path.

Even more amazing was that almost no one had the qualifications to cultivate heaven path.

So, it was extremely wise of Fang Yuan to choose heaven path as his specialty. Using heaven path for offensive methods was naturally the best choice.

Taking back the rank nine heavenly web Gu, Fang Yuan inspected his storage.

Because of two failures, a lot of heaven path immortal materials were expended. As for the secluded domain of heaven and earth, Refinement Sea, the sea level did fall but not to the point of exceeding the limit, it could self-recover even if it was not looked after.

Naturally, the constant resource deposit by Floating Refinement Hives accelerated the recovery of Refinement Sea.

Just as Fang Yuan was planning on which rank eight Immortal Gu to advance next, news arrived.

Five Heavenly Court immortals surrounded and attacked Lin clan’s first supreme elder Lin Jian Xing but were utterly defeated. Lin Jian Xing revealed pseudo venerable battle strength, he colluded with Fang clan and helped to hide them, sending them intel secretly. Moreover, he was an otherworldly demon himself!

There was much evidence pointing to the fact that Lin Jian Xing colluded with and protected Fang clan, it could be said to be ironclad. As an information path great expert, Zhou Xiong Xin not only had the ability to gather clues, he also had the ability to forge false evidence.

As for Lin Jian Xing’s otherworldly demon identity, it was deduced by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable personally.

The whole world was in an uproar, Western Desert was in even more chaos.

It was not easy for a pseudo venerable to emerge in this region, but before Western Desert’s righteous path could feel any pride about this, they were dumbfounded.

This pseudo venerable Lin Jian Xing was actually dabbling in the demonic path and his involvement was quite deep!

Chapter 2307: Star Constellation, I Will Need You To Die

If not for Heavenly Court revealing it, the world would still be unaware of Lin Jian Xing possessing pseudo venerable battle strength. He hid it so well that he definitely had other motives.

And looking at the reaction of most of the Lin clan Gu Immortals, they were also unaware of this.

Western Desert’s righteous path super forces were adopting a wait and see attitude.

Many of them anticipated Lin Jian Xing to give an explanation but Lin clan remained silent and gave no such thing.

There was no movement in Western Desert’s righteous path.

They did not want to create an anti-Lin alliance after the anti-Fang alliance.

The consequences of attacking Fang clan was already before them. If Lin clan were to imitate Fang clan as well, with a pseudo venerable bringing the whole clan to fight a guerrilla war, how Western Desert’s righteous path possibly survive?

“It is impossible for Fang clan to make a move. Seems like the previous series of Fang clan’s attacks was a deception created by Heavenly Court.” It was clear to Fang Yuan after he read through the whole information.

After Fang clan lost all their resource points, they had to rely on Fang Yuan even more. So, Fang Yuan had an even deeper control over them. If Fang clan were to attack at such a large scale, it was impossible for them to not notify him and ask for his instructions.

Fang Yuan found it somewhat funny.

Heavenly Court tried to put their hands in Western Desert, it would have been okay if they chose anyone else, but they just happened to choose the strongest target!

But shortly after, Fang Yuan fell into deep thought.

He thought of an issue: ”Why did Heavenly Court suddenly target Lin clan?”

Was it because they discovered Lin clan’s first supreme elder’s pseudo venerable strength and wanted to get rid of him in advance for their plan to conquest the five regions?

This possibility was too low.

Not to mention that the greatest obstacle to Heavenly Court ruling the five regions were the other venerables, pseudo venerables were inconsequential.

Also, even if Heavenly Court discovered that Lin clan’s first supreme elder had pseudo venerable battle strength, why would they only send five Heavenly Court Gu Immortals to kill him?

This was clearly not reasonable.

“What is Heavenly Court’s true motive? Why did they suddenly target Lin clan?”

Fang Yuan knew from Fang clan that Lin clan had never colluded with Fang clan.

This was just Heavenly Court framing them!

“Is it because Lin Jian Xing is an otherworldly demon?”

That was not right either.

Heavenly Court’s stance towards otherworldly demons was not radical extermination.

If they could be recruited, Heavenly Court would recruit them. They had tried to recruit Fang Yuan as well.

Heavenly Court’s recruitment standard was very clear—they just needed to be humans!

“So what was the reason? As the number one person in wisdom path, even if Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not make the plan, she must have agreed to attacking Lin clan. But she rarely miscalculates, so what was it that made her agree to attacking Lin clan?”

This question was crucial and was worth pondering over.

Even though wisdom Gu was only at rank eight, it was helpful to Fang Yuan.

After he used all kinds of wisdom path methods, Fang Yuan had some guesses but he was not certain.

After all, they were only deductions.

What was the truth?

Fang Yuan naturally had a way to verify his deductions.

He immediately sent an order to make a rank five Gu Master undergo immortal ascension.

Currently, there was no such rank five Gu Immortal seed in sovereign immortal aperture. Moreover, these Gu Immortal seeds did not have deep foundation or enough experience, the possibility of them succeeding in immortal ascension was very low. This was why Fang Yuan decided to stop them to let them continue to deepen their foundation.

But because this issue was very important, Fang Yuan felt it was worth expending a rank five Gu Master.

In the end, this rank five Gu Master failed and died from the imbalance of three qi.

But using the short period of time of merging the three qi, Fang Yuan used stealing heavenly secret to explore the truth.

Although Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was outside of Heavenly Court, being in Embroidered Tower, when she gave order to attack Lin clan, Bo Qing’s soul was taken out from Heavenly Court’s secret storage.

This was obvious evidence!

Adding on that Fairy Maiden Soul modified Bo Qing’s soul in Heavenly Court, Fang Yuan learned of many valuable information.

“Fairy Zi Wei and Ying Wu Xie are trapped in heaven path dream realms, so Star Constellation Immortal Venerable decided to cultivate Bo Qing even though this action carries risks.”

With these clues, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s goal was obvious, it was to use Bo Qing to scheme against Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

“Spectral Soul Demon Venerable...”

Fang Yuan’s eyes shone darkly as he mumbled.

He knew why Star Constellation Immortal Venerable wanted to deal with Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s actions already made him the main threat to Heavenly Court.

Naturally, this was Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s understanding under the condition of Fang Yuan hiding his situation.

Were the truth of Fang Yuan’s many rank nine Immortal Gu to be revealed, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable would be thrown aside, not only would Star Constellation Immortal Venerable find trouble with Fang Yuan, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable would also impatiently ally with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to attack Fang Yuan!

Splash splash splash.

At this time, Fang Yuan made deductions rapidly, thoughts gushed in his mind and formed into torrential waves.

He knew an opportunity was before him.

A huge opportunity!

If he missed this chance, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable might succeed in her plan.

Such opportunities seldom came twice.

So would he be able to grasp this opportunity?

If he could not, the outcome would be extremely bad to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan could not decide immediately.

Although he knew of heavenly court’s secret, he did not know how much progress Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had made over this period of time.

He was even more in the dark regarding Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Longevity Heaven.

Fang Yuan refined rank nine Immortal Gu, he had an advantage in this aspect. But the other venerables might be able to offset his refinement path advantage through other aspects.

Battle.

Fang Yuan did not like battles, but he did not hate or reject them.

As far as he was concerned, battles and killing were only a way to obtain benefits.

An outcome of inflicting a little more damage to enemy while suffering less damage was already a good result in a battle.

There were huge risks in battle.

It was not a wise decision to start a fight rashly.

Compared to fighting, Fang Yuan liked doing transactions — to plunder the economy.

But Fang Yuan was aware: There will be upcoming battles between the venerables and it will be frequent!

“Lets fight then.” After pondering and considering for several days, Fang Yuan finally made this decision.

And he immediately took action.

On one hand, he sent Gu Immortals to Western Desert to contact Lin Jian Xing and try to recruit him; on the other hand, he arranged a troop of capable experts.

After making proper arrangements, Fang Yuan flew to the sky and entered spectral heaven!

Great Love Immortal Venerable suddenly flew into spectral heaven—this significant information was quickly obtained by Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven, it was rapidly spread throughout the whole five regions’ Gu Immortal world.

Every action of a venerable captured the attention of all the Gu Immortals.

Let alone when Fang Yuan was making such a big movement!

“What is Heaven Refining Demon Venerable trying to do by entering spectral heaven? Fight with Spectral Soul Demon Venerable?” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was puzzled.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, however, felt her heart jump.

Not long ago, she had completed the transaction with Fang Yuan regarding the star array calculation formation. Her calculations went wrong because of Lin Jian Xing’s strength and she was just about to deal with this when Fang Yuan made such a strange movement.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not even make a deduction when a strong intuition hit her—this was going to be bad!

But as the exact situation and how this intuition was going to be realized, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not know. She needed to continue deducing or let the situation play out.

“Among the venerables, Fang Yuan is the person in the worst position. Why did he take the initiative to go to spectral heaven?” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was also puzzled.

Spectral heaven had already become Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s territory, he did not show any movements when other Gu Immortals entered or left spectral heaven.

But if a venerable like Fang Yuan entered?

This was like a tiger occupying a mountain, it would not move when some small animals stepped onto the mountain. But if another tiger entered the mountain, the tiger would become vigilant and even start a fight.

Would Spectral Soul Demon Venerable attack Fang Yuan?

The reply to this issue weighed on the two venerables’ minds.

They activated their investigative killer moves to pay close attention—Spectral Soul Demon Venerable did not show any movement!

Both venerables were shaken.

Both thought of a possibility at the same time: Did Fang Yuan have a method against Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, so he had the confidence to enter spectral heaven?

But why did he suddenly enter spectral heaven?

Similar question appeared before Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s first thought was: ”Has Fang Yuan already settled the issues inside sovereign immortal aperture and is trying to annex variant human grotto-heavens?”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s heart jolted as the bad feeling grew in her heart: ”Does Fang Yuan already know of the heaven path dream realms? In the battle in Crazed Demon Cave, he killed Paradise Earth and obtained a large piece of truthful floating ice left after Limitless Demon Venerable’s death....”

Fang Yuan did not conceal his movement and directly went towards the location of heaven path dream realms after he entered spectral heaven.

Soon, he was before the heaven path dream realms.

After sensing this, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was shaken: ”This is a dream realm? It is the dream realm closest to the depiction in <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>! So Fang Yuan’s target is them.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable frowned, Fang Yuan had heaven path cultivation and was also the number one person in the world regarding dream path, the heaven path dream realms were too useful to him.

“I can’t let Fang Yuan succeed!” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable thought of this and immediately contact Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable learned that these were heaven path dream realms.

He immediately agreed to ally with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to suppress Fang Yuan and stop him from obtaining heaven path dream realms. At the same time, he wondered to himself if this was real or not.

This was the first time Giant Sun Immortal Venerable knew of the heaven path dream realm’s existence.

“I already have a rank nine Gu, although it is light Gu, is damaged and can’t be used for the moment, this is already enough to make Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Heaven Refining Demon Venerable ally to deal with me. So, is this situation planned by them to plot against me?”

This was definitely a possibility.

Fang Yuan looked at the heaven path dream realm before him and sent dream butterfly Immortal Gu inside.

Dream butterfly Immortal Gu was an investigative Gu, Fang Yuan soon learned the details of the heaven path dream realm.

He became quite excited: ”The price to create these heaven path dream realms is huge, the Heavenly Dao definitely expended its true meaning. This means, if I obtain these dream realms and absorb the true meaning, the loss of the Heavenly Dao will become my gain. Through this, my attainment in some aspects of heaven path can become even higher than the Heavenly Dao!”

Naturally, this could not be considered as heaven path supreme grandmaster.

Because right now, there were too many things in heaven path that Fang Yuan still could not comprehend.

“Fang Yuan, have you been well?” Just as he was thinking, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable arrived.

“As expected, it is easy to do things secretly, but hard to do them openly. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable is probably arriving as well.” Fang Yuan thought of this and smiled at Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, ”Star Constellation, I must have these dream realms! If you don’t retreat, I will need you to die.”

Chapter 2308: Fang Yuan Versus Star Constellation

“You need me to die? Hehehe, it is rare to see you, Fang Yuan, act so enthusiastically.” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable smiled at Fang Yuan’s threat but was slightly shaken inwardly.

In her several fights with Fang Yuan, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable rarely saw Fang Yuan show such a firm attitude. It was clear that Fang Yuan was bent on gaining these heaven path dream realms!

Because of this, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable needed to stop Fang Yuan even more.

“We have not fought for many days, you’ve probably made a lot of progress.” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s long hair started fluttering without wind.

Her long dark hair was like the dark night, but countless starlight specks glittered in between the hair like a shrunken milky way, so dazzling that it could not be ignored.

Ding ding ding...

Innumerable starlight specks flowed out of her hair and gathered to form a powerful starlight torrent.

This torrent was made from countless star fragments that collided with each other, producing clear and crisp sounds.

Fang Yuan frowned, he had not seen this move before. He immediately pointed with his finger, using the killer move seven kills rainbow.

In an instant, metal path’s yellow light, wood path’s jade-green light, water path’s light blue hue, fire path’s red light, earth path’s brown light, wind path’s green radiance, and lightning path’s deep blue light merged together to form a huge drill that charged towards the star fragment current.

Rumble!

The collision produced a huge explosion first. Shortly after, metallic sounds of countless star fragments colliding with each other resounded in the battlefield.

Fang Yuan’s seven kills rainbow passed through star fragments and snaked its way towards Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable smiled as her body drifted back like there was a gust of wind.

Fang Yuan’s seven kills rainbow continued to lose strength as it passed through the star fragments. At first, it had an unstoppable penetrative force, but as star fragments continued to attach themselves onto it, its momentum reduced rapidly. In the end, the light pillar continued to thin out, and when it reached Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, it was just like a wisp of smoke.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable watched with a smile on her face as the seven kills rainbow dissipated before her.

Fang Yuan frowned slightly, his gaze fixed upon the star fragments that were scattered throughout the battlefield.

Every one of the star fragments was extremely small, they were not real star fragments but created from the killer move.

Originally, the star fragments flickered with blue light and gathered to form an azure torrent. But now, these star fragments were scattered, and as they absorbed the seven kills rainbow, their surface became tainted with colors like golden yellow, green, blue, red, brown, and so on. The sky above the battlefield was filled with all kinds of colors, forming a gorgeous scene.

Fang Yuan, however, sensed intense danger from this boundless beautiful scenery.

He continued to activate killer moves to probe, but each of them showed their might for a short period before their strength began to fall rapidly and were then absorbed by the star fragments.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable activated another method.

She occasionally flicked her fingers or waved them in the air. Following her movement, star path dao marks shone in the battlefield correspondingly.

These star path dao marks increased in numbers rapidly while connecting with each other; in just a dozen or so breaths of time, they had constructed the initial form of a battlefield killer move!

How could Fang Yuan let Star Constellation Immortal Venerable succeed so easily, once the battlefield killer move was activated, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would immediately have a huge territorial advantage.

Fang Yuan immediately acted to obstruct her but there was minimal effect.

The star fragments protected the dao marks, even if Fang Yuan destroyed the star path dao marks, these dao marks would break down into countless star fragments and fill the gaps.

“I need to thank you, Fang Yuan, if not for permanence Gu, there would not be these two moves.” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable said.

Fang Yuan had never heard of these two moves, they synchronized with each other and were indeed extraordinary.

Fang Yuan saw that he was unable to resolve this directly, he decisively stopped probing and used another killer move.

At the next moment, his body released the light qi of five colors; central restriction white-gold saint light qi, northern restriction jade licorice light qi, western restriction red raging flame light qi, and eastern restriction blue water light qi.

The light qi connected with each other but were distinct individually as well. They quickly spread throughout the battlefield, covering Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s incomplete battlefield killer move as well as the countless star fragments.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable nodded slightly, revealing her admiration.

Be it the previous seven kills rainbow or the current five restriction profound light qi, they were both modified by Fang Yuan.

If it were the original version, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would have immediately disrupted them, and Fang Yuan would have suffered backlash.

Seven kills rainbow’s modification was quite ordinary. In just this short while, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had already seen through it. As long as she was given some time, she could deduce a method to break it directly.

But this five restriction profound light qi killer move was modified properly, besides the increase in its power, its activation speed had also become very fast.

This modification level surpassed seven kills rainbow’s which showed that Fang Yuan had paid a lot attention to this.

“He must have invested a lot of time and energy.” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable thought.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable began to suffer backlash.

She did not have sovereign immortal body which had non-conflicting dao marks. In this five restriction profound light qi, the stronger the killer moves she used, the stronger the backlash she faced.

However, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was the number one person in wisdom path since ancient times. Five restriction profound light qi had been revealed before, so how could she not have a method to deal with it?

Over this period, she had thought of at least three ways to deal with every method of Fang Yuan’s.

Immediately, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable chose to use the simplest one.

She opened the door of her immortal aperture slightly, letting out countless star beasts.

These star beasts had varying sizes, they were as large as white whales or as small as mosquitoes. Some had huge heads and horns, some were soft and twisted, they were of all kinds and shapes.

But every one of these star beasts was at least an immemorial desolate beast. Among them, the leaders’ aura and status were clearly higher, their gazes even shone with shrewdness and spirituality.

The star beasts charged into five restriction profound light qi without any obstruction!

Five restriction profound light qi killer move originally came from Tao Zhu, he created it based upon the five regional walls. The five regional walls could obstruct the living beings of five regions but did not have much effect on the beings of the two heavens.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable deliberately raised these star path beasts which were all from the two heavens, so they were not suppressed by five restriction profound light qi.

The star beasts formed groups and charged forward aggressively.

Fang Yuan activated killer moves to clear out area after area, but Star Constellation Immortal Venerable kept on adding more beasts, the star beasts’ scale was still growing slowly. The star beast leaders even possessed their own immortal aperture and had Gu worms, their intelligence was not inferior to a human.

‘Star Constellation Immortal Venerable seems to be able to raise legendary immemorial beasts at a large scale?!’ Fang Yuan’s mind was shook.

But thinking about it, he understood why.

“Star Constellation Immortal Venerable is the number one person in wisdom path, enlightening the star beasts and giving them wisdom is her specialty domain.”

Actually, it was not just Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, the countless mutant Gu Immortals in Crazed Demon Cave originated from mountains, rocks, wind, fire, and so on, they were all evolved into Gu Immortals by Limitless Demon Venerable.

From a certain angle, in this aspect of enlightening legendary immemorial desolate beasts, Limitless Demon Venerable’s accomplishments were much more shocking than Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s.

“Star Constellation Immortal Venerable must have spent countless star path resources to nurture so many star beasts! The merging of the two heavens gave me countless heaven path immortal materials, it also gave her endless star path resources. It allowed her to construct the star array calculation formation and even raise so many star beasts.” Fang Yuan made a guess Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s wealth.

The truth was, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had spent a very large amount to raise so many star beasts. Not only did she use her gains from the merging of two heavens, she also used star path resources from Heavenly Court’s storage.

Looking at the approaching star beasts, Fang Yuan activated sword tongue dragon soul killer move while maintaining five restriction profound light qi.

Countless dragon souls flew and sword qi pervaded the air, but they still could not match the endless star beasts, at most they delayed the offense of some star beast groups.

After these star beasts were injured, the surrounding star fragments mended their injuries and healed them rapidly.

If they were severely injured, they would die and break down into star fragments.

Once the star fragments reached a certain level in an area, they easily formed star path dao marks.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s three moves were connected to each other. If one was weakened, the other would benefit, they were mutually linked and made Fang Yuan’s situation increasingly tough.

“Looks like this is another one of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s combat systems...” Fang Yuan noticed something.

His thoughts moved like lightning.

This fight with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was different from the battle in Crazed Demon Cave or the contest over rank nine light Gu.

The battle in Crazed Demon Cave was to seize Primordial Domain and the Crazed Demon formation. It prioritized on strategies and making use of the situation, it focused on the competition of information, people’s support, and their respective forces.

The contest over rank nine light Gu was a pursuit battle, it focused on speed, initiative, offense and defense.

This time, Fang Yuan wanted to seize heaven path dream realms, the prerequisite to this was to take control of this battlefield and gain territorial advantage!

Great minds thought alike, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had the same view.

Be it Fang Yuan’s five restriction profound light qi or Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s mysterious battlefield, they were both meant for this purpose.

From the start of the battle, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable directly used her new combat system, lowering the effectiveness of Fang Yuan’s five restriction profound light qi and other methods.

On the other hand, Fang Yuan was decisive, he saw the situation getting worse and immediately stopped all offensive methods, only defending himself.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable saw this and waved her sleeves, making all the star beasts press forward.

Fang Yuan could only dodge while preparing his killer move.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s eyes shone with starlight as she suddenly took out the lantern-like secluded domain of heaven and earth.

Mental Domain.

She lightly swung Mental Domain towards Fang Yuan’s direction.

Instantly, countless emotions attacked Fang Yuan’s mind and body.

But Fang Yuan was already prepared, he activated several defensive killer moves, among which was the killer move, calm and steady.

This move was already used in Crazed Demon Cave, it was also modified now. It suppressed and eliminated Fang Yuan’s emotions quickly.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not succeed in disturbing him, while Fang Yuan stabilized his footing as his preparation succeeded. He opened his mouth slightly, light smoke gushed out of his mouth and ears.

The pink smoke gathered above Fang Yuan’s head and turned into a mini image of Dang Hun Mountain.

At the next moment, the killer move activated as the mini Dang Hun Mountain shook intensely.

Ding——！

Ding——！

Ding——！

Sounds of crystals colliding resounded in the battlefield, and soon, the sound became ear-piercing.

The pink sound waves were visible to the naked eyes, wherever they went, star beasts cried in pain, freezing on the spot before crumbling apart.

The battlefield that was filled with star beasts became empty instantly.

Even the stronger star beast leaders were unable to resist as they collapsed amidst the pink sound waves.

Not only this, even the endless star fragments also disintegrated and disappeared. The surrounding star path dao marks were broken in succession and drowned in the pink sound waves.

Immortal killer move — Shocking Departure of Year Dream Wave and Dang Hun Sound!

One move swept the whole battlefield and changed the situation easily, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was aghast, her expression changed.

Chapter 2309: The Power of Heavenly Web!

Shocking Departure of Year Dream Wave and Dang Hun Sound was a compound killer move.

It used rank eight rule path departure Gu, rank eight wisdom path great shock Gu, rank eight time path year Gu, rank seven dream armor Gu, rank eight water path huge wave Gu, rank eight sound path ringing sound Gu, and its core was the secluded domain of heaven and earth, Dang Hun Mountain!

It was because the core was Dang Hun Mountain, a secluded domain of heaven and earth, that this move could be comparable to a rank nine killer move. Under the dao mark amplification of Fang Yuan’s various paths, its might was astonishing.

With just this move, Fang Yuan immediately broke Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s three continuous moves and alleviated his worsening situation, regaining his footing.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s expression changed as thoughts surged and moved in her mind, trying to analyze this move with all her strength.

“This move seems like Fang Yuan’s trump card, it is the source of his confidence to fight me.”

“Roughly analyzing it, this move contains rule path, wisdom path, time path, dream path, water path, soul path, and sound path. It really is difficult to block it completely.”

Wisdom path was fine, but dream path was troublesome. Despite the dream path Immortal Gu Dream Armor being only rank seven, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not have an effective way to block it.

Fang Yuan had the advantage in dream path, he was the number one in the current world!

“The greatest source of this move’s strength is Dang Hun Mountain. How much time and energy did Fang Yuan spend to deduce this move?”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable calculated inwardly while feeling somewhat helpless.

Her painstakingly created new combat system was broken by one move from Fang Yuan.

No matter how ingenious the three connected moves was, Fang Yuan’s Shocking Departure of Year Dream Wave and Dang Hun Sound was extremely domineering, directly clearing the battlefield.

The thing that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was concerned about: the time and energy she spent on these three moves compared to Fang Yuan’s expenditure in deducing Shocking Departure of Year Dream Wave and Dang Hun Sound.

It was fine if her time and energy spent was less.

If it was more, her losses would be more than gains.

The result of a confrontation between venerables also signified the difference in venerables’ cultivation and management methods.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable calculated inwardly and felt the possibility of Fang Yuan expending lesser than her was rather low.

But the truth was not so.

The main source of this killer move, Shocking Departure of Year Dream Wave and Dang Hun Sound, came from the nature of heaven and earth.

In the Remote Antiquity Era, there was a kind of immemorial desolate beast called shocking year beast, wherever it went, shocked year Gu would fly out. It was already extinct now.

Dream wave was a phenomenon, in Fang Yuan’s five hundred years of his previous life, dream wave was formed when dream realms appeared at a large scale.

There was no need to say much about Dang Hun Mountain.

Soul sound withered tree was an already extinct, rare immemorial desolate plant. It used wood path resources as nutrients and emitted soul sound that influence the souls of the surrounding living beings.

These phenomena and natural abilities existed throughout heaven and earth naturally.

After Fang Yuan gained the information through stealing heavenly secret, they became an important foundational reference material.

The creation of compound killer moves was actually easier than an individual path’s killer moves. Especially when Fang Yuan had rank eight wisdom Gu, it gave him accurate inspirations, so he did not have to waste time on dead ends.

This Shocking Departure of Year Dream Wave and Dang Hun Sound was essentially only a quasi-rank nine killer move because it did not contain a rank nine Immortal Gu.

Thus, rank eight wisdom Gu was helpful in deducing this move.

“Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, can you deal with this move?” Fang Yuan smiled as he calmly approached Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could only retreat constantly, maintaining distance from Fang Yuan.

It was difficult to construct a combat system.

The three connected moves that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable painstakingly created were exquisite and already formed an initial incomplete combat system.

But after Fang Yuan’s move unreasonably broke it, the three connected moves became a joke.

Naturally, this did not mean that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s effort ended up in vain.

Maybe in the future, when she obtains a rank nine star path Immortal Gu, this combat system’s power would rise explosively and be able to withstand Fang Yuan’s compound killer move.

The foundation of a combat system were still the Immortal Gu that formed it.

In a contest of venerables, they first competed with rank nine Immortal Gu. If there was no rank nine Immortal Gu, then they would contest with secluded domains of heaven and earth!

In this aspect, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable possessed the incomplete Blood Sea; Star Constellation Immortal Venerable possessed Book Mountain, Mental Domain, and the Door of Life and Death; Fang Yuan possessed Dang Hun Mountain, Luo Po Valley, City Well, Reverse Flow River, Hu Land, Refinement Sea, Human Sea, and the incomplete Qian Kun Crystal Wall.

When the foundation was solid and it was hard to determine a winner through fighting, the combat system became the biggest factor to decide victory or defeat.

“Fang Yuan really has extraordinary aptitude and shocking talent. This move is so powerful and mysterious, it is really hard to block. But I also have a move, please appraise it.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable shook the Mental Domain in her hand.

Fang Yuan immediately looked vigilant and activated reverse flow protection seal.

Reverse Flow River was already restored, reverse flow protection seal had even been modified.

Originally, after the killer move was activated, a large white robe was formed with ripples moved along the surface, this was the image of Reverse Flow River flowing slowly. The surface of the white robe had faint mist surrounding it. There was also a strip of light that was deep azure, it was curvy and wavy, resembling a long sash, it coiled around Fang Yuan’s arms, the back of his neck, and around his waist again.

Now, besides these, Fang Yuan’s peerlessly beautiful face was partly veiled by a translucent gauze, highlighting the matchless charm in the depths of his unconcealed eyes.

The lantern-like Mental Domain shook slightly; in an instant, the surrounding battlefield dimmed.

Mental Domain was like the only source of light, but it was letting out a mysterious suction force.

This move’s range was extremely large, Fang Yuan was directly struck by it. His accumulated emotions were extracted and absorbed by Mental Domain.

Fang Yuan immediately used calm and steady killer move, but could not block this process.

He used other methods as well, but as they showed no effects, his expression started to change.

Because at first, only emotions were extracted, but gradually, Fang Yuan’s wisdom path dao marks were also being extracted.

Wisdom path cultivation focused on three elements: thoughts, wills, and emotions. Furthermore, emotions were related to wisdom path dao marks. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s move was extremely powerful, besides extracting emotions, it could even extract wisdom path dao marks, permanently reducing the target’s wisdom path foundation!

“Once my emotions are all extracted, my heart will be empty. It will be extremely easy for Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to add in emotions then.” Fang Yuan felt that the situation was going south.

During the whole process, his reverse flow protection seal had no reaction.

Clearly, this extraction was extremely subtle and was not considered an attack, so it did not trigger reverse flow protection seal’s counterattack.

In fact, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable probably created this move to target reverse flow protection seal.

She succeeded.

Fang Yuan’s effort in modifying reverse flow protection seal was made pointless.

In just a few breaths of time, Fang Yuan already lost one hundred wisdom path dao marks.

He activated defensive methods crazily, but even dream armor Gu showed no effect.

The core of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s move was Mental Domain, it could be considered a quasi-rank nine killer move. Adding on the amplification from her wisdom path dao marks, it had overwhelming might.

Methods like that of dream armor Gu were at a lower level and did not have enough strength to block this.

Reverse flow protection seal was of a high level and had enough strength, but it could not be triggered.

Fang Yuan had another option, which was to continue activating Shocking Departure of Year Dream Wave and Dang Hun Sound, using offense against offense!

But he was in a dilemma.

It was not his intention to fight such an intense attrition battle with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. Both sides would suffer losses, giving Giant Sun Immortal Venerable the most gains.

Moreover, Fang Yuan did not want to fight Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, his first priority were the heaven path dream realms.

Thoughts collided in Fang Yuan’s mind, and after a few sparks between the thoughts, he made a decision. He secretly used a heaven path killer move — Heavenly Web Protection Veil.

This move originally formed a giant milky white web outside of the Gu Immortal to block attacks. But now, it quietly turned into a milky white light stream that entered the thin fishing net formed from obscured heavenly secret killer move.

Like this, the thin and tightly connected fishing net possessed the power of two killer moves, heavenly web protection veil and obscured heavenly secret!

Heavenly web Gu was a rank nine Immortal Gu.

Heavenly web protection veil’s defensive power was higher than the strength of Mental Domain’s killer move.

Heavenly web protection veil had gaps but nothing was allowed to pass through. or

As the saying went, the net of heaven has large meshes but it lets nothing through[1. A Chinese saying similar to ’The mills of God grind slowly but surely’.].

In an instant, it stopped Fang Yuan’s emotions from being extracted, causing Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to exclaim in surprise.

The even more amazing thing was that the rank nine Immortal Gu aura was not exposed. Because the two moves were interconnected, the aura was concealed by obscured heavenly secret killer move.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was truly Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, after just a few exchanges, she forced Fang Yuan to use his rank nine heavenly web Gu.

Like this, obscured heavenly secret killer move faced a huge burden!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s mood was even heavier.

She could not block Fang Yuan’s Shocking Departure of Year Dream Wave and Dang Hun Sound, but Fang Yuan could resist her Mental Domain’s killer move.

That meant she could not even keep up the attrition battle by using offense against offense.

“Does Fang Yuan have a method that is not weaker than mine in terms of wisdom path deduction?” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could not help but feel doubtful.

Fang Yuan thus gained the upper hand and finally had the leisure time to deal with the heaven path dream realms.

He did not attack Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and only defended against her while targeting those heaven path dream realms from afar.

His first method was naturally pure dream reality seeker transformation!

Ordinary dream realms would be transformed into Pure Dream Reality Seeker bodies by this move. But it had no effect on the heaven path dream realms, not only this, the heaven path dream realms were instead angered and formed a tidal wave that rushed towards Fang Yuan.

“These heaven path dream realms are filled with heaven’s will, while pure dream reality seeker transformation condenses a dream realm into a human body with human will as the core. This means I need to get rid of all the heaven’s will in the dream realms first.”

After learning of this, Fang Yuan activated heaven’s will dissipation killer move.

He had used this move many times before to deal with dream realms and its effect was extraordinary.

But this time, although it was still effective, its side effect was much larger. Fang Yuan felt some heartache as he watched the targeted heaven path dream realm shrinking rapidly.

“Seems like heaven’s will dissipation is usable against ordinary dream realms, but is an extremely crude measure against heaven path dream realms. It not only removes heaven’s will, it even eradicates the true meaning contained in the dream realm.”

Fang Yuan was not without gains, he realized that heaven’s will and heaven path true meaning were entangled in the heaven path dream realms, so they were hard to separate.

His wisdom path methods were rough, it was difficult for him to precisely separate the two and target just heaven’s will.

But Fang Yuan still had a way to deal with this.

At the next moment, he brought out his dream path clone Meng Qiu Zhen, letting him be devoured by a heaven path dream realm.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable sighed, feeling somewhat anxious.

Fang Yuan’s strength was exposed which made her quite surprised, he was actually starting to take these heaven path dream realms right under her eyes.

“Giant Sun, are you going to watch as Heaven Refining Demon Venerable takes these heaven path dream realms and increases his strength?” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable contacted Giant Sun.

“Of course not!”

At the next moment, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable showed himself.

Chapter 2310: Two Venerables Fight Against Fang Yuan

Ever since Fang Yuan suddenly flew into spectral heaven, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had been paying close attention to this place.

When Fang Yuan and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable fought, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was happy at first. After all, the two venerables expending each other’s resources was most beneficial to him.

But shortly after, he was faintly worried about Fang Yuan not being able to withstand Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s attacks and getting defeated too early.

“If Fang Yuan can’t continue, I will help him a bit.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had been secretly preparing to help Fang Yuan.

He naturally did not have good intentions.

First, Fang Yuan being in a weaker position was not beneficial to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. As far as he was concerned, Heavenly Court was still the biggest enemy.

Second, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable still wanted Fang Yuan and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to continue wearing each other down, so he needed to help Fang Yuan to maintain the battle of attrition between the two venerables to gain the most benefits.

“I have Unified Essence Yi Qi Zi after all, my immortal essence can be replenished greatly. Consuming some immortal essence in battle is more detrimental for them!”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had this thought back then.

He was not wrong.

It was also very reasonable.

It was just that he did not know the truth.

He only possessed the information that he could obtain.

But soon, he was shocked to see that in the battle between Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Fang Yuan, it was Fang Yuan who had the upper hand!

He had not expected this.

After all, in his impression, Fang Yuan was behind on refining dao marks, although he had potential, his immortal essence reserve was the worst.

How could he gain the upper hand?

He even made Star Constellation Immortal Venerable take the initiative to ask for help from Giant Sun Immortal Venerable!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had witnessed the whole fight, after the surprise, he felt that it made sense.

Shocking Departure of Year Dream Wave and Dang Hun Sound left an extremely deep impression on him.

Fang Yuan used Dang Hun Mountain as the core to create such a powerful killer move that destroyed Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s incomplete combat system.

It made sense for Fang Yuan to be victorious.

When Shocking Departure of Year Dream Wave and Dang Hun Sound showed its might, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was actually not too anxious, instead, he became a little relieved and no longer felt such an urge to probe Fang Yuan’s foundation.

The reason?

Fang Yuan lacked immortal essence and was the slowest one at refining natural dao marks, what did he spend the rest of his time on?

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable understood now.

“So he used his time to deduce killer moves.”

This was a rather correct choice in Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s opinion.

He was even more at ease because the killer move used a secluded domain of heaven and earth as the core.

“Looks like Fang Yuan does not have a rank nine Immortal Gu, so he used a secluded domain of heaven and earth to create a quasi-rank nine killer move.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could not help feeling envious.

Fang Yuan had the most number of secluded domains of heaven and earth, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable also had several, but he, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, only had one and it was incomplete.

He really wanted to have a complete secluded domain of heaven and earth!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was observing the battle quietly, when he saw Fang Yuan gaining the upper hand with Shocking Departure of Year Dream Wave and Dang Hun Sound killer move, his mind turned calm. However, when he saw Fang Yuan withstanding Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s Mental Domain’s killer move, he could no longer sit still.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable already expected Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to use a wisdom path killer move with Mental Domain as the core.

But he never expected Fang Yuan to have a defensive method that could block this Mental Domain’s killer move!

Fang Yuan’s reverse flow protection seal already made Giant Sun Immortal Venerable feel a headache, he had racked his brains to secretly deduce a luck path method to counter it. But he did not think Fang Yuan was still hiding another defensive method that was even stronger than reverse flow protection seal.

Fang Yuan’s performance went beyond Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s expectations.

Now, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was wary.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could not break Fang Yuan’s defensive method, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was the same!

“I did not think that you, Fang Yuan, has such deep attainment in wisdom path as well. In just a short period of time, you actually created, deduced, and modified so many killer moves.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable entered the battlefield and praised Fang Yuan sincerely.

This was actually nothing.

Fang Yuan possessed stealing heavenly secret and wisdom Gu, and with sovereign immortal body’s advantage, it was easy to create compound killer moves. Just one of these advantages alone could make the other venerables envious. Now that these advantages were stacked together, even Fang Yuan felt it was terrifying!

Shocking Departure of Year Dream Wave and Dang Hun Sound and heavenly web protection veil were only a part of Fang Yuan’s recent gains.

He chose to use them because he felt they suited the situation.

Fang Yuan had at least ten killer moves of similar level.

The power of stealing heavenly secret could be seen from this; of course, rank eight wisdom Gu also provided a lot of help.

It was because of these two that Fang Yuan caught up from behind in terms of killer moves. He even had a wide range of options to choose from.

Naturally, nothing could be perceived from Fang Yuan’s expression.

Facing Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, he frowned and snorted coldly: ”I must obtain these heaven path dream realms, Giant Sun, you also want to block me? Are you still not clear of who is stronger between Heavenly Court and me?”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s looked at Fang Yuan’s incisive gaze, his expression eased and turned somewhat complex.

In his view, compared to Heavenly Court and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, Fang Yuan was still weaker.

The reason?

Fang Yuan did not have enough immortal essence!

He had been venerable for the shortest time and did not even have his own base. How many natural refinement path dao marks did he refine in this period of time?

It was very obvious.

Fang Yuan looked powerful, even suppressing Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. But in fact, he was relying on the novelty of new killer moves and their powerful strength.

How much immortal essence could he have?

How could he fight a battle of attrition?

From what Giant Sun Immortal Venerable thought, Fang Yuan’s situation did not look good.

But even though Fang Yuan was weaker, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable still needed to stop Fang Yuan and stand with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable for the time being.

The reason?

Because Fang Yuan wanted heaven path dream realms.

This could not be allowed!

If Fang Yuan absorbed all these heaven path dream realms, he would definitely rise in power and change the power structure of the venerables.

This was something that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not want to see.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable felt Heavenly Court and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable were his greatest threats, but he also wanted to suppress the rise of Fang Yuan who was the weakest venerable but had the most potential.

Thus, he took part in the battle. On the surface, he was helping Star Constellation Immortal Venerable; but secretly, he was striving for Star Constellation and Fang Yuan to expend their immortal essence, so that he could maintain and enlarge his advantage!

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s choice was no doubt extremely sensible from his point of view.

With his help, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable immediately changed the battle situation and began to suppress Fang Yuan.

The environment in spectral heaven was not helpful to the three venerables, they relied on their own foundation and strength. Under this situation, Fang Yuan’s worsening situation was immediately clear.

After all, he was fighting two opponents on his own.

Naturally, this was under the condition where Fang Yuan preserved most of his methods and did not use his full battle strength.

The fight of the three venerables shook heaven and earth.

Every Gu Immortal in five regions raised their heads and watched the battle nervously.

“Oh no, Lord Alliance Leader’s situation is not good.”

“Good, good, good, this demon Fang Yuan will finally face retribution!”

“I did not expect my Ancestor Giant Sun to join hands with Heavenly Court.”

“Heavenly Court is quite sensible to not look for trouble with my Ancestor Giant Sun.”

“Being able to make Giant Sun Immortal Venerable help her so easily proves Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable is indeed the number one person in wisdom path.”

Rank eight Gu Immortals understood the situation more clearly, they saw Fang Yuan being suppressed and his situation getting worse. The Eastern Sea immortals looked extremely solemn while Central Continent and Northern Plains’ Gu Immortals were rejoicing with raised morale.

Thunder rumbled and countless rays of light exploded from the collision of killer moves.

Fang Yuan’s situation did not look good but he was calm inwardly.

Although the two venerables allied, due to their conflicting paths, they could only attack Fang Yuan in turns.

Moreover, the two venerables were wary of each other, one would not allow the other to set a battlefield.

Without the threat of a battlefield killer move, Fang Yuan still had a grasp over the choice of fighting or retreating.

More importantly, Meng Qiu Zhen was already in a heaven path dream realm and was making good progress.

Because of the sharing of the clones’ and main body’s attainment levels, Fang Yuan could clearly feel his heaven path attainment level rising slowly!

Fang Yuan just needed to maintain this situation and it would do.

What was the use of superficial victory or defeat?

Man strives for recognition while Buddha requires incense; this was a reasonable proverb. But Fang Yuan was far beyond the age of fighting for recognition and he was more willing to strive for benefits.

If the choice of honor and benefit went against each other, Fang Yuan would unhesitatingly choose the latter.

It was this situation right now.

He could be forceful and suppress the two venerables. But what was the use when he would not be able to kill them?

Instead, it would make the two venerables wary and deepen their alliance. Was this not asking for trouble?

As for the support and morale of the five regions’ Gu Immortals, Fang Yuan did not care.

What was the use of that?

Even if Fang Yuan was defeated miserably today, the five regions’ Gu Immortals still could not defeat him. They still had to fear and revere Fang Yuan.

As long as Fang Yuan was not dead, could Fang clan, the two heavens’ grotto-heavens’ variant humans, or even the Eastern Sea super forces side with someone else?

They still had to follow Fang Yuan!

It was just that they would be more worried about their future.

But what did the worries of these minor characters have to do with Fang Yuan?

Fang Yuan did not need to bother with such things.

There were no two ways about it, these minor characters were only resources and tools in Fang Yuan’s eyes. The Gu cultivation world was ruled by the strong, the actual trend of the world still depended on the fight between venerables.

Even if Fang Yuan was defeated, as long as Meng Qiu Zhen made huge gains, he would be the biggest winner. The loss could be considered a victory.

Even if Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable beat Fang Yuan badly, as long as Fang Yuan lived and absorbed all the heaven path dream realms, their victory would be the same as defeat.

Fang Yuan knew this, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was aware of it as well.

The alliance of the two venerables could not make Fang Yuan retreat, he was still absorbing the true meaning in the heaven path dream realms.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was truly anxious.

She transmitted her voice to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable: ”Giant Sun, if this continues, Heaven Refining Demon Venerable will succeed. What are you still holding back for?”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable snorted coldly: ”Star Constellation, are you telling me that you are not holding back?”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had a solemn expression: ”I am going to prepare a killer move to search for Fang Yuan’s dream path clone and try to eradicate it!”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable took a deep look at her before nodding: ”Then I will target Fang Yuan’s reverse flow protection seal and pressure him in order to create a chance for you.”

Chapter 2311: Meng Qiu Zhen’s Crisis

Although Giant Sun Immortal Venerable participated in the battle, he had been preserving his strength.

He wanted to save his immortal essence and continue to hide his trump cards while making Star Constellation and Fang Yuan expend each other’s immortal essence.

Although Fang Yuan’s situation was bad and was in a disadvantage, he was actually making gains constantly. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could not take it anymore.

Giant Sun was an Immortal Venerable, he would not be easily deceived by the advantage they had right now.

“Fang Yuan, take this move!” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable shouted as he used two killer moves, lingering scrap luck and accumulated return, in succession.

Lingering scrap luck’s activation was extremely fast, Fang Yuan could not dodge it.

It was because Giant Sun Immortal Venerable used this move towards himself and not on Fang Yuan.

Faint golden fog curled up around Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

But the next moment, this golden fog appeared indescribably on Fang Yuan’s body!

Fang Yuan was startled for a moment before understand the profundity in this move.

When Giant Sun Immortal Venerable fought with Fang Yuan, their luck continued to entangle and form a close connection like a bridge. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable acted based on this and easily sent lingering scrap luck to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan also had high luck path attainment and immediately saw through this.

But his luck path attainment was far inferior to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s, even if he saw through this profundity, it was hard for him to stop it.

Lingering scrap luck killer move coiled around Fang Yuan’s body, constantly scrapping his luck.

Reverse flow protection seal was triggered at this moment and reflected lingering scrap luck killer move.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was happy to see this, he coordinated with reverse flow protection seal and let this backlash reach him by following their connected luck.

Accumulated return killer move showed its effect, increasingly the density of his surrounding golden fog.

The slightly denser golden fog followed the connection of the luck and returned to Fang Yuan’s body.

Lingering scrap luck killer move was reflected once again by reverse flow protection seal, and was again strengthened by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s accumulated return before it returned to Fang Yuan’s body again.

As this back and forth action continued, lingering scrap luck’s power continued to grow.

Fang Yuan had a solemn expression, venerables could not be underestimated. It was not only Star Constellation Immortal Venerable who thought of a counter to reverse flow protection seal, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable also did the same.

Comparatively, as a wisdom path Gu Immortal, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s method was even more thorough as it directly bypassed reverse flow protection seal.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s method was not thorough, he chose a different approach which was to imitate reverse flow protection seal. Reverse flow protection seal could reflect attacks, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable also reflected them back.

With the two linked moves, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable gained an advantage.

Simply because lingering scrap luck killer move was becoming increasingly strong, even if reverse flow protection seal could reflect it, Reverse Flow River had a fixed amount of water.

While both sides had not reached the limit, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable achieved his goal of using his immortal essence to expend Reverse Flow River.

Reverse flow protection seal was very hard to deal with indeed. In the past fights with Fang Yuan, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had used all kinds of attacks to trigger reverse flow protection seal and expend Reverse Flow River.

Now, he was using lingering scrap luck and accumulated return together, it was much more efficient than directly attacking.

Using immortal essence to expend a secluded domain of heaven and earth was also a huge gain.

After all, it was much easier to accumulate immortal essence than to restore Reverse Flow River.

Fang Yuan was shocked and furious: ”Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, I will definitely pay you back for this.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable looked at Fang Yuan and sighed inwardly. He felt that it was unwise of Fang Yuan to fight for the heaven path dream realms!

However, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable thought about it and understood the reason behind his decision.

‘After all, heaven path dream realms are resources that can overturn the contest of the venerables!’

‘If these heaven path dream realms are changed to a rank nine blood path Immortal Gu, blood path or even luck path secluded domain of heaven and earth, I will be blinded by greed too.’

‘Looks like Fang Yuan plans to develop heaven path.’

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable used his hidden methods to further suppress Fang Yuan.

On the other side, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable finished preparing her killer move. Boundless azure radiance spread as she activated the move.

The radiance shone on the dream realms, the heaven path dream realms went berserk; their shape distorted constantly like a spasm, turning into dough that was kneaded constantly.

‘Oh no! Star Constellation Immortal Venerable actually has a method to target the dream realms.’ A sharp light flashed across Fang Yuan’s eyes.

He immediately canceled reverse flow protection seal, only using obscured heavenly secret and heavenly web protection veil to forcibly endure Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s attack while rushing towards Star Constellation Immortal Venerable!

......

After Fang Yuan’s clone, Meng Qiu Zhen, entered the heaven path dream realm, his vision changed.

Shortly after, he found that he had turned into a land spirit in the shape of a pink cloth doll.

Meng Qiu Zhen was not surprised.

He snickered and began to use his power to change and manage this blessed land in the dream.

Different from Fairy Zi Wei and Ying Wu Xie, Meng Qiu Zhen came fully prepared.

Since Fang Yuan took the initiative to make a move, he naturally made sufficient preparation. Although he could not fully understand the complexities of the heaven path dream realms with stealing heavenly secret, he had a clear idea of the general rules in the dream realms.

Meng Qiu Zhen tested for a while and learned the limit of his capabilities.

Immortal killer move — Butterfly Explores Heavenly Secret!

This move used dream path investigative Immortal Gu Dream Butterfly as the core, it was based on exposing heavenly secret killer move, and was specifically made to be used in heaven path dream realms. It could obtain the details of the calamities and tribulations in heaven path dream realms in advance.

This move was one of the preparations Fang Yuan made.

After Meng Qiu Zhen used this move, he knew the details of the first earthly calamity. But he was not satisfied as he used the move another two times, expending a lot of immortal essence to probe the types and scale of the next two earthly calamities.

This was different from exposing heavenly secret.

Exposing heavenly secret could only explore the details of the next calamity and tribulation; moreover, the Gu cultivator could not be too far away from the next tribulation.

But butterfly explores heavenly secret could probe the details of the next three calamities. Naturally, this number was related to the power of the killer move as well as the size of the heaven path dream realm.

After finishing all this, Meng Qiu Zhen began to manage the blessed land.

There was only a rock field before him, flat and lifeless.

He assembled wind and cloud to accumulate lightning and bombarded the rock field.

Thirty percent of the rock field was blasted away, the remaining portion was filled with cracks and ravines.

Meng Qiu Zhen stopped the lightning and began to control the strength of the land.

The rock field that had lost thirty percent of its area was no longer as compact as before, after resisting for a while, it finally began to tremor slightly.

The tremors continued to grow bigger until deep trenches formed.

After the earth trenches formed, Meng Qiu Zhen moved wind and clouds again, accumulating heavy clouds. But this time, he did not create lightning but heavy rain.

There were very few water path dao marks in this heaven path dream realm’s blessed land which was not favorable to Meng Qiu Zhen’s plan.

But under Meng Qiu Zhen’s continuous effort, rainwater accumulated, finally overflowing out of the earth trenches and covering the rock field.

After finishing all these, Meng Qiu Zhen calculated the time and noticed that he had already spent a lot of time, it was nearing the first earthly calamity.

He activated create dream killer move to create countless firm rock spikes out of nothing.

When he almost changed the whole rock field into a land of spikes, the first earthly calamity arrived.

It was a desolate beast calamity.

A ferocious four-armed ape intruded the blessed land.

It roared as it fixed its gaze at Meng Qiu Zhen and ran towards him.

Meng Qiu Zhen was a land spirit but had no ability to teleport, so he was chased by the four-armed ape everywhere.

Looking at the four-armed ape not giving up on him and destroying countless earth spikes wherever it passed by, Meng Qiu Zhen did not panic, instead, he smiled slightly.

Everything was within his plan.

The four-armed ape rampaged for a while before its whole body became covered in injuries and blood.

This stimulated its bestial nature, it became increasingly berserk and its speed finally surpassed Meng Qiu Zhen’s.

Meng Qiu Zhen was already prepared, he stopped running on the ground and drilled into the earth trenches.

His size was small, and although the four-armed ape was agile, it was as large as an elephant. It was stopped outside, it stretched its long arm into the earth trench but could not grab onto Meng Qiu Zhen.

Meng Qiu Zhen even easily experienced the power of a land spirit.

In fact, this was an extremely rare and valuable experience!

Gu Immortals were not land spirits, they might be the owner of their immortal aperture but their control over their own immortal aperture was far lower than land spirits or heavenly spirits.

It was like how Fang Yuan had to spread his divine sense to the whole of sovereign immortal aperture to inspect the situation.

Land spirits or heavenly spirits were formed by Gu Immortal obsessions fused with the immortal aperture’s heavenly power.

In this sense, land spirits and heavenly spirits were one with the immortal aperture. The Gu Immortal’s obsession gave them their spirituality.

Land spirits and heavenly spirits had an extremely deep understanding and control over the immortal aperture.

Fang Yuan had to use perceivable dao Immortal Gu or such methods to inspect the number of his dao marks. But land spirits or heavenly spirits could easily know it; they only had to concentrate slightly and they would know the number and distribution of the dao marks.

This chasing and escaping situation continued for several days, Meng Qiu Zhen had no injuries, but the four-armed ape was heavily injured and died after exhausting all its strength.

After it died, Meng Qiu Zhen used wind and rain to decompose its blood and flesh, before using lightning to turn its bones into scraps. He then buried the bones underground, all the strength path dao marks were quickly added to the blessed land.

After finishing all these, Meng Qiu Zhen opened his small doll palm and crushed a small rock.

Meng Qiu Zhen nodded with joy.

The land spirit’s strength was connected to the heavenly power of the small world. What was the foundation of the heavenly power?

It was the dao marks in the immortal aperture.

After passing the four-armed ape desolate beast earthly calamity, the blessed land’s strength path dao marks surged which increased Meng Qiu Zhen’s strength. He could crush these firm rocks which he had not been able to do earlier.

Crushing the rock pieces was only a small display, Meng Qiu Zhen gathered his strength and stirred the water surface, creating huge waves.

Chapter 2312: Profundity of the Heaven Path Dream Realm

Waves continued to strike the rocky land, flooding and breaking the land including the earth spikes.

Earth trenches were already submerged in water, the underwater force continued to surge and slam into the trenches, enlarging them.

Faint rumbling sounds resounded in the blessed land, the rocky land started to break apart due to the continuous flood.

The separated rocky land turned into five large islands and tens of smaller islands.

Meng Qiu Zhen finally relaxed after finishing this step, a sense of accomplishment rose in his heart.

It was not easy to reach this stage.

At first, this blessed land had the highest number of earth path dao marks, the dao marks of other paths were very few, the difference between the two was large which led the terrain to become rocky.

The rocky land’s advantages and disadvantages were obvious. It could produce rock materials and ore mines which were very beneficial to the rockmen’s habitat, but it was not beneficial for the growth of vegetation.

The blessed land’s terrain was not a bad thing originally.

However, when Meng Qiu Zhen probed the next three earthly calamities; the first calamity was the strength path beast calamity four-armed ferocious ape; the second calamity was a fire path calamity fire rain, and the third was a transformation path calamity flies tribulation.

Meng Qiu Zhen understood that this dream path blessed land’s calamities and tribulations were not based on earth path. Developing in earth path did not have much prospects.

Meng Qiu Zhen immediately decided to remodel the terrain!

After a Gu Master undergoes immortal ascension, very few who would change the terrain of their immortal aperture.

This step was not easy.

Fortunately, this was a dream realm and Meng Qiu Zhen had a land spirit’s powers.

He first destroyed the complete rocky land but he could not do it perfectly because he lacked strength path dao marks.

Afterwards, he used his create dream killer move to create earth spikes and used earth trenches and caverns to kill the four-armed ape.

This step was quite difficult.

If he did not have create dream, Meng Qiu Zhen would have no earth spikes, the four-armed ape would have lived for a very long period. He would need to wait for it to die of hunger before the immortal aperture blessed land could digested it slowly to obtain strength path dao marks.

Using the earth spikes, Meng Qiu Zhen quickly got rid of the four-armed ape.

But because of conflicting dao marks, the blessed land could only absorb most of the strength path dao marks and not all of it. Fortunately, this portion was enough, Meng Qiu Zhen finally split apart the complete rock land.

Next was painstaking work.

Meng Qiu Zhen chose a large island and began to crush the peripheral rocky land into a large amount of gravel.

This was an arduous task.

First, he had to accumulate lightning clouds to bombard it, then use fierce wind and water waves to erode the land.

With strength path dao marks, the wind and waves were much more forceful than before but the efficiency of crushing rocks was not high. A lot of strength had to be spent for minimal results.

In fact, there were a lot of good methods. For instance, using fire to heat the rock surface then using water to cool it immediately would disintegrate the rocks easily.

But this dream realm blessed land did not have fire path dao marks which really troubled Meng Qiu Zhen.

What he was doing now was the same as using a knife to cut a tree.

Several days passed as he continued this laborious grinding, gravel filled the surrounding of the large island. These gravel were ground down by wind and water, they were tiny and smooth like mini cobblestones.

The work on the first large island was completed, Meng Qiu Zhen then worked on the second large island.

Rainwater had gathered into a sea around the islands.

In actuality, it could not be considered a sea, it was at most a large lake.

Meng Qiu Zhen did not bother to create waves normally, so the water surface was smooth as a mirror. Only when he needed to crush the firm rocks or step on water to as a traveling method would he take the initiative to raise the wind and waves.

This blessed land did not not have space path dao marks, it was not large and Meng Qiu Zhen could not teleport even as a land spirit.

Time passed by as the small islands were remodeled.After Meng Qiu Zhen finished remodeling all the large islands and even seven-eight small islands, he welcomed the fire path calamity.

Fire rain fell heavily.

Every drop of fire rain was the size of a wash basin, countless fire raindrops struck with a huge momentum

The fire rain fell on the islands, the rocky ground and gravel burned intensely. Some thin gravel even melted, turning into lava that slowly flowed towards the water.

Gradually, the rock islands with towering edges began to transform under the devastating fire rain. All the peripheral areas of the islands got submerged under water, the middle part was level with the lake surface, while the upper part was slightly higher, forming a beach made of gravel.

Most of the fire rain landed on the water, creating towering steam. The vapor rose and gradually formed thick clouds that covered the whole blessed land.

Meng Qiu Zhen was hiding under the ground where there were dense earth path dao marks as he had the ability to move underground as a land spirit.

He let the fire rain wreak havoc while occasionally keeping an eye on the rock islands.

The fire rain lasted for a long time before dissipating.

Meng Qiu Zhen returned above ground and sensed that the temperature had risen by several times while the air was moist and hot.

The whole blessed land was covered with thick clouds. As there was a large fire rain just now, the clouds looked like a burning blanket.

How could it not be hot?

Meng Qiu Zhen used wind to blow away these clouds which immediately cooled the atmosphere.

However, shortly after, steam condensed in the sky again, forming light clouds. It would probably form back into the thick cloud layer after some time.

Meng Qiu Zhen immediately realized that the fire path calamity brought a large number of fire path dao marks. He needed to restrain most of the fire path dao marks and could let them interfere with his arrangements.

“If there is a large number of light path dao marks, I can gather most of the fire path dao marks into an artificial sun.”

Meng Qiu Zhen felt some pity.

This dream realm blessed land had light path dao marks but they were so few that the blessed land had always been dimly lit.

The plan to create a sun was not possible but Meng Qiu Zhen had other methods.

Immediately, he activated create dream killer move, and after going through ten or so procedures, most of the fire path dao marks were gathered in the depths of the roots of the large islands.

Fire path dao marks were restrained by the even denser earth path dao marks, forming magma inside the large islands.

Outside of the islands, the temperature fell down rapidly because of the decrease in fire path dao marks. The light clouds that were floating in the sky would no longer accumulate by itself.

“There is no artificial sun so there won’t be hot weather, but with magma, there is geothermal energy which can be used similarly.”

As long as Meng Qiu Zhen used the strength path dao marks, he could trigger a reaction to turn the large islands into live volcanoes that shoot out qi currents before exploding with flowing lava and a large amount of ash.

Meng Qiu Zhen’s mind jolted as he had a sudden realization.

“My blessed land does not have qi path dao marks or sound path dao marks, but when the volcanoes erupt, they will shoot out qi currents and create loud explosions. Previously, the fire rain hit the lake and created steam clouds but there were no cloud path dao marks here.”

“This is probably the origin of the ability to mimic other paths!”

When a Gu cultivator cultivates a path to a certain level, they can imitate the power of other paths and reach a comprehensive balance.

For instance, the wood path killer move fleeting bloom imitated the power of time path.

Bai Xiang killer move belonged to ice and snow path but had transformation path power.

Stone throw inquiry killer move was an earth path move but had information path effect.

After comprehending this truth, a portion of the true meaning of this dream realm was absorbed by Meng Qiu Zhen. His heaven path attainment level increased slightly which synchronized with the main body and other clones.

Meng Qiu Zhen inspected himself and found that although he had become a land spirit, he could not completely control the dao marks of every path.

Land spirits controlled heavenly power but were only a portion of the immortal aperture’s accumulation.

For instance, Meng Qiu Zhen went to painstaking efforts to crush the rocks, it was in essence loosening a lump of earth path dao marks and separating them.

If Meng Qiu Zhen had full control over earth path dao marks, he could turn the firm rocks into sand with just a thought.

Land spirits controlled heavenly power but their usage of it was only at the superficial level. Moreover, he had to use wind, water, and other forces to crush the rocks.

So how could he deepen this control?

More specifically speaking, how could he turn the firm rocks into sand?

Meng Qiu Zhen immediately thought of turn sand Gu.

This Gu could turn earth and rocks into fine sand.

He then thought of many killer moves of different paths that could turn the rocks into sand.

In an instant, Meng Qiu Zhen’s perception of killer moves and Gu worms became different.

He could not put it in words or explain it.

These insights accumulated in his mind and were slightly inferior to the previous comprehension. Only a thorough comprehension would increase his heaven path attainment level.

Heaven path dream realms were different from the past dream realms.

To absorb the true meaning in the heaven path dream realms, one had to develop the dream realm blessed land while also comprehending the truth of the operations of heaven and earth.

This made it difficult.

When Fang Yuan explored human path dream realms[. The new theory of Feng Jin Huang, it can be of any path as long as it is a human dream.], he only needed to explore them to a certain degree to raise his attainment levels.

Exploration of heaven path dream realms only maintained a close connection between the person and the heaven path true meaning, this link needed to be comprehended to raise the attainment level.

“After all, there is a thin line separating the heaven path dream realm and the human.”

Just as Meng Qiu Zhen was thinking, the world turned upside down.

The whole blessed land shook intensely and turned upside down; the lake overturned and gushed backwards while the islands flew and crashed with each other.

“What... what’s going on?!” Meng Qiu Zhen’s expression changed. The suddenly disorder in the dream realm gave him a huge pressure.

Meng Qiu Zhen quickly activated Dream Armor to protect himself.

Fortunately, the dream realm’s shaking only lasted for a while before calming.

Meng Qiu Zhen’s expression was pale. It was very fortunate that he had dream armor Gu and he chose to explore a mid-size heaven path dream realm instead of being greedy.

If not for this, he would have died in this calamity.

“This is not a development of the heaven path dream realm but an interference from the outside world! It is probably a venerable who made the move.”

Meng Qiu Zhen thought as he looked at the ruins in front of him, smiling bitterly at the scene of the disorderly blessed land.

His hard work and effort were all wasted!

“If this attack occurs few times more, I won’t be able to continue exploring. The calamities and tribulations will become increasingly strong. Sigh, hopefully, my main body can protect me.”

Chapter 2313: Heavenly Ghost Concealment

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s killer move was called chaotic intent dispels dream.

It was a wisdom path killer move but included a large number of dream path mortal Gu to imitate the power of dream path, it could influence dream realms.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable deduced this move to counter Fang Yuan’s dream realm methods.

In the past, Fang Yuan had self-detonated Pure Dream Reality Seeker bodies to create dream realms in battles, and with most methods in the world being ineffective against dream realms, Fang Yuan was able to succeed time and again.

Afterwards, when Fang Yuan wanted to collect these dream realms, he would use pure dream reality seeker transformation killer move to transform the dream realms into clones and take them away.

But this situation could not happen after chaotic intent dispels dream killer move was used.

The dream path mortal Gu in chaotic intent dispels dream only had the function of a key, the true method was still wisdom path.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used the wisdom path method to disturb the will and emotions contained in the dream realm to make them chaotic.

Whether it be the human path dream realms or heaven path dream realms, they contained human wills and emotions, or heaven’s will.

When these wills and emotions turn chaotic, dream realms—especially the orderly dream realms—would lose their order and turn chaotic. The Gu cultivator who was exploring the dream realm would be met with calamity like a fish that entered water which had started to boil.

Once the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies were struck by this move, their stable human bodies would turn back into dream realms. Their human wills, emotions, and so on would turn disorderly along with the dream realms and be unable to think.

Meng Qiu Zhen who entered with his body and soul would be torn into pieces by the chaotic dream realm as time passed.

Fortunately, Fang Yuan stopped this in time, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was forced to stop the move which allowed Meng Qiu Zhen to escape disaster.

As for the efforts in remodeling the dream realm blessed land turning to waste, they were already minor details.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable flew back while avoiding Fang Yuan’s attacks and observing the heaven path dream realm.

When she saw the heaven path dream realm that swallowed Meng Qiu Zhen returning to its previous self and not having any other abnormal changes, she knew Meng Qiu Zhen was still alive.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable sighed inwardly.

Deducing this chaotic intent dispels dream was already the limit of her ability.

It was because dream path restricted her.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was almost a blank slate in dream path, she also did not have any dream path Immortal Gu and had to use a large number of dream path mortal Gu as replacement. She fully relied on her terrifying wisdom path foundation to raise the killer move to rank eight level!

She wanted to do more but she was powerless.

This was the reason she could not save Fairy Zi Wei and Ying Wu Xie who were trapped in heaven path dream realms. At most, she could use this killer move to kill them.

But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable needed a living Spectral Soul clone, there was no meaning in killing him.

She, however, wanted to kill Meng Qiu Zhen.

But chaotic intent dispels dream’s activation needed to be maintained, if she was disturbed by Fang Yuan in this process, she would suffer a backlash which was dangerous.

Fang Yuan attacked intensely, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s method made him anxious. He could only observe closely and not give her any chance to continue activating the killer move.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable attacked crazily from the side.

Fang Yuan’s attention was mainly on Star Constellation Immortal Venerable so he could only try to dodge Giant Sun’s attacks.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was aggressive and had plenty of battle experience, most of his attacks still landed on Fang Yuan’s body.

Fang Yuan had reverse flow protection seal but Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s lingering scrap luck was too troublesome so he canceled the move and relied on heavenly web protection veil to defend himself.

This was a genuine rank nine killer move with the amplification of Fang Yuan’s heaven path dao marks, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s attacks did not achieve anything.

No matter how mysterious and ingenious or grand and majestic Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s attacks were, they were treated as non-existent when they struck Fang Yuan.

“What kind of defensive method is this?!” The more Giant Sun Immortal Venerable fought, the more shaken he was. Even his face started to shake.

The tighter Fang Yuan’s defense was, the more Giant Sun Immortal Venerable wanted to see through him. But obscured heavenly secret had merged with heavenly web protection veil, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s investigative methods were all thwarted by obscured heavenly secret.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could not see through him, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was the same.

The two venerables felt increasingly suspicious.

Fang Yuan was defending against Star Constellation Immortal Venerable while transmitting his voice to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to help him and attack Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, emphasizing on Heavenly Court’s strength.

Moreover, he promised Giant Sun Immortal Venerable that if he did this, he would innovate even more blood path Immortal Gu and blood path research results, he would give them to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable immediately felt much better, if Fang Yuan was making such a big concession, it meant he probably could not hold on for long.

But his attacks became even stronger as he transmitted his voice: ”Fang Yuan, you are too modest, you are probably the strongest among us three venerables currently! Not to mention anything else, just your defensive method actually made us helpless.”

Fang Yuan quickly said: ”This killer move uses secluded domain of heaven and earth—City Well—as the core, Giant Sun, you have no rank nine killer move currently, how can you break it? Since you can’t break it, why make things difficult for me and let Star Constellation Immortal Venerable obtain the biggest benefits?”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable slowed down his attacks.

In his mind, he thought: ’Fang Yuan is doing his best to convince me and speaking so submissively, he may really be at his limit. He has the least immortal essence, his killer moves are so terrifying, how can they not expend a lot of immortal essence?’

‘I will slow down my attacks and let him catch a breather so he can continue this battle of attrition with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable!’

‘As for the heaven path dream realms, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable almost succeeded just earlier. How can Fang Yuan absorb so many heaven path dream realms in a short time?’

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable saw Giant Sun Immortal Venerable slowing his attacks, she immediately had a bad feeling and inwardly cursed Giant Sun while transmitting her voice to him.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable told Giant Sun that attainment levels were the most difficult to progress in, since Fang Yuan was so determined on developing in heaven path, these heaven path dreams were of huge help to him. How could they watch as he succeeds?

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable made a perfunctory reply.

The fight of the three venerables continued in a stalemate, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable continued to persuade: ”Giant Sun, look at Heaven Refining Demon Venerable. His situation is the worst but is already fighting me to a draw. What will happen if he has enough immortal essence in the future?”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable sighed as he replied: ”What you say makes sense. But...”

He sighed again as he hesitated to speak.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s eyelids twitched slightly, she knew she had to give benefits to make Giant Sun Immortal Venerable take action.

She did not hesitate as she immediately handed many blood path research results to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable through treasure yellow heaven.

After obtaining the benefits, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable attacked Fang Yuan madly once again.

Fang Yuan sighed inwardly.

He knew that the strength he exposed had already touched the bottom-line of the two venerables. If he crossed it by even a little, the two venerables would ally even more closely.

This would incur an unfavorable loss.

Immediately, Fang Yuan shouted loudly: ”You guys forced me!”

The moment he finished speaking, he activated a killer move, turning into a spiral light rainbow that zoomed past the battlefield.

The two venerables were stunned before their expressions changed. They understood Fang Yuan’s evil intention as they quickly used their methods to obstruct the spiral rainbow.

The two venerables lacked tacit coordination, they attacked at the same time which instead left Fang Yuan unharmed.

Fang Yuan did not receive any attacks. He immediately retreated and pulled apart some distance from the two venerables before using a killer move to fly out of the battlefield.

The two venerables could only try to obstruct him again.

This time, they communicated with each other and there was no loophole like before.

But like this, Fang Yuan had the initiative instead.

The two venerables felt stifled as Fang Yuan was headed towards Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

In the fight of the three venerables, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s inactivity was a good thing to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. Fang Yuan had evil intentions, he wanted to anger this venerable and bring him over to create chaos while he looked to gain benefits.

The confrontation lasted for a while but the two venerables could not stop him every time, eventually, Fang Yuan managed to hit Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had lost his rationality, he was a venerable but was closer to being a soul beast.

After being angered, he immediately charged into the battlefield of the three venerables.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could only helplessly face him.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable did not care who was who, anyone that was before him needed to be dealt with!

Over this period, his strength had increased by a lot and was no longer in the previously weak state. The three venerables needed to be much more careful than before when fighting Spectral Soul.

Spectral Soul’s attacks were grand and ferocious, he even activated killer moves from time to time.

The three venerables did not want to provoke this lunatic. They had to fight each other as well; in short, the situation was extremely chaotic.

The chaotic battlefield was the most beneficial to Fang Yuan as he could finally take a breather. If the previous situation continued, his obscured heavenly secret would not have been able to last for long.

Immediately, he took advantage of the chaos to activate obscured heavenly secret twice on himself without leaking even a trace of their aura.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable kept on planning and finally grasped the chance, luring Spectral Soul Demon Venerable into the group of heaven path dream realms.

But the heaven path dream realms did not do anything to Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, thwarting Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s plan.

The four venerables fought amidst the heaven path dream realms, as long as it was not a dream path killer move, even venerable killer moves could not harm the heaven path dream realms.

The heaven path dream realms did not attack Spectral Soul Demon Venerable but attacked the other three venerables.

At the same time, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable joined hands to attack Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan needed to attack Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and continue pressuring her to stop her from harming his clone Meng Qiu Zhen.

As for Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, he attacked no matter who it was. The heaven path dream realms were not an exception, but his attacks were ineffective on them.

This chaotic scene lasted for fifteen minutes, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable gradually gained an upper hand.

She was a wisdom path Gu Immortal who was proficient in planning, a chaotic situation meant she had much more factors to calculate. When she started adapting and was clear of various factors, she could make use of the surrounding environment easily.

Discovering that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had repeatedly used the surrounding heaven path dream realms, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, or Spectral Soul Demon Venerable to stop him, Fang Yuan knew it was time to use another trump card.

Immortal killer move — Heavenly Ghost Concealment!

At the next moment, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable directly ignored Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan openly moved past Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s countless hands and reached Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

A fierce killer move dealt a huge blow to the unprepared Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

“Fang Yuan, you...”

“Fang Yuan, impressive, so that was it.”

Star Constellation and Giant Sun were shaken.

Chapter 2314: I Reside in All Living Beings and Heaven and Earth

Among the many modified killer moves, heavenly ghost concealment was actually the first to be completed.

Since the battle in Crazed Demon Cave where Fang Yuan’s ghostly concealment was restrained, Fang Yuan had the thought of modifying it.

When his heaven path attainment level rose rapidly and had stealing heavenly secret killer move, he modified ghostly concealment into heavenly ghost concealment.

Ghostly concealment killer move itself was at rank nine so there was not much improvement. But after adding in heaven path Gu worms, the previous targeted methods against ghostly concealment became ineffective.

At this time, Fang Yuan’s body was covered by a layer of dark translucent armor and a pale white bone mask covered his face.

[EMPTY]

It was the manifestation of heavenly ghost concealment killer move.

Different from obscured heavenly secret, heavenly ghost concealment’s aura was surging but it seemed to be completely non-existent to Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable used many methods in a row but they were all ineffective towards Fang Yuan’s heavenly ghost concealment.

“This is a heaven path method which shows Fang Yuan has talents and attainment in this path. Giant Sun, are you still going to watch as Fang Yuan gains these heaven path dream realms and let him gain a boost of strength?” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used this chance to persuade Giant Sun and strengthen his wariness towards Fang Yuan.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable heaved a sigh: ”Fang Yuan can cultivate all paths, once he succeeds in cultivating heaven path, it will form a mystical connection with other paths, and his gains will be inestimable.”

He was persuaded by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and increased the power of his attacks.

Despite this, Fang Yuan’s situation had turned better.

He fought while moving around Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, his main target still Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Immortal killer move — Seven Kills Rainbow!

This compound killer move was used by Fang Yuan repeatedly to disturb Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable tried to use chaotic intent dispels dream killer move again and again; sometimes, she would have just finished preparing the move when Fang Yuan caught up to her, and sometimes, she just activated it but had to cancel it to cope with Fang Yuan’s attacks.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable attacked Fang Yuan but Fang Yuan stayed close to Spectral Soul Demon Venerable and dodged slightly to let Spectral Soul Demon Venerable take the attacks.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable took on the attacks and became more furious, going on full offensive. He saw Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable as a thorn in his eyes but ignored Fang Yuan who was using him.

After this stalemate lasted for a long time, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable decisively changed the strategy. She made Giant Sun Immortal Venerable protect her while she looked for a chance to use her killer move.

Fang Yuan’s expression shook slightly.

As the battle continued, these two venerables’ cooperation became even deeper.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable roared as he attacked Star Constellation Immortal Venerable with his countless giant arms.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable gave a shout as he blocked in front of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable; vast golden fog appeared and covered most of the battlefield.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s countless hands slammed into the golden fog and rummaged through them. The golden fog continued to dissipate but was quickly replenished.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had lost his senses, he should have used a killer move at this moment to break through the defense quickly.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable took advantage of this point. Even if Spectral Soul Demon Venerable used a killer move, it might not be the correct choice.

Fang Yuan heaved a sigh, he had no choice but to use another card.

Immortal killer move — Arrival of Dragon Snake with Dust Fog and Explosive Soul Wind!

Fang Yuan pointed at Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable immediately wailed mournfully, one hundred of his large black arms suddenly twisted and turned into dragons and snakes that breathed out dust and dense fog. They then exploded, forming countless wind blades that destroyed Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s golden fog.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable coughed out a huge mouthful of blood, his defensive method was broken and he suffered a backlash.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was also caught in the move and the chaotic intent dispels dream that was activated for a few breaths of time was forced to stop.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable howled and roared in anger as he charged towards the two venerables. Fang Yuan was hidden by heavenly ghost concealment, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable thought the two venerables had attacked instead.

“A new killer move again! This aura... the core is definitely the secluded domain of heaven and earth—Luo Po Valley.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable grabbed his chest as he healed his injuries while avoiding Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s ghost hands.

“How many killer moves of this level did he deduce?” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable gritted her teeth, her eyes flickered with starlight as she wanted to see through Fang Yuan.

But Fang Yuan was still protected by obscured heavenly secret, she could not see through him no matter what she did.

After Fang Yuan used this move, he looked exhausted and attacked less as if he had expended a lot of immortal essence.

He could not use Shocking Departure of Year Dream Wave and Dang Hun Sound because the rank seven Dream Armor was given to Meng Qiu Zhen.

Arrival of Dragon Snake with Dust Fog and Explosive Soul Wind was was quite good.

But because it was a compound killer move, involving many paths and Gu worms, Fang Yuan’s thoughts were almost emptied. After all, he had to continue maintaining rank nine killer moves, heavenly web protection veil and heavenly ghost concealment. Fortunately, rank nine obscured heavenly secret killer move did not need him to pay attention to it at all times.

One of the disadvantages of compound killer moves was that they expended too much thoughts.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable made a clever adjustment but still failed. Meng Qiu Zhen continued to explore the dream realm, providing constant benefits to Fang Yuan’s main body.

Although Fang Yuan’s attacks decreased visibly, he used Arrival of Dragon Snake with Dust Fog and Explosive Soul Wind to repel and suppress the two venerables.

Spectral heaven had just formed, the heavenly wind qi wall was not thick enough, and there were no clouds, the five regions’ Gu Immortals could observe the battle easily.

Looking at Fang Yuan gaining the upper hand, many Gu Immortals of Central Continent and Northern Plains were shocked and worried. Some cursed Fang Yuan for his shamelessness; some prayed for the righteous path; while some were shaken by the demonic might, their face turned deathly pale.

As for the Eastern Sea Gu Immortals, joy showed on their faces.

“Damn it, if my Blood Sea was completed and I had a blood path killer move of such a level, why would I fear Fang Yuan’s methods?” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable gritted his teeth, his stifled emotions accumulated to the limit, finally making him use his full strength!

Luck path killer move — I Reside in All Living Beings and Heaven and Earth!

After Giant Sun Immortal Venerable activated this move, a giant pillar of light formed immediately. The light pillar was dazzlingly golden and stood majestically between heaven and earth, it was tens of thousands of feet tall and was very thick.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable stood inside the golden light pillar, his two hands and legs were spread apart to the sides.

His hair fluttered, his face distorted ferociously as he screamed, veins bulged over his whole body as if he was in extreme pain.

When the killer move was activated, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s attacks were all blocked by the golden light pillar. Fang Yuan tried to attack but found that if he attacked the golden light pillar once, his luck would shake and even showed a sign of being absorbed by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Fang Yuan made a wise decision to stop his action.

“Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, what did you do?” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s expression was unsightly as well.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s move was too powerful and even influenced her.

The golden light pillar lasted for a short nine breaths of time before stopping abruptly and dissipating.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s body was covered in a layer of golden radiance. His muscles were bulging, his golden hair fluttered wildly, his entire body seemed to have expanded.

He looked towards Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. The sharp gaze made even Star Constellation Immortal Venerable narrow her eyes.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable mumbled: ”Star Constellation, do not worry. This move’s range covers the entire five regions, there was no way to avoid you.”

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable roared, raising terrifying black fog that covered the sky.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable shouted and breathed out fiercely, forming a boundless hurricane.

The hurricane swept everything, pushing aside the black fog, revealing hundreds of thousands of tadpole like soul balls.

The soul balls exploded around Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable snorted in disdain, that faint golden light barrier was not even the least bit damaged.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s countless hands attacked, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable met the attacks with just fists and kicks.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s ghost hands and dark arms were like eggs thrown at a rock. After the collision, countless golden light specks drilled into the dark arms then shot out, exploding the dark arms.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable began to counterattack, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was immediately suppressed. No matter how madly he counterattacked, he was attacked even more ruthlessly by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Fang Yuan fought with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and found that Giant Sun had gotten a comprehensive boost in offense, defense, movement, and healing.

Fang Yuan was also suppressed but he gradually saw some details: ”This move is probably forcibly extracting external luck and enforcing it on his body. But how large is the range of this move?”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s conversation with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable just earlier was done through voice transmission. Fang Yuan did not know this move’s range was so shocking large that it covered the entire five regions!

This move had an even deeper profundity, it could influence heaven and earth luck, as well as all living beings luck, making all the luck revolve around Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

The killer move was called ’I reside in all living beings and heaven and earth’, it truly lived up to its name!

Fang Yuan had Cooking Luck Pot and heavenly web protection veil, his luck was not influenced by this move. But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s defensive methods against luck path were broken by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and rendered useless.

But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not express anything for the moment. After all, the urgent thing was to deal with Fang Yuan and kill Meng Qiu Zhen!

After activating the killer move, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s luck rose to an unprecedented level. Adding on his combat system, his strength received a terrifying all-rounded amplification.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was lacking rationality, after attacking madly for a while, he actually showed signs of defeat.

Fang Yuan was not well-off either, but he was still concentrating on Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

In fact, whether Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was strong or not was not crucial. As long as there was no restriction from a battlefield killer move, Fang Yuan was free to advance and retreat.

In Fang Yuan’s opinion, the key factor was still Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

He shouted towards Star Constellation Immortal Venerable openly and not through voice transmission: ”Star Constellation, you have a good plan to make me and Giant Sun expend our immortal essence while you stall for time. Can your method even destroy my dream path clone?”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable sneered: ”If that’s what you think, how about letting me have a try?”

Fang Yuan replied calmly: ”Star Constellation, you are still the more skillful one, you saw through my cautious mind and that I won’t dare to take a risk in this matter. In that case, I have no choice but to resort to other methods.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable were immediately vigilant.

Since the start, the killer moves Fang Yuan revealed were extremely shocking and powerful. Especially his defensive method, the two venerables were still unable to see through it.

The two venerables were paying close attention for a while but did not see Fang Yuan using any more methods.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable chuckled: ”Fang Yuan, just a verbal threat does not mean anything.”

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: ”I have used this method long ago. Speaking of it, Star Constellation’s star array calculation formation is really vast and amazing. Such a pity, it is such a pity, it was constructed in a hurry and is going to be destroyed just as quickly as well.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable immediately frowned.

At the same time.

Central Continent.

Outside of the star array calculation formation.

Qi Sea Ancestor appeared.

Rumble...

His qi path killer move activated. At the next moment, heaven and earth shook as boundless qi surged and pressed down on the star array calculation formation.

Chapter 2315: Nothing is Certain Except Success

Ever since the sun was destroyed, five regions and two heavens fell into deep darkness.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable who was burning with blue, eerie fire could never replace the sun. Because what he gave the world were not vitality and warmth, but coldness and killing intent.

In this darkness, the countless stars shining in the sky of Central Continent became a consolation for the mortals.

However, right now, these dazzling starlights were being attacked!

Vast and surging qi currents submerged the boundless starlight.

Qi Sea Ancestor waved his sleeves as he slowly flew in the air and continued his attacks with an indifferent expression.

He was one of the arrangements Fang Yuan made when he deployed troops before. Right now, he immediately acted after receiving the main body’s message.

The space inside star array calculation formation was in an uproar.

There were many Gu Immortals stationed here.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable arranged many Gu Immortals here because star array calculation formation was fragile.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was aware that star array calculation formation which was constructed in just a short period was Heavenly Court’s weakness and would become other venerables’ target.

So she also left Embroidered Tower and Star Constellation Chessboard in this formation!

“Qi Sea Ancestor appeared at the northeast side, he extinguished three thousand eight hundred and seventy-one stars with one move.”

“Urgent report! Fang Yuan’s enslavement path clone Wu Shuai appeared at the northwest side and destroyed two thousand six hundred and sixty-four stars.”

Star Constellation’s will inside Embroidered Tower was just about to send orders when the whole formation space shook fiercely.

She then heard the Gu Immortals in charge of information shout in panic: ”Zhan Bu Du, Zhan Bu Du appeared! He is attacking from the south and is coming straight towards us!”

“Zhan Bu Du?” Star Constellation’s will immediately controlled her thoughts to take a look through the star array calculation formation. She saw a bright-looking young man wearing a large blood-red cape. His momentum was like a tiger coming out of the mountain or a mad dragon descending upon the world, his attacks produced explosive sounds as he moved forward.

Star Constellation’s will sighed.

There were already clues from Fang clan’s situation about Fang Yuan being able to revive Gu Immortals. Zhan Bu Du’s revival did not surprise Star Constellation’s will.

But she was a bit troubled in this situation.

Qi Sea Ancestor and Zhan Bu Du had pseudo venerable battle strength while Wu Shuai was a peak rank eight expert. In this aspect, Heavenly Court lacked elite experts that could match them.

Qing Chou could be considered one but was guarding Divine Emperor City at this moment. Based on strategical importance, Divine Emperor City was much more important than star array calculation formation.

As for Qin Ding Ling, Che Wei, and the rest, they were experts among rank eights but were still lacking compared to Qi Sea and Zhan Bu Du.

“Fang Yuan can revive Gu Immortals while preserving their cultivation level. If so, where are his variant human rank eight subordinates hiding now?

The situation was not clear, Star Constellation’s will decided to play it safe and prioritize defending star array calculation formation.

Star Constellation’s will personally controlled star array calculation formation; in an instant, dazzling starlight shone.

Qi Sea Ancestor and Wu Shuai had to close their eyes and use investigative killer moves. Only Zhan Bu Du who had a very strong body opened his eyes wide without any worries.

Starlight dimmed quickly, Qi Sea Ancestor, Wu Shuai, and Zhan Bu Du’s vision changed suddenly, they found themselves on a large chessboard.

“This is... Star Constellation Chessboard?”

“Hmph! This star array calculation formation and Star Constellation Chessboard can mutually support each other.”

“Not only this, it probably has Embroidered Tower’s help as well!”

Fang Yuan’s three clones conversed secretly while attacking madly.

Explosions rang, star array calculation formation shook intensely but it was able to barely hold on with the help of Embroidered Tower and Star Constellation Chessboard.

“This is not good, if the situation falls into a stalemate, how can we help our main body pressure Star Constellation Immortal Venerable?” Qi Sea Ancestor’s heart sank slightly.

The other two knew this was not good and strengthened their attacks.

Spectral heaven.

The fight of the four venerables was continuing.

Fang Yuan’s clones made a move but were blocked by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s arrangements. However, Fang Yuan’s situation was improving quickly.

His situation was troubling earlier because Giant Sun Immortal Venerable used his full strength.

But the situation was changing now because of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable as well.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s battle strength was falling constantly.

Although the killer move—I reside in all living beings and heaven and earth—was very strong, it forcibly extracted external luck. It was like a rootless tree or a sourceless body of water; the more it was used, the less would remain.

Not only this, when the effect of this move dissipate completely, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s luck would fall into a weakened state which would last for a while before it goes back to normal.

The news of star array calculation formation being attacked was already known by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable at the very first moment.

But she could not go back to reinforce it.

The moment she did that, she would fall into Fang Yuan’s trap. At that time, why would Giant Sun Immortal Venerable be willing to fight against Spectral Soul Demon Venerable and Fang Yuan alone?

If Star Constellation Immortal Venerable blindly cared about Heavenly Court’s benefits, it would definitely put a crack in the two venerables’ alliance. After all, Giant Sun was not a Heavenly Court venerable, he did not share the same sentiments as Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, this alliance was just because of the situation.

In fact, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable suspected that if she were to go back to reinforce Central Continent, Fang Yuan would give chase.

Among the venerables, only Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could pose a threat to Meng Qiu Zhen. Fang Yuan would directly bring the battlefield to Central Continent which was even more harmful to Central Continent.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable defended against Fang Yuan’s constant interference while inwardly sighing at his craftiness and understanding of the human heart, choosing a perfect time for his clones to make a move.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable also tried using other killer moves to attack Fang Yuan.

Although Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was strong, he had lost his senses and was only an annoyance. Fang Yuan was still the crucial factor and the biggest threat!

But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s constant attempts showed no visible effects.

Fang Yuan used Spectral Soul Demon Venerable to protect himself, his battle tactic was shallow but it had an excellent effect.

The four venerables’ chaotic battle lasted for a while longer. Seeing that ’I reside in all living beings and heaven and earth’ killer move was decreasing in effect, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had no choice but to activate this move again.

In an instant, golden light pillar appeared once again. It spanned across heaven and earth, it was grand, magnificent, and extremely dazzling.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s luck strengthened once again and his battle strength rose to the previous state.

I reside in all living beings and heaven and earth killer move could be used continuously but its after-effects would increase subsequently. Right now, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was in a position from which he could not retreat, his whole combat system was based on his positive luck. If his luck was low, his battle strength would reduced significantly.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable naturally did not want to reveal the flaw of this move when he was using it for the first time.

Fang Yuan saw Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s aura rising again, he immediately retreated and used Spectral Soul Demon Venerable as a shield to block the attacks.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s clenched his teeth in hatred as he saw Fang Yuan’s action.

He knew that if he did not do something, the previous situation would replay, so he immediately used another trump card.

Luck path killer move — Nothing is Certain Except Success!

Golden light flickered on Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s body. The golden light slowly rose above his head and turned into an amber jade sphere.

The amber jade sphere’s aura was extremely powerful, even Fang Yuan and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable felt their hearts palpitate.

Next, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable gave a low shout and fiercely struck the amber jade sphere with his head.

The amber jade sphere shot off towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan knew how terrifying this move was when he saw that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s surging luck had mostly dissipated and nearly went back to its original state.

He could not immediately decipher the profundities in this move so he did not take this move head-on, instead dodging behind Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had no fear as he swatted the amber jade sphere far away with one hand.

The amber jade sphere was like a ball that directly fell from spectral heaven.

“What?” Fang Yuan and Star Constellation were slightly astonished.

This move had such a terrifying aura but it was actually suppressed so easily?

“Giant Sun...” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable directly expressed her concern.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable smiled, replying confidently: ”Star Constellation, please watch. This move is extraordinarily profound. It is created using self luck, all living being’s luck, and heaven and earth luck. It is not restricted by the usual concept of offense and defense but uses the variables in heaven and earth and all living beings to form a result that will astonish both of us. It is just that this move needs some time to show its power.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable heard this reply and immediately asked the crucial question: ”Then how long does it need to show an effect?”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s expression stiffened: ”The time is... not fixed.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable: ”...”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable continued: ”This move has already been used, you don’t need to worry about it. Why don’t you attack Fang Yuan with me?”

He then pounced at Fang Yuan.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable glanced at the amber jade sphere before coordinating with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable as they flew around Spectral Soul Demon Venerable and attacked Fang Yuan.

The amber jade sphere encountered a large soul beast army on its descent. After piercing through hundreds of soul beasts, its aura fell by ten percent and its direction also changed slightly.

It continued to fall, its aura dropping by another ten percent as it pierced through the heavenly wind qi wall. After it reached the sky of Central Continent, it directly shot into star array calculation formation.

Star Constellation’s will was controlling Star Constellation Chessboard and star array calculation formation to deal with Fang Yuan’s three clones.

The two sides were still in a stalemate when suddenly, the luck path killer move that looked like an amber egg intruded the inside of the starry chessboard.

“What is this?!” Qi Sea Ancestor and the group were immediately vigilant.

“Oh no.” Star Constellation’s will’s expression changed intensely.

Be it star array calculation formation or Star Constellation Chessboard, they were both wisdom path methods characterized by delicate and complicated calculations.

But the amber jade sphere was the congregation of luck path, it was a huge variable.

The amber jade sphere entered Star Constellation Chessboard and immediately disturbed the whole battlefield. It continuously absorbed and repelled all kinds of arrangements made by Star Constellation’s will, making everything turn chaotic.

Star Constellation’s will quickly tried to suppress the variables and maintain the battlefield but she could not avoid showing certain loopholes as a result.

Fang Yuan’s three clones were joyous and immediately grabbed this chance to attack the loopholes.

A while later.

There was a huge explosion. The vision of Fang Yuan’s clones changed suddenly as they reappeared in the sky above Central Continent.

A small portion of Star Constellation Chessboard was destroyed and Star Constellation’s will immediately stored it in Embroidered Tower.

Chapter 2316: Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s Explanation

Spectral heaven battlefield.

Boom!

Seven kills rainbow attacked, while starlight shone around Star Constellation Immortal Venerable as she dodged.

She was about to counterattack, when she saw Fang Yuan hiding beside Spectral Soul Demon Venerable. Since the battle started, this situation had already occurred about a hundred times.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was no longer as peeved as she was at first. She looked at Giant Sun Immortal Venerable being attacked by hundreds of Spectral Soul’s giant hands and activated a killer move, destroying tens of black hands rapidly.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable used the chance to get past the encirclement of the giant hands. Being suddenly attacked, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable changed his target to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

“Star Constellation, lure the attention of Spectral Soul while I go and capture Fang Yuan!” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable said quickly when he saw this. He then turned into golden light that moved rapidly past Spectral Soul Demon Venerable and towards Fang Yuan.

However, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable snorted coldly, she did not stay to stall Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, leaving a star avatar while her true body retreated.

The star avatar was instantly destroyed by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, he then turned around and attacked Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was entrapped once again and quickly transmitted his voice to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable with some doubts: ”Star Constellation, what are you doing?”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable directly gave Giant Sun Immortal Venerable the details of what happened in the star array calculation formation, she questioned: ”Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, how do you explain this?”

“This...” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable laughed awkwardly as he realized what happened, ”Have you heard of the luck path theory, that luck turns better after hitting rock-bottom and that fortune and misfortune coexist? This luck path killer move works like that. After it is activated, I lose all control over it. I have no idea how it will work and what effect it will show.”

“The star array calculation formation is not destroyed, this is only a small mishap. Good luck comes after bad luck, this mishap will create a huge fortune in the near future! We should be expectant.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable sneered: ”Using my mishap to exchange for your fortune? Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, is this what you are saying?”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable choked on his words and could only say: ”I will compensate you for all the direct losses, but how about we discuss the specific amount after the fight?”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable nodded at Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and continued to fight alongside him.

She chose to believe Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

In her opinion, although Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s standpoint was different from Heavenly Court, he placed great importance on family and had clear morals, he cherished his descendants and was very protective of them.

There was a clear difference between him and Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan had no limits and needed to be guarded against, his promises could not be trusted. But Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s words were believable to a degree.

Especially when this compensation was not the important thing.

Naturally, the important thing was that in this situation, a single venerable would not be able to deal with Fang Yuan.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could not stand by and watch Fang Yuan absorb all the heaven path dream realms.

At the star array calculation formation.

Qi Sea Ancestor stirred up countless qi currents that were hard to block. Zhan Bu Du charged forward like a dragon and no one was able to stop him. Wu Shuai controlled countless ants to infiltrate and tear the whole star array calculation formation apart.

Inside Embroidered Tower, Star Constellation’s will did everything to repair Star Constellation Chessboard, while controlling Embroidered Tower to help the star array calculation formation.

The star array calculation formation had very low offensive and defensive capabilities, if not for this, Giant Sun and Fang Yuan would not have stayed still as Star Constellation Immortal Venerable constructed such a formation.

Despite the help of Embroidered Tower and having the Gu Immortals inside the formation space do their best to control and repair it, the star array calculation formation was still crumbling under the fierce attacks of Fang Yuan’s three clones.

Finally, several formation cores were exposed.

“These formation cores have Immortal Gu. They are quite mysterious, my ants cannot infiltrate them.” Wu Shuai transmitted his voice.

Qi Sea Ancestor and Zhan Bu Du each made an attempt but failed as well.

These formation cores were covered in starlight and it was hard to tell if they were real or fake. The attacks of Fang Yuan’s clones had no effect and only shook the starlight intensely.

“This probably is a phantom path method. I can’t do anything.” Zhan Bu Du shrugged.

He mainly relied on incomplete freedom transformation, so he was strong in charging and breaking enemy formations, but was not good at other aspects.

Qi Sea Ancestor frowned. At this difficult time, he glanced at the amber jade sphere.

After this amber jade sphere damaged Star Constellation Chessboard, its aura and radiance had dimmed by a lot, its size shrank by sixty percent, leaving only twenty percent of its initial size.

“How about we make use of this yellow egg killer move from Giant Sun Immortal Venerable?” Qi Sea Ancestor had already obtained the information from the main body.

He communicated with the other two clones and arranged a battle tactic.

Zhan Bu Du and Wu Shuai lured the attention of Star Constellation’s will, while Qi Sea Ancestor used his qi path giant hand to grab the amber jade sphere and throw it towards the nearest formation core.

Black Heaven Temple’s Gu Immortal Zhang Ji was in charge of this formation core. He saw the amber jade sphere approaching the formation core and quickly called for help.

Star Constellation’s will noticed this and immediately made a move. Embroidered Tower shot out countless dao marks at the amber jade sphere, deviating its path away from the formation core, causing it to stop nearby.

The Gu worms near the formation core were affected by the amber jade sphere and turned chaotic.

Zhang Ji was just about to suppress this emerging problem when Fang Yuan’s three clones started attacking wantonly.

Embroidered Tower tried to defend with all its strength but the turbulence still affected other Gu worms. Originally, whether these mortal Gu died or destabilized would not have been an issue.

As long as the Immortal Gu in the formation core was safe, it was okay to just replace the mortal Gu that were lost.

But the actual situation was different.

The destabilization and destruction of the surrounding mortal Gu formed minor variables that accumulated rapidly, until they threatened the Immortal Gu in the formation core.

Zhang Ji’s effort to stabilize the situation instead assisted in this.

Then, under his incredulous gaze, the Immortal Gu in the formation core shattered directly.

The Immortal Gu in the formation cores of the star array calculation formation were originally intact, covering up for each other and closely connected. Now that one formation core suddenly crumbled apart, it immediately revealed a huge flaw in the entire formation.

Fang Yuan’s three clones attacked fiercely, Star Constellation’s will could not consider anything else and had to concentrate fully on protecting the star array calculation formation.

“Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, how do you explain this now?!” In spectral heaven, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable questioned again.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable sighed: ”I will compensate you!”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable snorted coldly: ”Is this just an issue of compensation?”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable sighed again: ”Please calm down, the most important thing now is to stop Fang Yuan. Do I look like someone who can’t understand the situation? Once this move is activated, it really is out of my control. We can only watch as it plays out.”

“Your move helped Fang Yuan’s clones and is already expended, it has disappeared completely. How can it trouble Fang Yuan’s clones now?”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable laughed heartily: ”It only disappeared on the surface, the real variables are invisible, and have already started to affect and change the world and all living beings.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s mind shook slightly, she was deducing and deepening her understanding of the killer move nothing is certain except success.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had shocking talent, this move went beyond common sense and was not in the category of any offensive killer move in history, it was new and unique.

“Then I shall wait and see.” With the enemy in front, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could only compromise.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable let out a sigh of relief in actuality.

He finally could relax now that the amber jade sphere had disappeared: ”Even if Heavenly Court suffers losses from this move in the future, there won’t be any evidence.”

“This move triggers variables in a way that is most beneficial to me. Looks like Heavenly Court is my main enemy currently which is why this move did not affect Fang Yuan, instead helping him to deal with Heavenly Court!”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable tried to figure out the situation.

In the space inside the star array calculation formation, Gu Immortal Zhang Ji coughed out a mouthful of blood, his face was extremely pale.

He used all his strength to protect the formation core but still failed in the end.

Fang Yuan’s three clones had already latched onto the weakness and began to increase their battle achievements.

Originally, the star array calculation formation was perfect, thanks to phantom path, Fang Yuan’s three clones were not able to attack it easily. But now that they had made a crucial breakthrough, there was a hole in the perfect structure and they started to attack using it.

A Gu Immortal in charge of healing arrived in front of Zhang Ji and began to treat him.

Zhang Ji was downcast as he berated himself while coughing blood: ”I am unworthy of Heavenly Court’s support and Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s trust, I lost the formation core!”

The healer Gu Immortal consoled him: ”This was all due to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s killer move, it is not your fault.”

Zhang Ji had an incredulous expression: ”This luck path killer move is truly insidious, it connected all the variables and expanded them until even the formation core Immortal Gu was harmed.”

It was like a scale where if one end was weighed down, the other end would rise. The formation cores’ Immortal Gu and the surrounding mortal Gu were like an integral whole made from countless carrying poles.

But instead of raising one end when the other was pushed down, another weight was added to suppress the rising end, these two variables canceled each other.

Nothing is certain except success acted the opposite way, it united the power of all the variables, thus destroying the formation core’s Immortal Gu.

After healing for a while, Zhang Ji’s situation was finally stable.

Over this period, another three formation cores of the star array calculation formation were destroyed by Fang Yuan’s clones.

“This is all my fault!” Zhang Ji blamed himself even more, he felt that the situation was crumbling apart.

But at this time, another Gu Immortal arrived beside him.

This was a formation path grandmaster: ”The situation is urgent, I came to repair the formation and will need your assistance.”

Zhang Ji quickly cupped his fists in greeting, expressing he would stake everything to help.

Although the formation core’s Immortal Gu was destroyed, this formation path grandmaster could use immortal materials, to set up a formation that could temporarily replace the position of the destroyed formation core’s Immortal Gu.

It was not easy to construct the star array calculation formation, Star Constellation’s will was not willing to see it be destroyed. Central Continent’s ten great sects’ Gu Immortals had tasted the benefits of this formation and were also not willing to see its destruction.

Chapter 2317: Eight-Desolate Sword Leaf Tree

The formation grandmaster calculated with all his efforts, after a while, he said with perspiration running down his face: ”I need five hundred kilograms of rank eight immortal material, heavy sand, to temporarily cover the shortage of this formation core.”

Zhang Ji’s heart sank, heavy sand was a specialty product of Western Desert and was not produced in other four regions. How could he collect such a large amount of heavy sand at this moment?

Just as Zhang Ji was worried, the formation grandmaster let out a breath of turbid air and said: ”You can get heavy sand from Heavenly Court’s storage, but I need someone to go to spectral heaven and pour at least two hundred and fifty kilograms from top to bottom. At that time, we will cooperate with that person from inside the formation and fill the hole.”

“I will go!” Zhang Ji immediately said.

The formation grandmaster shook his head, saying directly: ”Your injuries have only been suppressed and you are too weak. If you rashly exit the formation, you will be killed by those three demons easily. Those three demons will gain clues and know the approximate location of this formation space!”

“Then what should we do?” Zhang Ji sighed bitterly.

The formation grandmaster was slightly dazed as he received Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s instructions, saying: ”Alright, be it immortal materials or manpower, Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable will personally make arrangements. Zhang Ji, use this time to heal your injuries quickly. I will go to the next formation core and prepare the method to fix it.”

The formation grandmaster left hurriedly.

Zhang Ji looked at his receding figure before turning to observe his surroundings, only seeing chaos and commotion in the formation space. The Gu Immortals who were stationed here were running everywhere.

Even with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s will personally attending to this place, Fang Yuan’s three clones posed a huge threat to them.

Zhang Ji could deeply feel his powerlessness, he sighed helplessly and started healing his injuries.

Western Desert.

Lin clan’s blessed land headquarters.

Lin clan’s first supreme elder, the number one Gu Immortal in the present Western Desert, Lin Jian Xing walked out of the blessed land with Nine Spiritual Fairy.

“I wish you a smooth journey.” Lin Jian Xing smiled.

Heavenly Court wanted Lin Jian Xing’s body to create Bo Qing and restrain Spectral Soul Demon Venerable. Nine Spiritual Fairy and four other Heavenly Court Gu Immortals surrounded and attacked Lin Jian Xing but suffered a miserable defeat. Nine Spiritual Fairy covered the retreat and was captured by Lin Jian Xing.

But now, she was being personally released by Lin Jian Xing.

Nine Spiritual Fairy’s expression was heavy, she did not feel happy when regaining freedom. She looked at Lin Jian Xing and asked: ”What did Heavenly Court pay you to release me?”

Lin Jian Xing said directly: ”Star Constellation Immortal Venerable places a great importance on you, I daringly to make an offer and obtained eleven eight-desolate sword leaf trees fortunately.”

“Eight-desolate sword leaf tree....” Nine Spiritual Fairy’s heart became even heavier.

The story behind these eight-desolate sword leaf trees was huge, they originated from Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable. They were immemorial desolate plants created by the venerable and were not a naturally produced resource.

Eight-desolate sword leaf tree contained a dense number of wood path dao marks but it grew on ore mines with metal path immortal materials, and the leaves it produced were rank eight sword path immortal materials.

These eight-desolate sword leaf trees were unique resources. Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable grew them personally and only left twenty or so trees in Heavenly Court.

A number of the eight-desolate sword leaf trees died or were expended in the following period after his death. Only these eleven trees were left now and they were all obtained by Lin Jian Xing.

Lin Jian Xing accompanied Nine Spiritual Fairy till the previous regional wall area that spanned across Western Desert, Central Continent, and Northern Plains. He then watched Nine Spiritual Fairy leave alone.

“When I was negotiating with Star Constellation’s will, we were always deadlocked over the price. I did not expect Star Constellation’s will to suddenly be willing to hand me eleven eight-desolate sword leaf trees but they wanted me to provide one hundred kilograms of heavy sand along with the release of Nine Spiritual Fairy.”

“I have really made a huge gain by getting these eleven eight-desolate sword leaf trees. My guess was not wrong, as long as I can gain some comprehension from them, the recreation of my sword forest will just be around the corner.”

“Heavenly Court has too many assets and an extremely deep foundation. Even after repeated losses in battle, their foundation still cannot be matched by other super forces.”

“What a pity that I was only able to capture Nine Spiritual Fairy. Otherwise, I could have demanded even more cultivation resources from Heavenly Court.”

The destruction of fate Gu had a lasting influence on the whole world and even Gu cultivators.

Heavenly Court possessed the immortal graveyard, their Gu Immortals could revive after death. So it was a great battle tactic for them to seek death and not care for their life.

Fang Yuan went even further in this aspect, he intentionally revived Gu Immortals as Gu Masters to make them undergo immortal ascension again, using stealing heavenly secret to make huge gains.

So even if Lin Jian Xing killed Heavenly Court’s members, there would not be a huge grudge. They could revive anyway!

On the contrary, he was able to capture Nine Spiritual Fairy alive and stopped her from dying which instead became an issue for Heavenly Court.

After a long period of negotiations, Heavenly Court finally redeemed this captive by giving Lin Jian Xing what he wanted.

“It is a pity that my sword path is strong in offense but not that proficient in capturing methods.”

“Sigh, this world is quite extraordinary. My former world focused on cultivation methods, but this world prioritizes Gu worms, immortal essence, immortal materials, and other cultivation resources.”

“Cultivation resources are the foundation of everything. This confrontation of venerables is the perfect time for my Lin clan to expand. If a victor is decided between the venerables and I am still not a sword path venerable, I may have no choice other than to submit to the winner.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s previous deduction was not wrong, Lin Jian Xing was indeed an otherworldly demon. In his former world, he was the head of a Sword Sect and was known as the Grand Ancestor.

Such a person was naturally not willing to be subservient, he was a person who had seen through worldly affairs and was full of ambitions.

So, after Lin Jian Xing defeated the five Heavenly Court immortals, he did not give any explanations. He was actually happy to be treated as a demonic path member.

What would he, a grand sword path pseudo venerable, fear?

Would he fear other Western Desert super forces? Laughable!

The ones who hoped he, Lin Jian Xing, clarified that he and Lin clan were in the righteous path were these Western Desert super forces.

If so, Lin clan would be restrained under the rules of the righteous path and be unable to expand freely.

But so what if he explained himself?

Was Lin clan not a righteous path super force previously? It did not matter, Heavenly Court still attacked without a reason. This was the number one righteous path super force in the world!

On the contrary, joining demonic path was much better for Lin clan to annex other forces and expand wantonly!

Naturally, even Lin Jian Xing could not resist a venerable’s attack.

But did that mean he had to give up?

There was no such logic in Lin Jian Xing’s heart!

If one was weak, they needed to do everything to become stronger, to become an expert. It was because they would be bullied that they had to grab every chance to resist and become stronger.

Lin Jian Xing had such thoughts and did just that.

He had already made enough mental preparation, he would bear the responsibility even if a venerable targeted him in the future.

As long as he could preserve his life, he would surrender to the venerables. He might even be lucky and get the venerable’s support, making even greater achievements!

After sending off Nine Spiritual Fairy, Lin Jian Xing did not return to the headquarters but continued to head north and entered Northern Plains.

He turned invisible and flew rapidly, soon arriving at Flower Forest Forbidden Land.

Flower Forest Forbidden Land was one of the ten great fierce areas in Northern Plains and was home to countless mushrooms. These mushrooms were as large as trees and the huge number of them formed a vast forest.

All kinds of flowers bloomed in the forest, their aroma permeated the surroundings and were dense to the point of forming fog.

Every full moon, the fragrance of the flowers would condense into water droplets that flowed to the surroundings, nourishing the mushroom trees and strengthening them further.

Similar to all the fierce areas, countless desolate beast groups lived here including many immemorial desolate beasts and plants.

Zuo Ye Hui had been hiding in the depths of Flower Forest Forbidden Land over these days.

It was a legendary immemorial desolate beast, it was much easier and more suitable for it enter and live in fierce areas than Gu Immortals.

Zuo Ye Hui naturally had its plans for hiding in the Flower Forest.

Its goal was You Tian Guang who was imprisoned by Longevity Heaven. It wanted to save the latter!

Flower Forest Forbidden Land was a fierce area in Northern Plains that could not only hide him but was also nearest to Longevity Heaven.

“I am going now, the following plan will depend on you two. Don’t think of running away, you are both struck by my method and are not of Huang Jin bloodline, who will save you?” Zuo Ye Hui did not forget to warn Lu Qing Ming and Su Guang before leaving.

These two Gu Immortals were really unlucky.

They had wanted to escape Northern Plains and were heading towards Western Desert when they were caught by Zuo Ye Hui midway and were brought to Flower Forest Forbidden Land.

The environment in a fierce area was extremely dangerous, they could not escape with their strength. If not for Zuo Ye Hui’s protection, they would not be able to survive even a day in this fierce area.

“We won’t dare, our lives depend on you, lord. We will definitely use all our strength for the plan.” Lu Qing Ming quickly replied.

Zuo Ye Hui snorted coldly, its huge body suddenly turned into a puddle of dark liquid that seeped into the ground and disappeared.

Lu Qing Ming and Su Guang were helpless and could only follow Zuo Ye Hui’s instructions.

They entered an immortal formation and began to activate it.

The strength of the immortal formation began to spread to the surroundings, the whole process did not leak any aura and was silent, this was the specialty of dark path.

As time passed, many immemorial desolate beast groups in Flower Forest Forbidden Land started to get agitated. Zuo Ye Hui had even used its methods on the leaders of these beast groups without them noticing it.

Most Gu Immortals would not be able to accomplish this. Zuo Ye Hui was a dark path legendary immemorial beast, it could be considered as the number Gu cultivator in dark path in the present era and it had used all its methods for this.

Not long later, the immemorial beast groups began to roar irritatedly.

Beasts lacked wisdom, they were on guard against each other and went into conflict, thus,outbreaks started to occur.

Under the influence of the immortal formation, immemorial beast groups began to run madly with their groups. They completely disrupted the order of the whole fierce area, forming a beast tide of a grand scale.

This beast tide broke out of Flower Forest Forbidden Land’s territory and started to rush towards the nearby Huang Jin tribes.

The Huang Jin tribes were shaken and immediately asked Longevity Heaven for help.

In this situation, Lin Jian Xing arrived in the sky above Flower Forest Forbidden Land.

Chapter 2318: Giant Sun Accidentally Harms His Son

Even before the Huang Jin tribes asked for help, Longevity Heaven had already detected the commotion in Flower Forest Forbidden Land.

Bing Sai Chuan was overseeing Longevity Heaven.

He was having a discussion with Yao Huang and some of the Eight Extremities.

“The commotion in the fierce area is no small matter, we have to take care of it.”

“In my opinion, we must verify the reason for the commotion!”

“Maybe because the sun was destroyed and spectral heaven formed, it caused light path to decline and dark path to prosper. Flower Forest Forbidden Land has a dense number of dark path dao marks.”

After the discussion, Bing Sai Chuan personally moved towards the fierce area to inspect the situation while the others continued to guard Longevity Heaven.

The reason for this arrangement was because Bing Sai Chuan possessed a time path killer move that could trace an event to its source and see the truth in the past.

Longevity Heaven opened its entrance as Bing Sai Chuan moved directly to Flower Forest Forbidden Land.

Zuo Ye Hui who was already hiding in spectral heaven was near Longevity Heaven’s entrance.

it saw the entrance open and close but did not move.

The opening of the entrance was indeed an excellent chance to enter the grotto-heaven but it was too conspicuous. Even if Zuo Ye Hui had concealment methods, it was not easy to do this.

Gu Immortals were deeply concerned whenever they opened their immortal aperture. If Zuo Ye Hui entered at this time, it was simply exposing itself and looking for trouble, and it was also underestimating Bing Sai Chuan.

Zuo Ye Hui did not want to have a frontal fight.

It might be a grand legendary immemorial beast but it was nothing when compared to Longevity Heaven and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

From the start, it had not thought of forcefully intruding to save You Tian Guang.The rescue was a technical operation, if it acted rashly, it was likely to fail and even cause himself to get captured!

Zuo Ye Hui continued to hide and activate a killer move.

“This opportunity is extremely rare, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable is fighting the other three venerables and has no leisure time to split his concentration. Flower Forest Forbidden Land lured away a rank eight expert. The specific location of Longevity Heaven’s entrance is also exposed. I must make the best use of this time!”

Zuo Ye Hui and You Tian Guang had a mysterious connection.

Relying on this connection, Zuo Ye Hui’s dark path killer move gradually showed a miraculous effect.

Inside Longevity Heaven, You Tian Guang was imprisoned in Calamity Luck Altar.

Suddenly having a sensation, You Tian Guang lowered its head and looked at its heart. Shortly after, it reacted, roaring and struggling fiercely.

Calamity Luck Altar shook constantly, the Eight Extremities, who were guarding outside, saw this and quickly acted to suppress You Tian Guang.

“You Tian Guang, you have tried so many times but still haven’t realized that you can’t escape Calamity Luck Altar by yourself?”

“Surrendering to my Longevity Heaven is your only way out.”

“As long as you surrender to Longevity Heaven, you will be protected by Lord Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.”

You Tian Guang roared furiously: ”Return my light Gu!”

The Eight Extremities persuaded: ”You Tian Guang, light Gu has always been a wild Gu, it only resided in your body temporarily, how can you call it yours?”

“That’s correct. Lord Giant Sun Immortal Venerable won against two venerables and seized this Gu, it belongs to my Longevity Heaven now!”

“You should be grateful to Lord Immortal Venerable and his son, if not for them, you would have already been killed by Star Constellation or Fang Yuan.”

You Tian Guang’s aura declined rapidly from their suppression but it still shouted: ”Return my light Gu and I will consider surrendering!”

The few Eight Extremities looked at each other before shaking their heads and strengthening the suppression power of Calamity Luck Altar.

Finally, You Tian Guang exhausted all its strength and gave up with reluctance, hatred, and anger as it was suppressed.

But this time, it had a new hope.

“Brother, I am coming to save you, let’s discuss the plan first!” A lump of black liquid flowed out of You Tian Guang’s heart and turned into the appearance of a mini Zuo Ye Hui.

Zuo Ye Hui paused for a moment before continuing: ”My killer move has gone through modification and will continue to accumulate strength inside your body. When it has accumulated enough strength, you can use my strength to erupt with all your power. At that time, I will coordinate with you from outside Longevity Heaven and open a hole in Longevity Heaven!”

You Tian Guang did not feel at ease: ”Giant Sun Immortal Venerable cannot be underestimated, be careful of him, you must not trap yourself.”

Zuo Ye Hui informed You Tian Guang of the current situation.

You Tian Guang was exulted: ”The chaotic battle of four venerables will probably last for a long time. This is indeed the best time for me to escape! It is a pity that your arrangements in Flower Forest Forbidden Land only lured away Bing Sai Chuan.”

“Longevity Heaven is probably cautious because of Fang Yuan. Fang Yuan’s three clones are wreaking havoc in Central Continent and the star array calculation formation is already damaged.” Zuo Ye Hui analyzed.

The two legendary immemorial beasts conversed secretly, no one in Longevity Heaven sensed it.

Bing Sai Chuan quietly landed in Flower Forest Forbidden Land.

He searched all the way and traced the aura to its source, gradually nearing the area where Zuo Ye Hui set up the immortal formation.

“There is trouble!” Lu Qing Ming and Su Guang who were controlling the formation sensed Bing Sai Chuan early on.

Their expressions were heavy as they knew the severity of the situation.

Once they were discovered by Bing Sai Chuan, there would be no way for them to escape.

The two had thought of surrendering but they were under the control of Zuo Ye Hui’s dark path method. As long as they even tried to surrender, the dark path method would trigger and take their lives.

They two had to continue to activate the immortal formation and enlarge the scale of the beast tide, they could not stop for even a while.

Otherwise, the dark path method would similarly trigger and kill them directly.

“Zuo Ye Hui is using us as cannon fodder!”

“Sigh, I did not expect today that we will die today.”

Just as the two were in despair, the situation suddenly took a turn for the better.

“Who is it?!” Bing Sai Chuan stopped, his gaze emitting cold light as he became vigilant.

Lin Jian Xing’s mind jolted slightly.

He had come to Flower Forest Forbidden Land secretly and was concealed. His goal was to gather some precious and rare immortal materials to help him complete the sword forest killer move.

But then, the beast tide occurred.

This was a good thing for Lin Jian Xing.

The chaotic situation was much more suitable for him to look for benefits.

Lin Jian Xing entered deep inside the fierce area and ran into Bing Sai Chuan.

Although he had pseudo venerable battle strength, he was not proficient at concealment methods. Fortunately, Bing Sai Chuan looked around a few times before shaking his head.

“Maybe I was wrong?”

Bing Sai Chuan whispered softly before continuing forward while inspecting the area.

He did not notice any suspicious interference in this beast tide but he also did not find the reason for the beast tide’s outbreak.

He followed the traces to their source and gradually neared the dark path immortal formation.

Right at this time, a group of four-legged white scale snake flew over.

The white scale snakes had already turned mad, when they discovered Bing Sai Chuan, they attacked immediately without thinking.

Bing Sai Chuan’s pupils shrank and was about to kill these snakes when a ray of sword qi shot towards him from the left.

Bing Sai Chuan was not surprised and quickly acted to block the sword qi while saying to Lin Jian Xing who had revealed himself: ”Hehe, I knew there was someone there... hmm? Lin Jian Xing!”

Bing Sai Chuan recognized Lin Jian Xing.

After the five Heavenly Court immortals lost to Lin Jian Xing, his appearance was already spread widely, Bing Sai Chuan naturally knew of him.

Bing Sai Chuan’s brows furrowed tightly: ”Lin Jian Xing, do you want to stand against my Longevity Heaven?”

Lin Jian Xing frowned but he looked at the group of white scale snakes: ”These white scale snakes’ tongues are sword path immortal materials that I require. I came for them this time. Bing Sai Chuan, I seek your understanding.”

“Is that so?” Bing Sai Chuan was doubtful but Lin Jian Xing was a pseudo venerable after all, he did not want to start a fight rashly, ”These white scale snakes’ tongues are indeed rare resources. But don’t worry, Lin Jian Xing, Longevity Heaven has many of them in our storage. If you are interested, I am willing to deepen our friendship and gift them to you.”

“Oh?” Lin Jian Xing raised his brows slightly. He was just about to consider when a large group of immemorial desolate beast rushed towards this area.

The scene became chaotic immediately.

The white scale snakes were only ancient desolate beasts, they were not the match of these immemorial desolate beasts. But it was too late to escape now, their formation was scattered by the immemorial desolate beasts.

Lin Jian Xing attacked these immemorial desolate beasts and retrieved as many white scale snake tongues as he could.

Bing Sai Chuan observed from the side while urgently contacting Longevity Heaven to mobilize the Harem Palaces of Northern Plains and Western Desert.

He would not easily believe Lin Jian Xing’s one-sided statement, it was much safer to use Immortal Gu Houses to face a pseudo venerable.

Back then, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable gathered beauties and constructed five harem palaces in the five regions which were all Immortal Gu Houses.

A few members of the Eight Extremities received the command and immediately flew out of Longevity Heaven with the Immortal Gu Houses.

Zuo Ye Hui was doubtful and happy at this sight.

In fact, Lu Qing Ming and Su Guang still being concealed at this point was already beyond Zuo Ye Hui’s expectations.

Right now, Longevity Heaven sent two Immortal Gu Houses and several Gu Immortals, their direction was clearly Flower Forest Forbidden Land; Zuo Ye Hui could not understand what was going on.

But no matter what, his situation had become better than before.

After a while, You Tian Guang roared fiercely, erupting with the accumulated dark path strength and catching the Eight Extremities, who were guarding this place, off-guard.

You Tian Guang seized this chance and attacked. After ten breaths of time of stalemate, it was able to charge out of Calamity Luck Altar.

It did not escape immediately, instead, it followed its sense towards a secluded area.

The Eight Extremities left behind were pale with fright: ”Oh no! That is where our prince is resting!!”

Yao Huang had already come out of Blood Sea and wanted to stop You Tian Guang, but he was a step late.

He watched with the newly arrived Mao Li Qiu as You Tian Guang took Light Emperor and left.

Light Emperor was nourishing rank nine light Gu with his body. Even under such a drastic situation, he was still like a statue with his eyes closed as if he had lost all perception towards the outside world.

“Don’t provoke me or I may crush him to death!” You Tian Guang roared loudly, the encircling Gu Immortals hesitated and were in a dilemma.

“Don’t kill him, otherwise when Lord Giant Sun Immortal Venerable returns, you will definitely die!”

“You Tian Guang, everything can be discussed, please calm down.”

“Quick, call Bing Sai Chuan and the others to come back.”

While the Longevity Heaven Gu Immortals were panicking, You Tian Guang made a move. Zuo Ye Hui also came out of hiding in the outside world, the two had a high degree of coordination, directly tearing open a hole in Longevity Heaven.

This hole was not large but You Tian Guang had an amazing method.

He first swallowed Light Emperor before transforming his body into a lump of light that forced its way through the hole and into the outside world.

After appearing in the outside world, the light changed back into You Tian Guang.

Longevity Heaven’s Gu Immortals gave chase and arrived outside, they saw You Tian Guang and their expressions turned unsightly when the saw Zuo Ye Hui as well.

“We fell for their trap!” Yao Huang stomped his foot in anger.

After Bing Sai Chuan received the news, he looked at Lin Jian Xing with narrowed eyes: ”So it was like this, Brother Lin actually joined hands with Zuo Ye Hui.”

“What do you mean?” Lin Jian Xing was baffled.

In the battlefield over the heaven path dream realms.

“What?” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had been concentrating on fighting Fang Yuan when he heard this bad news.

“This situation seems to be created by my nothing is certain except success killer move!” The vague luck path sensation stupefied Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable wanted to explain the situation to himself but he was not able to!

“My killer move should... not have a problem, right?”

“I rarely used it in my previous life.”

“I have modified this move recently, indeed... there should be... probably... not much of an issue.”

“Giant Sun, what happened?” As the number one person in wisdom path, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was very perceptive towards the changes of emotions, she asked directly.

“Ah, nothing, there is no issue.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable shook his hands repeatedly while feeling bitter inwardly.

Chapter 2319: Star Constellation Admits Defeat

Heaven and earth was torn apart like a huge opened mouth. Endless lightning exploded and resisted the fierce tornadoes.

Meng Qiu Zhen floated in the air and observed the land.

“Lightning, come!” He shouted and at the next moment, tens of thousands of lightning balls fell from the sky and collided with the tornadoes, causing huge explosions.

Ten or so tornadoes were destroyed but there were still about a hundred tornadoes which connected the small world’s sky and ground like giant pillars.

Meng Qiu Zhen gritted his teeth as he recognized the crucial point: He had to find the location of this dream realm’s land spirit as soon as possible and attack it. Otherwise, with so many tornadoes, even if he destroyed all of them, he would have used all his strength which was detrimental to his future dream realm explorations.

With the main body’s protection, after experiencing that thrilling moment before, Meng Qiu Zhen did not run into anymore mishaps.

He continued to explore the heaven path dream realms, not only raising his heaven path attainment level greatly but also raising his strength in the dream realm immortal aperture. He became a heavenly spirit and his methods were at a completely different level than before.

Meng Qiu Zhen could now control heavenly power and produce strength similar to calamities and tribulations!

Moreover, he also found that heaven path dream realms could annex each other, constantly bringing him risks as well as opportunities in the explorations.

“Ice, come!” Meng Qiu Zhen seized the timing, his two small hands spread apart and pressed down.

Hailstones rained down heavily from the sky.

The hailstones continued to grow bigger every moment, some of them were even as large as a hill in just a few breaths of time.

These hailstones fell on the tornadoes and were rapidly swept away.

The dark-green tornadoes were soon covered by a layer of bluish white frost and their speed fell sharply.

“So it was here.” Meng Qiu Zhen succeeded in weakening the enemy and discovered that there was a white feather flying fish hiding in the leftmost tornado.

This white feather flying fish was the heavenly spirit of the other dream realm immortal aperture!

Heaven path dream realms could annex each other, this current manifestation was the result of the two dream realm immortal apertures annexing each other. As the heavenly spirit of a dream realm immortal aperture, Meng Qiu Zhen had to lead his dream realm immortal aperture to suppress the other side’s dream realm immortal aperture and even annex it.

There was a crucial step in this, that was to find the other side’s heavenly spirit and exterminate it.

“Die!” Meng Qiu Zhen used one method after the other, the flying fish heavenly spirit got dizzy from seeing all the attacks.

Lighting flashed, thunder rumbled, storm brewed, meteors fell, and lava gushed out; all kinds of attacks were thrown out before the flying fish heavenly spirit was finally exterminated.

Without the control of the heavenly spirit, the tornadoes still existed but were moving disorderly instead of being orderly like before, immediately becoming non-threatening.

At the same time, Meng Qiu Zhen’s dream realm immortal aperture also quickened the pace of annexing the enemy dream realm immortal aperture.

With the flying fish heavenly spirit dead, it was like the opposing army’s commander was beheaded, they would fall into disorder and be defeated no matter how strong they were.

Meng Qiu Zhen followed up his victory and finally expanded his dream realm immortal aperture by another area.

“There is a huge rise in wind path dao marks, the outcome is pretty good. Hmm? Another dream realm immortal aperture is coming close.” Meng Qiu Zhen had not even rested when he saw an indistinct red shadow appear outside the dream realm immortal aperture.

The indistinct red shadow covered the sky and ground, obscuring the sun and moon. A huge explosion resounded as it collided with Meng Qiu Zhen’s dream realm immortal aperture.

The immortal aperture’s boundary was broken as the two dream realm immortal apertures connected to each other and started a brutal annexing process.

“Wait, this heavenly spirit is different!” Meng Qiu Zhen’s expression changed slightly as he discovered that the enemy was extremely shrewd and could adapt to the situation easily with plenty of methods that were not fewer than Meng Qiu Zhen’s.

“Don’t tell me...”

Profound Literature grotto-heaven.

Qi tides surged and formed tens of thousands of qi monsters everywhere, forming a huge calamity.

A large number of mortals in Profound Literature grotto-heaven became corpses under the rampage of the qi monsters.

“Damn it!”

“We must persevere!”

“These qi monsters are coming endlessly, when will it stop?”

The Gu Immortals of Profound Literature grotto-heaven used all their strength to defend, Old Immortal Hua Yu personally entered the battle and was barely able to hold the situation.

This was not a heavenly tribulation or earthly calamity, it was the qi path killer move that Qi Sea Ancestor used to attack the star array calculation formation.

The star array calculation formation had a large number of formation cores. After a number of the formation cores’ Immortal Gu were destroyed by Fang Yuan’s three clones, the formation bases were exposed.

These formation bases were Profound Literature grotto-heaven, Skeleton grotto-heaven, and so on.

As long as these grotto-heavens were destroyed, the star array calculation formation would lose its foundation and collapse completely.

“If we had known this earlier, why would we try all means possible to defect?”

“Sigh, it is already too late to say this. We can only hope that Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable has enough methods to protect our homeland.”

These grotto-heaven Gu Immortals were feeling regret to some extent.

Rumble!

An explosion rang, qi currents rampaged like ten thousand horses as Qi Sea Ancestor gradually appeared inside Skeleton grotto-heaven.

Granny Skeleton was in despair but before she even asked for help, many rank eight Heavenly Court Gu Immortals arrived in Skeleton grotto-heaven in Immortal Gu Houses.

Without any delay, a huge battle erupted!

Heaven and earth shook, qi sea rose, golden lights flew, jade water floated in the sky... a large number of killer moves were activated, their aftershock creating huge casualties.

Immortal killer move — Unlimited Qi Sea!

Qi Sea Ancestor continued to gather his momentum before finally using this move.

With one move, heaven and earth was overturned, several Immortal Gu Houses of Heavenly Court were damaged heavily, one even crumbled apart.

Qin Ding Ling and the rest coughed blood repeatedly from the serious injuries.

“Hold on!” Qin Ding Ling shouted.

“Watch this!” Che Wei tried bravely to use offense against offense.

Qi Sea Ancestor was struck by his killer move and suffered some injuries.

Immortal killer move — Qi Jue Revival!

At the next moment, a large number of qi path immortal materials was expended as Qi Sea Ancestor recovered rapidly.

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals turned pale.

“Let’s end this.”

Qi Sea Ancestor gave a shout and activated the killer move, Hu elevation!

Towering and terrifying qi pillars shot out, directly piercing through Skeleton grotto-heaven.

Granny Skeleton’s eyes were wide open and had no time to dodge, she was annihilated by the qi pillar with not even a small piece of her remaining.

Skeleton grotto-heaven was heavily damaged and started to produce the winds of assimilation.

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals left from the large hole while Qi Sea Ancestor gave chase.

Star Constellation’s will saw this from inside Embroidered Tower and was about to make a move when Zhan Bu Du charged inside the formation space.

“It is here after all!” Wu Shuai was happy.

He controlled ants to infiltrate the depths of the star array calculation formation and forcibly drilled a pathway from which Zhan Bu Du squeezed inside.

The Gu Immortals inside the formation space were mostly from ten great ancient sects; although they were all elites, they were still far from reaching the level of Heavenly Court’s members.

Even the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals could not easily fight a pseudo venerable, let alone them.

Zhan Bu Du was like a tiger entering a herd of sheep, blood started to flow instantly.

Star Constellation’s will heaved a sigh, she could only give up on targeting Qi Sea Ancestor and activated Embroidered Tower to block Zhan Bu Du.

After a period of stalemate, Fang Yuan’s three clones finally created an opening and started destroying the star array calculation formation as easily as cutting bamboo.

Heavenly Court was beaten back again and again without getting any chance to stabilize their footing.

This news immediately reached Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable sighed as she activated two human path killer moves.

One was heroes among people and the other was hope of the people.

Divine Emperor City which was the largest human vein node of Central Continent released countless white light. The countless specks and lumps of light were like lanterns or candles.

These lights moved like fish or birds returning to their homes, landing in all of the Gu Immortals inside the star array calculation formation, forming a dense white radiance.

The white radiance started to shrink while the Gu Immortals’ auras started to grow.

Just like in the fate war, they received a huge amplification once again.

“As expected, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used this move, it hasn’t crossed Lord Alliance Leader’s calculations.” Lu Wei Yin was watching Divine Emperor City from some distance with a moved expression.

“She is using the same ability again, it means she ran out of tricks.” Shen Shang smiled lightly as he attacked Divine Emperor City with Lu Wei Yin.

Genesis Lotus’ will and Qing Chou were guarding Divine Emperor City. As they were attacked by two experts, they could only stop supporting the two human path killer moves and defend themselves.

Spectral heaven battlefield.

The white radiance formed from the human path killer moves similarly covered Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

The two received the amplification, their strength rose by a huge degree!

“As expected of human path methods, even a venerable like me can benefit from it.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable clicked his tongue in praise.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable frowned: ”There are almost no heaven path dream realms left, we’ve lost this battle!”

Chapter 2320: Like It Was Nothing!

The battle over the heaven path dream realms was started by Fang Yuan.

In this battle, Fang Yuan revealed new killer moves like Arrival of Dragon Snake with Dust Fog and Explosive Soul Wind, Shocking Departure of Year Dream Wave and Dang Hun Sound, and heavenly ghost concealment.

Seven kills rainbow, sword tongue dragon soul, and other killer moves were greatly improved, and there were also obscured heavenly secret and heavenly web protection veil that was supporting Fang Yuan secretly.

Thus, Fang Yuan gained the upper hand in the battle, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had no choice but to join hands to match him.

However, because Fang Yuan needed to protect Meng Qiu Zhen, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable who had chaotic intent dispels dream killer move gradually gained the initiative.

At the same time, Fang Yuan’s strength made Giant Sun Immortal Venerable wary. No matter how Fang Yuan tried to persuade him, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was firm on stopping Fang Yuan from obtaining the heaven path dream realms.

As a result, Fang Yuan ordered his subordinates to attack Central Continent’s important areas to harass Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable saw through Fang Yuan’s plan and did not return to defend Central Continent.

To continue hiding his strength and pretend to have a shortage of immortal essence, Fang Yuan angered Spectral Soul Demon Venerable and lured him into battle. He used heavenly ghost concealment killer move to become half an alliance mate of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

Fang Yuan’s scheme succeeded!

Because of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable disrupting the situation, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable were not able to emit enough pressure on Fang Yuan. But conversely, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was continued to be interrupted by Fang Yuan and had no more opportunities to harm Meng Qiu Zhen. Even when Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used two powerful human path killer moves, it was hard to change the battle situation.

The battle situation was in a stalemate, and as time passed, heaven path dream realms annexed each other and were mostly absorbed by Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan’s gains in this battle far surpassed Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

On the contrary, among the two venerables; one lost his eldest son and rank nine light Gu while the other’s painstakingly created the star array calculation formation was almost destroyed, over ten Central Continent Gu Immortals were killed and even Heavenly Court’s Gu Immortals were in a dangerous situation.

This made Star Constellation Immortal Venerable come to a complete realization, Fang Yuan had won a huge victory in this battle. No matter how miserable he looked now, he was the person who reaped the most benefits!

“Whether Fang Yuan still has trump cards or not, or if he really lacks immortal essence, at the end of it, the crucial factor of this battle was Spectral Soul Demon Venerable!”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable looked at the heavily injured Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, she was reluctant, furious, and also helpless.

Since long ago, she had wanted to get rid of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable but never succeeded.

There was a good opportunity before but Fang Yuan disturbed them. It was mainly thanks to Fang Yuan that Spectral Soul Demon Venerable could still stay alive.

In this battle, Fang Yuan used Spectral Soul Demon Venerable to obtain huge gains, this proved how far-sighted he was.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s injuries were mostly received in place of Fang Yuan. He had less than one thousand arms left, his enormous body had shrunk by sixty percent, and even his roar sounded hoarse and soft.

“Maybe, this is a chance to get rid of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable!” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had this thought.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was a huge obstruction.

Although Star Constellation Immortal Venerable controlled Spectral Soul Demon Venerable before, she was much clearer than others that Spectral Soul Demon Venerable who was filled with heaven’s will could not longer be controlled by her.

Sometimes, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable admired Fang Yuan’s craftiness and sinisterness. He was able to successfully turn Spectral Soul Demon Venerable into half an alliance mate.

Although Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had lost his senses, under Fang Yuan’s heavenly ghost concealment killer move, he was even more dependable than ordinary alliance mates and was also easier to be made use of.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable then looked at Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Although the two venerables had allied, there was always deep vigilance between Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and her.

Looking back at this battle, even though Giant Sun Immortal Venerable used his full strength, it was of little effect on Fang Yuan, it instead cost Central Continent a lot.

The comparison showed a stark contrast.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would rather have the irrational Spectral Soul Demon Venerable as her alliance mate than be allies with a sane Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

But if she wanted to get rid of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable now, she still had to get Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s help.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable immediately transmitted her voice: ”Giant Sun, there is no need to care about Fang Yuan now. Let’s join hands to get rid of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable! As you can see from the current situation, we cannot let this venerable continue living.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable deeply agreed with these words!

He felt that they were not able to deal with Fang Yuan mainly because of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable. These two’s combination truly gave him a headache.

Naturally, Fang Yuan could ’ally’ with Spectral Soul Demon Venerable because of heavenly ghost concealment killer move. As long as this move was broken, it was the same as breaking the alliance between Fang Yuan and Spectral Soul.

But Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was also aware that even if he broke it this time, Fang Yuan could continue to modify it.

Fang Yuan was a refinement path venerable, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not think highly of his modification abilities before. But after this battle, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable who was baptized by killer moves like Shocking Departure of Year Dream Wave and Dang Hun Sound and Arrival of Dragon Snake with Dust Fog and Explosive Soul Wind changed his perception fully.

Right now, in his opinion, Fang Yuan’s wisdom path attainment was already above him. Even when looking at all the venerables, besides Limitless Demon Venerable, Fang Yuan was right below Star Constellation Immortal Venerable!

So, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not want to play the pointless game of unraveling, modifying, then unraveling again before modifying again with Fang Yuan.

“It is a good idea indeed to kill Spectral Soul Demon Venerable! We can end this problem once and for all, Fang Yuan will have no alliance mate left.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable transmitted his reply to Star Constellation.

“Moreover, Fang Yuan lacks immortal essence right now, but we are different. It will be much more difficult for him to protect Spectral Soul Demon Venerable now. If he exhausts all his strength to protect the latter, he may land in a predicament with just a slight carelessness. At that time, we can then target him and even create an opportunity to behead this Heaven Refining Demon Venerable!”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was not as optimistic as Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, she replied: ”Fang Yuan will never throw himself in a predicament to protect Spectral Soul.”

The two venerables reached a consensus and focused all their attacks on Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

“They made this decision indeed.” Fang Yuan revealed a troubled expression but was getting increasingly excited inwardly.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable fought fiercely with the two venerables, and with Fang Yuan’s help from the side, both sides would suffer.

But in the end, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable would probably die.

After all, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was filled with heaven’s will. He did not have any sanity and used immortal killer moves randomly, it was really too much of a disadvantage.

But like this, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would also be weakened greatly.

This was a great opportunity to get rid of two venerables!

As long as they did not escape to their headquarters, Fang Yuan had certainty to kill one of them with his full strength.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable wanted to kill Spectral Soul Demon Venerable but Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was thinking of a chance to get rid of Fang Yuan while Fang Yuan was also plotting to get rid of the two.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was attacked by the full strength of the two venerables, his injuries continued to become more severe. Many of his large black arms were broken, leaving behind only two-three hundred.

“Go!” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable suddenly threw a golden meteor.

The meteor struck Spectral Soul Demon Venerable and destroyed one of his heads.

Out of his three heads, only one remained now. He was forced into a desperate situation with danger everywhere around him but Fang Yuan still attacked steadily, deliberately maintaining the frequency of his attacks.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable roared furiously, a large blue fire burned on his body.

But this fire was not burning hot, instead, it let out a strong chill.

The temperature dropped rapidly.

Rank nine fire Gu finally could not sit still, it felt the danger to its host’s life and finally used its strength!

It was rank nine after all, all three venerables retreated, even Fang Yuan who had heavenly ghost concealment was the same.

Fang Yuan relied on this killer move to deceive Spectral Soul Demon Venerable but he could not deceive rank nine fire Gu. After all, it was a Gu worm and not a soul beast.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable remained still. The blue fire quickly spread, forcing the three venerables to continue retreating.

The fire expanded towards the heaven path dream realms. The dream realms shrunk rapidly and were actually being burned!

Fang Yuan’s eyes shone with a sharp light as he thought: “<<The Legends of Ren Zu>> stated that dream realms are restrained by fire Gu, looks like it is true.”

He felt that it was a pity.

While fighting with the venerables, his heaven path attainment level had already advanced from grandmaster to great grandmaster level.

Moreover, he had not just stepped into great grandmaster, his accumulation was already deep and robust.

If Fang Yuan absorbed all of the heaven path dream realms here, he might even be able to advance to supreme grandmaster level. Even if he could not, he had a high possibility of becoming a quasi-supreme grandmaster.

However, most of the remaining heaven path dream realms were destroyed by fire Gu.

“This is an opportunity, Giant Sun!” Looking at this scene, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable started preparing chaotic intent dispels dream killer move.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not protect Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, instead, charging towards the heaven path dream realms.

Fang Yuan immediately fell into a dilemma of advancing or retreating!

Within the spark of a moment, he made a decision, he gave up on Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and pounced upon Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was blocked by Fang Yuan, the two venerables fought fiercely.

In this process, the heaven path dream realms were burned by the fire, there was almost none left. Be it Fairy Zi Wei, Ying Wu Xie or Meng Qiu Zhen, they were all burning!

While Fang Yuan obstructed Giant Sun, he was also getting closer to the heaven path dream realms.

Seeing this, he immediately gave up on Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and went in the direction of his dream path clone.

Meng Qiu Zhen’s eyes were closed and would not wake up in a short while.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable saw Fang Yuan ignoring him and leaving, he shouted in fury: ”Fang Yuan, such audacity! I will make you pay.”

At the next moment, hundreds of golden meteors shot out together. Their power was so terrifying that even heaven and earth changed colors.

At the same time, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable finally finished preparing her killer move and activated chaotic intent dispels dream.

She directly attacked Meng Qiu Zhen.

Bam bam bam bam!

The golden meteors struck Fang Yuan and Meng Qiu Zhen, explosions rang continuously, shaking the world.

Terrifying air waves rampaged in every direction.

The golden lights dissipated, Fang Yuan and Meng Qiu Zhen were moving down extremely quickly.

“Huh?!” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s eyes almost popped out, Fang Yuan was not even injured at all.

What kind of defensive killer move was this!

“Oh no!” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s expression changed greatly.

Fang Yuan was headed towards Central Continent.

As for Meng Qiu Zhen, he was already awake and had activated dream armor Gu to protect himself. At the same time, his body was covered by a layer of rippling reverse flow protection seal.

Through Fang Yuan’s modification, reverse flow protection seal could help others as well and was not limited to himself.

With two layers of defense, Meng Qiu Zhen, just like the main body, took on Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s killer move like it was nothing.

Chapter 2321: Qi Sea’s Divine Might

“What a scheme, Fang Yuan!”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s expression looked unsightly.

Fang Yuan’s move was extremely ingenious.

He took Meng Qiu Zhen to Central Continent, forcing Star Constellation Immortal Venerable into a dilemma.

If Star Constellation Immortal Venerable continued to fight Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, Fang Yuan would take the chance to open his immortal aperture and put Meng Qiu Zhen inside before wreaking havoc in Central Continent.

Heavenly Court was already in a dangerous situation, the star array calculation formation was in an extremely damaged state with eighty percent of it destroyed. Divine Emperor City was being attacked by Shen Shang and Lu Wei Yin, it was already showing signs of being unable to maintain the two human path killer moves.

If Fang Yuan attacked in this situation, he would definitely create an unimaginable massacre in Central Continent and Heavenly Court!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was worthy of being the number one person in wisdom path, she made a decision almost immediately.

She sighed and said to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable: ”Fang Yuan is extremely crafty, he wants to use this way to protect Spectral Soul Demon Venerable! We cannot fall for his trap! I will go chase him and not let him get any chance to put his clone back in his aperture. Giant Sun, I hope you can kill Spectral Soul Demon Venerable!”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable knew in his heart: Star Constellation Immortal Venerable clearly knew this was Fang Yuan’s scheme but she had to fall into it. It was true that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was going to make things difficult for Fang Yuan, but it was even more true that she was going back to defend Central Continent.

But Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not argue.

If it were him, he would also be willing to fall into the scheme to protect his Huang Jin bloodline.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable nodded, saying decisively: ”Today, either Spectral Soul Demon Venerable or Fang Yuan must die!”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s cooperation made Star Constellation Immortal Venerable let out a sigh of relief.

At the crucial moment, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable made a clear and sensible decision!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable immediately chased after Fang Yuan.

Within the star array calculation formation’s inner space.

Demon Judgment Board was sent flying.

Inside Demon Judgment Board, Gu Yue Fang Zheng and Red Heart Traveler were sweating heavily, their faces turned pale with a sense of trepidation.

At this moment, the previous owner and the current owner of Demon Judgment Board had joined hands!

But they were still in a disadvantage.

What forced Demon Judgment Board to retreat time and again?

“Careful, he is coming again!” Red Heart Traveler who was mainly responsible for controlling Demon Judgment Board reminded suddenly.

Zhan Bu Du’s cape fluttered fiercely as he flew closer.

After he activated incomplete freedom transformation, he was a genuine human-shaped beast. Even Demon Judgment Board was not able to properly take a hit from him.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng received Red Heart Traveler’s reminder, he felt a quiver and shouted frantically: ”Let’s try again!”

Demon Judgment Board let out waves of blood light.

The blood light was like a tide that quickly spread thousands of feet. The scarlet-red blood light contained endless coldness.

Zhan Bu Du had to charge into the blood light to near Demon Judgment Board. His movement inevitably slowed down.

“This move again.” Zhan Bu Du’s expression turned somewhat strange.

He had already been obstructed by this blood path killer move three times in a row.

Demon Judgment Board used the time when Zhan Bu Du had slowed down to retreat to a safe distance.

And the one who accomplished this was Gu Yue Fang Zheng.

Red Heart Traveler looked at Gu Yue Fang Zheng with gratitude and admiration. Gu Yue Fang Zheng had activated blood turns cold killer move but he had connected this move to Demon Judgment Board so closely that it felt like blood turns cold was Demon Judgment Board’s killer move.

This was an extremely ingenious pioneering work, none of the past owners of Demon Judgment Board accomplished this.

Speaking of which, Red Heart Traveler was Gu Yue Fang Zheng’s master.

But he did not accept the disciple voluntarily, it was mainly because of the orders from higher-ups and his own benefits. So, Red Heart Traveler’s perception of Gu Yue Fang Zheng had always been poor and did not have much affection for this disciple.

But now, Red Heart Traveler’s impression of Gu Yue Fang Zheng underwent a huge change.

“It was not a mistake to hand Demon Judgment Board over to you. Fang Zheng, you have to work harder in the future.” Red Heart Traveler encouraged.

“Oh, yes, I will engrave master’s words in my heart.” Gu Yue Fang Zheng was somewhat surprised before saying with a sigh, ”I came in touch with the essence of painting path when I entered derivation formation, which allowed me to modify blood turns cold killer move. Its might is amplified through Demon Judgment Board and is able to freeze the blood of rank eight Gu Immortal experts and kill them. But against Zhan Bu Du, it can only obstruct him for a short while.”

Red Heart Traveler shook his head, advising: ”It is not that you are not excellent but the enemy is too strong. He... is one of the strongest clones of Heaven Refining Demon Venerable after all!”

When he heard the mention of his big brother Gu Yue Fang Yuan, Fang Zheng heaved a deep sigh.

“Alright, we must keep on pestering Zhan Bu Du and not let him destroy the whole formation space easily.” Red Heart Traveler could not hide his worries when he said this, ”Sigh, if we really were to talk of it, Heaven Refining Demon Venerable’s strongest clone is Qi Sea Ancestor. I hope Lady Qin Ding Ling can stall him.”

Profound Literature grotto-heaven.

The star array calculation formation’s bases were set up in the two heavens’ grotto-heavens; right now, there were almost none of these grotto-heavens remaining.

Profound Literature grotto-heaven was the last pillar remaining!

Qi currents gushed out like an ocean swarming the sky as Qi Sea Ancestor who was standing high in the sky looked down at everyone.

Qi Sea Ancestor, Duke Mei, Duke Tong, and the rest were either controlling Immortal Gu Houses or floating alone in the air as they looked up at Qi Sea Ancestor with an extremely solemn expression.

In this fight, Qi Sea Ancestor showed the strongest battle strength among all the existing pseudo venerables!

Especially Hu elevation, once it was activated, it could forcibly break a grotto-heaven and no one was able to block it.

Be it Qin Ding Ling’s luck path, Che Wei’s weapon path, or the senior Heavenly Court experts like Duke Mei and Duke Tong fighting without caring for their lives, or even the continuous harassment by experts like Zhou Xiong Xin and Nine Spiritual Fairy, they could not stop Qi Sea Ancestor from destroying the star array calculation formation.

Immortal killer move — Nine Essence Jade Dew Pill.

Ruan Dan was constantly activating pill path killer moves to heal the Heavenly Court immortals.

He also had a move called life sustaining small revival pill which could forcibly prolong the life of others if they were hit by a fatal attack.

These were the gains he made in derivation formation.

If not for Ruan Dan’s spectacular performance in this battle, Heavenly Court’s Gu Immortals could not have lasted for so long.

Be it Ruan Dan or other Heavenly Court Gu Immortals, all of them had made progress. However, Qi Sea Ancestor had become much stronger, almost comparable to Duke Long at his final moment in the fate war!

Qi currents billowed as they turned into tens of thousands of giant dragons. They then dispersed and attacked Profound Literature grotto-heaven from all directions, ignoring Heavenly Court’s immortals.

Old Immortal Hua Yu cried out in sadness: ”Lord Fang Yuan, are you really going to exterminate everyone?!”

His tears started falling.

Duke Tong shouted: ”Everyone, don’t be shaken, don’t risk yourselves in saving the mortals. This demon is trying to use our sympathy to influence our rational decision-making. Once our forces are split, we will definitely fall apart in his hands!”

“It is our turn now.” Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch suddenly transmitted his voice to Shabi Ninety-five.

“Master, you want to use that move? But we are not proficient in it yet.”

“There is no other option, we need to give it a try. We must pressure and disturb Qi Sea Ancestor; otherwise, if he gets a chance, he will use Hu elevation killer move again.” Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch activated the killer move.

Shabi Ninety-five took a deep breath and followed up by activating its Gu worms.

Their aura linked together; Shabi Ninety-five turned into a vast lump of qi that poured into Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch.

Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch who had a round head and large ears breathed in the vast qi through his nose and mouth, his body expanding rapidly.

When he absorbed all the qi in his body, he transformed into a huge giant.

The giant Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch slammed into the sky-covering qi sea, stirring up the boundless qi currents; Qi Sea Ancestor’s body shook and almost lost control of the qi sea.

Inside the qi sea, the giant Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch started sucking in the qi currents crazily.

The qi sea’s size continued to shrink.

“We need to act fast.”

“Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch is using Shabi Ninety-five’s special characteristic to absorb all the foreign qi. He cannot hold on for long, once the absorbed qi currents reach the limit, he will explode and die!”

Heavenly Court Gu Immortals knew the details of this move and acted quickly.

Qi Sea Ancestor was besieged from all sides, he pushed his palms to raise a thousand feet tall qi wall to stop Heavenly Court’s attacks.

He then slashed down with one arm; qi blades appeared from thin air and cut Duke Tong and Nine Spiritual Fairy, making them cough blood and retreat.

Qi currents became vast and grand, Qi Sea Ancestor was about to continue his attack but Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch started absorbing without any regards for his life; the qi currents became listless again.

Qi Sea Ancestor snorted coldly, using yin-yang great killer hands to send Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch flying like a ball.

He used divine flick to flick at Qin Ding Ling, Che Wei, Old Immortal Hua Yu, and Zhou Xiong Xin, easily forcing them back.

Jun Shen Guang was extremely fast and sent a killer move at Qi Sea Ancestor again but was blocked by Qi Sea Ancestor’s defensive methods.

Immortal killer move — Orchid Breath.

Qi Sea Ancestor’s injuries were healed rapidly.

Immortal killer move — Qi Engulfing Mountains and Rivers!

This was a killer move within Primordial Origin true inheritance, it was modified by Qi Sea Ancestor and had its activation speed increased by more than twice.

Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch, Duke Tong, Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch, and the rest who were still counterattacking shook intensely and fell from the sky.

In the chaotic battle, Wan Zi Hong, Prince Feng Xian, Bai Cang Shui, and Uncle Feng occupied the east, south, north, and west directions, trapping Qi Sea Ancestor at the center.

Immortal killer move — Earth Water Wood Fire Four Elements Shifting Formation!

This was not an ordinary killer move but an ancient battle formation. This formation required four rank eight Gu Immortals, there could not be one more or one less.

Not only this, the four Gu Immortals had to cultivate earth path, water path, wood path, and fire path respectively.

The killer move activated successfully. Wan Zi Hong, Prince Feng Xian, Bai Cang Shui, and Uncle Feng were covered in armor that shone with green, red, black, or yellow radiance.

The four colors spread quickly and linked together, showing a sign of transforming into a battlefield killer move!

“Hmm?” Qi Sea Ancestor’s expression shook slightly as he revealed a trace of admiration.

This move was a new innovation and was already vaguely reaching a whole new realm.

It was not only an ancient battle formation but also a battlefield killer move!

“We must trap him!”

“We cannot relax.”

“Success depends on this!!”

The Heavenly Court immortals roused themselves.

Qi Sea Ancestor laughed heartily: ”It is a good move indeed.”

The moment he finished speaking, a figure descended from the sky.

The immortals’ expressions changed.

Chapter 2322: Star Constellation’s Scheme

Just as Qi Sea Ancestor was about to be trapped by the Earth Water Wood Fire Four Elements Shifting Formation, a rank eight Gu Immortal came charging.

The immortals saw the person, he had a tall and fit stature with a high nose bridge, there were golden dragon scales on his body, he had a pair of topaz-like dragon pupils, there was also a pair of golden coral-like dragon horns on his head. He looked like a peerless hero.

He was one of the three main clones of Fang Yuan, dragonman Wu Shuai!

The moment Wu Shuai landed in Profound Literature grotto-heaven, two Heavenly Court members, Fairy Maiden Soul and Golden Hooped Great Immortal, arrived closely behind.

Wu Shuai had been fighting with them before but had not completely gotten away from them.

Be it Qi Sea Ancestor, Zhan Bu Du or Wu Shuai, they had all made a breakthrough in their strength. Qi Sea Ancestor’s strength increased to the level of Duke Long at his final moments; Zhan Bu Du increased the number of Gu worms he used and his methods became more comprehensive. As for Wu Shuai, he had only been at the level of a Heavenly Court Gu Immortal, but now, his strength surpassed two Heavenly Court rank eights.

“If this continues, Wu Shuai will definitely become a pseudo venerable one day!”

“We must stop Wu Shuai, don’t let him save Qi Sea Ancestor!!”

Heavenly Court Gu Immortal Jun Shen Guang was the first to move, followed by Nine Spiritual Fairy, Duke Mei, and Duke Tong.

Wu Shuai was attacked by six Heavenly Court Gu Immortals, his situation instantly turning dangerous.

He could only choose to protect himself first; countless ants wrapped around him layer upon layer, no matter how many were destroyed, they would be replenished immediately as if they were infinitely spawning.

“Open up.” Qi Sea Ancestor’s sleeves fluttered wildly as a thousand feet qi current rose.

The four Gu Immortals who formed the Four Elements Shifting Formation had a great change in their expressions, they felt they were like mortals lying on the body of an evil dragon.

The four Gu Immortals maintained the formation with all their strength, which was like pitting their strength against Qi Sea Ancestor, they immediately started coughing blood.

“Support us.” Bai Cang Shui called out.

“This is not good! Help them.”

“We can’t lose this formation!”

Heavenly Court’s Gu Immortals were anxious. Duke Tong, Duke Mei, and other immortals surrounded and attacked Qi Sea Ancestor.

Qi Sea Ancestor remained unmoved, he defended against the attacks from all directions with a composed smile, showing a calm expression: ”Let’s see how long you can defend yourselves.”

Because Qi Sea Ancestor showed his power, Wu Shuai obtained a much needed break.

He pointed his hand, the large group of army ants formed into the shape of a giant eagle, the eagle attacked Profound Literature grotto-heaven like it was swooping on prey.

“Stop!” Old Immortal Hua Yu was seething with fury, he moved forward to block, but all his methods could only destroy about fifteen percent of the attack and were helpless against the remaining eighty-five percent.

The whole of Profound Literature grotto-heaven shook intensely, army ants were tearing and gnawing at everything. The endless gnawing sounds were extremely horrifying.

“Save Profound Literature grotto-heaven, it is the final support pillar of the star array calculation formation!” Old Immortal Hua Yu shouted in grief.

Heavenly Court Gu Immortals had to send some people to defend Profound Literature grotto-heaven.

Like this, the pressure on Qi Sea Ancestor lessened and he could grasp onto battle opportunities more easily.

Because they had to defend the star array calculation formation, Heavenly Court was in a passive situation from the start.

This disadvantage was exploited viciously by Fang Yuan’s three clones, not giving the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals any chance to rest.

Profound Literature grotto-heaven was already in a ruined state, countless beings were dead, and ants roamed everywhere. Many areas were even drilled through, forming tunnels that directly led from Profound Literature grotto-heaven to the outside.

But these were not routes to escape, most of the Gu Masters could not fly and escaping the grotto-heaven meant falling to their deaths. Even the Gu Masters were in this situation, not to mention the mortals, animals, and plants.

“Xiao Bai, leave with my daughter, go!” Imperial Minister Su was a rank seven Gu Immortal of Profound Literature grotto-heaven. Right now, he was defending Li Xiao Bai and Su Qi Han who were behind him.

“No, I will continue to fight! This is my home...” Li Xiao Bai was already heavily injured, his voice was shaky, blood and tears flowed as he spoke.

Imperial Minister Su turned around and glared at Li Xiao Bai: ”Now is not the time to be brave! The future of Profound Literature grotto-heaven is bleak, but you are our hope. The people inside your immortal aperture are the hope of continuing the legacy of Profound Literature grotto-heaven! Get lost now!”

“Father-in-law, let’s go together!” Li Xiao Bai tugged at Imperial Minister Su.

Imperial Minister Su shook his head fiercely, berating furiously: ”I am an important official of the Imperial Court while you are not. You can leave but I cannot. The dynasty is about to fall, so what if I die? Hahaha!”

Imperial Minister Su laughed loudly as he pushed Li Xiao Bai outside of Profound Literature grotto-heaven and then flew into the ant groups, engaging in a fierce battle.

“Father——!” Su Qi Han shouted with tears flowing down her face. She was forcefully dragged by Li Xiao Bai and left through the hole in the grotto-heaven.

But just as the two was about to escape successfully, a strange anomaly occurred.

The aperture walls of Profound Literature grotto-heaven crumbled apart instantly and were replaced by huge dark brown earth walls that were filled with bumps and holes.

There were countless caves and passageways in the earth walls, it was like a maze.

The couple, Li Xiao Bai and Su Qi Han, almost escaped but were bounced back in by the earth walls.

“What is this?!” Almost all the Gu Immortals were astonished.

“A battlefield killer move... it is actually faster than my rumor cage!” Zhou Xiong Xin’s expression changed.

Other Heavenly Court members also had unsightly expressions.

They had yet to trap Qi Sea Ancestor completely, when they discovered that they were the ones to fall into a battlefield killer move first.

“That is Wu Shuai’s killer move.” Qi Sea Ancestor laughed to himself.

Before the battle, they had already shared information about their respective strength and methods.

Qi Sea Ancestor knew this was Wu Shuai’s myriad army ant nest battlefield killer move.

Its core Immortal Gu was rank eight ant nest Immortal Gu. This move used a blessed land or grotto-heaven as the base, countless army ants would first be sent to corrode the blessed land or grotto-heaven, after the corrosion reached a certain point, the battlefield would activate.

Once it was activated, it turned the crumbling blessed land or grotto-heaven into an ant nest battlefield. The activation process was extremely fast, but the prior accumulation took a long time.

Thus, the fastest battlefield killer move was still rumor cage.

After Wu Shuai activated the battlefield killer move myriad army ant nest, every existence in Profound Literature grotto-heaven was trapped in this battlefield.

He immediately sent army ants to attack Gu Immortals everywhere. At the same time, he also sent many ants to devour the resources and breed rapidly.

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were attacked by the army ants. Looking at the army ants that worked in tandem with this battlefield, they realized that Wu Shuai was the user of this battlefield killer move!

“We underestimated him.”

“Fang Yuan’s three main clones have many new methods and almost all their killer moves have been modified. What about Fang Yuan’s main body?”

“It is not the time to be concerned about Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s situation, we need to break this battlefield quickly!”

Heavenly Court Gu Immortals discussed quickly and reached a consensus.

But how could it be easy to find a person in the ant nest battlefield that was as large as Profound Literature grotto-heaven?

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals tried many methods but had no gains.

Wu Shuai was hiding at a corner, leisurely mobilizing army ants to move through countless tunnels, to attack the four Heavenly Court immortals who were in a formation.

The four Heavenly Court immortals formed a battle formation to temporarily trap Qi Sea Ancestor but were being attacked fiercely from the outside.

Qi Sea Ancestor saw the chance and raised tens of thousands of qi currents, Heavenly Court’s four immortals received the attack and were at the brink of death.

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were unable to find Wu Shuai for the moment and focused their strength to suppress Qi Sea Ancestor.

After several exchanges, the four Heavenly Court immortals were soaked in blood, their aura declined again, on the contrary, Qi Sea Ancestor still had ample energy and strength.

“If this formation were made of the four major paths—earth, water, wind, and fire—its strength should be much higher. Unfortunately, you lack a wind path expert.” Qi Sea Ancestor laughed, as time passed, he started to see many more details.

“Qi Sea, take this!” Golden Hooped Great Immortal charged forward, sending hundreds of golden hoops that flew chaotically in the air.

The golden hoops were set to land on Qi Sea Ancestor, but were blocked by the surrounding qi currents.

Duke Mei suddenly appeared, his snow-white eyebrows grew in size and pierced through the qi currents, binding Qi Sea Ancestor’s hands.

Qi Sea Ancestor gave a shout, qi currents erupted like a vast tide that threatened to destroy everything!

The qi currents struck Golden Hooped Great Immortal, Duke Mei, and the other four Heavenly Court immortals.

At the crucial moment, Jun Shen Guang, Zhou Xiong Xin, and others stepped in to help the six Heavenly Court members.

Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch attacked, his giant hand slammed down on Qi Sea Ancestor’s head!

At the critical moment, Qi Sea Ancestor smiled lightly.

Immortal killer move — Ancestor Qi Retraction!

This move was modified from triple qi retraction killer move, it used two great rank eight Immortal Gu, Heaven Qi and Earth Qi, as the cores. All the lifeforms in the range of the killer move would gradually turn into qi currents that would return to Qi Sea Ancestor and turn into qi path dao marks.

Hence, this was not only an offensive method, but could also be used to cultivate and increase the number of his qi path dao marks.

This move was extremely powerful and mysterious but had two huge flaws.

Firstly, it consumed a lot of lifespan.

Secondly, once the move was activated, whether it succeeded or failed, it could not be activated again for one hundred days (in terms of Qi Sea Ancestor’s time).

Under ancestor qi retraction, Heavenly Court’s Gu Immortals were first shackled, unable to even budge.

Duke Mei was the first person affected. His eyebrows, skin, blood, flesh, and lastly his bones, organs, and so on were all melted into qi currents that were absorbed by Qi Sea Ancestor.

When Duke Mei’s corrosion reached his bones, Golden Hooped Great Immortal also started turning into qi until he was reduced to nothingness.

Duke Mei and Golden Hooped Great Immortal died one after the other, followed by Jun Shen Guang, Zhou Xiong Xin, and others, before finally affecting the four Heavenly Court immortals who were the furthest away.

Wan Zi Hong was the first to be unable to hold on, second was Prince Feng Xian, then Bai Cang Shui and Uncle Feng.

Qi Sea Ancestor looked at the four: ”You still lack tacit coordination. More importantly, two of you have been revived recently and don’t have all your Gu worms so your conditions are not perfect, which is the greatest flaw in this battle formation. You are dreaming if you want to trap me!”

The four Heavenly Court immortals held on with clenched teeth and had no energy to reply.

Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch was unwilling to give in, most of his body had already melted but he still raised his injured fist and tried to smash Qi Sea Ancestor.

“You all seem to have forgotten me.” Wu Shuai’s voice rang in the battlefield. Densely packed army ants climbed up Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch’s body.

The giant Seven Fiendish Primeval Monarch broke apart at the very next moment.

“Our main body is arriving, we’ve won this battle!” Wu Shuai laughed loudly.

He could tell that even without him making a move, in just a while longer, Qi Sea Ancestor would be able to kill the four Heavenly Court immortals.

“Is that so?” At the juncture of defeat, Prince Feng Xian suddenly revealed a smug smile: ”Qi Sea Ancestor, you fell for it.”

His words had not even finished when Qi Sea Ancestor, who was in the center of the Four Elements Shifting Formation, shook suddenly.

The qi currents around him transformed rapidly into the appearance of Lin Jian Xing, and he stood right behind Qi Sea Ancestor.

Lin Jian Xing, who was formed from the qi currents, was lifelike, but he had no expression.

At the next moment, he moved forward and forcefully entered Qi Sea Ancestor’s body.

Immediately, Qi Sea Ancestor suffered a severe injury, his defenses crumbled apart.

In a battlefield not far away.

Star Constellation’s will smiled inside Embroidered Tower and disregarded Zhan Bu Du as she threw out Star Constellation Chessboard: ”Now, you shall see the true secret of the star array calculation formation!”

The star array calculation formation collapsed, the remaining stars self-detonated and let out a majestic and strange power. Under the control of Star Constellation Chessboard, this power directly broke the ant nest battlefield and reduced the four Heavenly Court immortals into powder, finally sealing Qi Sea Ancestor.

“Go!” The voice of Star Constellation’s will transmitted from Star Constellation Chessboard.

Star Constellation Chessboard circled rapidly above Qi Sea Ancestor’s head, shooting starry radiance that covered Qi Sea Ancestor and dragged him towards Heavenly Court.

Heavenly Court’s entrance opened a little, having clearly been prepared for a long time for this moment.

Fang Yuan’s main body arrived and saw this scene, his expression immediately turned shocked and furious as he shouted: ”Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, so this is all your scheme!”

Chapter 2323: Central Continent Held Hostage

“Success! We succeeded!!” Prince Feng Xian shouted loudly, his pale face was filled with excitement.

“I accomplished the mission...” Wan Zi Hong’s eyes were shut, her aura was almost depleted, she had never felt so weak and tired before.

The so-called Four Elements Shifting Formation was only a cover to lure attention away, its true goal was to create an environment for Lin Jian Xing’s sword qi takes form killer move!

Prince Feng Xian, Wan Zi Hong, and the rest had lost in the battle against Lin Jian Xing not long ago.

When they returned, they admitted their blunder to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable with a heavy heart but Star Constellation Immortal Venerable instead rewarded them and said: This was all part of her plan!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was the number one person in wisdom path since ancient times. In the contest of three venerables, she had relied on all kinds of small clues to deduce that Lin Jian Xing was an otherworldly demon and that his strength had reached pseudo venerable level.

Lin Jian Xing was cultivating in seclusion, hiding his strength. The world did not know of his secret.

Although Star Constellation Immortal Venerable deduced it, she kept it a secret.

Then she intentionally sent the five Heavenly Court Gu Immortals to attack Lin Jian Xing. The goal was to use phantom path methods to capture the power of Lin Jian Xing’s killer move.

Everyone knew that the Heavenly Court members’ immortal apertures were phantom apertures.

The injuries that they suffered in the intense battle with Lin Jian Xing were essentially sword path dao marks being engraved on them.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable deduced and modified a phantom path method to make these phantom apertures contain those sword path dao marks and bring them back along with the Heavenly Court members.

The retrieved sword path dao marks could restore Lin Jian Xing’s method after a series of procedures.

Qi Sea Ancestor was struck by this move, he immediately lost his footing and was then attacked by Star Constellation’s will, he did not even have the time to defend when he was sealed.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable concealed the truth and only told the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals of her plan after they returned.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable even apologized to the immortals.

The four Heavenly Court immortals did not dare to accept the apology and only felt intense joy with not even any grievance.

They were loyal to Heavenly Court and realized that it was very reasonable of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to conceal the truth. Only under the condition where they did not know of it could they maintain such a secret and fight with Lin Jian Xing without revealing any flaws in their emotions.

“But why try so hard to capture Lin Jian Xing’s method?” Wan Zi Hong had mentioned this doubt back then.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not reply, only instructing them to follow her arrangements.

When they saw Qi Sea Ancestor being sealed, Prince Feng Xian and Wan Zi Hong finally understood Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s effort.

The most important element was Lin Jian Xing’s power.

First of all, he was a pseudo venerable himself, although he was weaker than Qi Sea Ancestor, Heavenly Court’s replicated sword qi method had gone through many amplifications and was stronger than Lin Jian Xing’s current limit.

Secondly, Lin Jian Xing’s core Immortal Gu was sword qi Gu, although his sword qi was filled with sword path dao marks, it also had dense number of qi path dao marks. It was because of this that it could target Qi Sea Ancestor who cultivated qi path.

Finally, Lin Jian Xing’s sword qi attack was too sudden, Qi Sea Ancestor was truly caught off guard.

“Qi Sea Ancestor is finally sealed. But Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable spent so much effort and trouble to capture Qi Sea Ancestor, what is this for?”

“Qi Sea Ancestor is the strongest clone of Heaven Refining Demon Venerable, maybe it is to restrain Fang Yuan?”

“I heard Fairy Maiden Soul modified Bo Qing’s soul, this shows that clones might be convenient but are also a huge flaw of the main body.”

The other Heavenly Court Gu Immortals discussed as they watched Qi Sea Ancestor being escorted to Heavenly Court’s entrance.

“Stop dreaming!” Right at this time, a venerable landed from the sky.

He was wearing a white robe, his black hair fluttered in the air, his eyes were black like the abyss, and his face showed fury and killing intent.

It was Fang Yuan!

Fang Yuan grabbed Meng Qiu Zhen’s shoulder as he maintained reverse flow protection seal and activated another move.

Immortal killer move — Arrival of Dragon Snake with Dust Fog and Explosive Soul Wind!

Fog billowed, dragons and snakes roared, forming a terrifying attack that fell on Qi Sea Ancestor like a vast heavenly river.

Seeing Fang Yuan trying to kill his strongest clone without any consideration, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable who was close behind showed a solemn expression.

“Friend Fang Yuan, you are indeed vicious! You show no hesitation even when getting rid of your own clone. Unfortunately for you, I am here.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable took back her secluded domain of heaven and earth Mental Domain and stretched her ten fingers. Her fingers pointed repeatedly with such speed that it created multicolored shadows of her moving fingers.

The finger shadows condensed into deep-blue lights that were extremely bright like shining crystals.

Fang Yuan’s soul fog was constantly cut by the blue crystal light and crumbled rapidly, the remaining power was blocked by Embroidered Tower while some traces of the power reached Qi Sea Ancestor but were blocked by the tight defenses of Star Constellation Chessboard.

“Star Constellation, you!” Fang Yuan’s eyes narrowed sharply as he looked at Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

In the previous fight, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had not used such a method. It was not that she did not have them but chose to not use them.

She had been concealing them!

Qi Sea Ancestor being sealed and Fang Yuan counterattacking fiercely were within Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s expectations.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable defended with all her strength, not letting Fang Yuan have any progress.

If it were Star Constellation Immortal Venerable who attacked Qi Sea Ancestor and tried to capture him, she would be obstructed by Fang Yuan and could not succeed easily. With the same logic, Qi Sea Ancestor was already captured now, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had the initiative and it became easier for her to obstruct Fang Yuan.

In the end, under Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s obstruction and protection, Qi Sea Ancestor was escorted into Heavenly Court.

“Master’s revival... there is finally some hope.” A huge rock weighing on Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s mind was lifted at this sight, she could not restrain her joy.

In the contest of three venerables, with Spectral Soul controlling the fused heaven, Giant Sun and Fang Yuan only had one option which was to confront each other and wait for a chance while managing and preparing their forces.

But there was a better option for Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

That was to revive other venerables.

Three Immortal Kings appeared in Heavenly Court’s history, if Red Lotus Demon Venerable was also counted, it could be said that they nurtured four venerables.

Among eleven venerables, four were from Heavenly Court, this was a huge number.

Besides this, there were no other super forces that could nurture a venerable.

Heavenly Court was the first and the only super force.

As long as another venerable was revived, Heavenly Court would have a huge advantage.

There was no need to consider Red Lotus for now but Primordial Origin and Genesis Lotus were very good candidates to revive.

From what Star Constellation Immortal Venerable knew, Primordial Origin and Genesis Lotus had two revival methods but they were concealed deeply.

Time was needed to search for clues regarding Genesis Lotus’s self-portrait and Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s Primordial Origin Treasury, it clearly seemed like it would take a long time. But Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable had another revival method, it was the qi harvest fruit.

Heavenly Court’s qi harvest fruit formed Qi Sea Ancestor, so Star Constellation Immortal Venerable wanted to trap Qi Sea and resume the interrupted revival of Primordial Origin.

To do this, Qi Sea Ancestor could not be killed. He needed to be alive to preserve the qi harvest fruit as much as possible.

The difficulty in capturing a pseudo venerable alive was very high!

Qi Sea Ancestor could even endure one or two moves from a venerable and was not without any ability to resist. This was because he had the secluded domain of heaven and earth Hu Land, while Star Constellation Immortal Venerable lacked a rank nine wisdom path or star path Immortal Gu.

Moreover, Fang Yuan had plenty of experience and was very crafty. Normally, he paid a lot of attention to his clones’ safety and stored them in his immortal aperture, very rarely sending them out.

If Star Constellation Immortal Venerable were to make a move personally, the commotion would be too huge and she would be obstructed by Fang Yuan at the very beginning.

Thus, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable began to plan.

Heavenly Court lacked pseudo venerable level battle strength, it was an obvious disadvantage but it could be turned into an advantage if used well.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable set up the star array calculation formation to quicken the cultivation speed of Central Continent’s Gu Immortals and also to use as bait to lure Qi Sea Ancestor.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable then used Lin Jian Xing’s strength as the crucial method to target Qi Sea Ancestor. At the same time, she also showed all kinds of flaws to display her weakness to the enemy.

She still thought all these preparations were not enough.

Heaven path dream realms!

This was an opportunity to Fang Yuan, but was it not a fortuitous encounter for Star Constellation Immortal Venerable?

As long as the enemy’s fortuitous encounter was used properly, it might be one’s own fortuitous encounter!

“Fang Yuan will definitely come!” The moment Star Constellation Immortal Venerable discovered the heaven path dream realms, she knew what Fang Yuan’s action would be.

She could not do anything to the heaven path dream realms and Feng Jin Huang had not grown up, but Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could use them as bait!

In fact, even if Feng Jin Huang was fully matured, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was somewhat doubtful about using this girl.

Feng Jin Huang’s father was Feng Jiu Ge, the latter had an unclear relationship with Red Lotus Demon Venerable. Dream wings Immortal Gu took the initiative to send itself to Feng Jin Huang, it was clearly the fortune of being Great Dream’s seed, and the so-called Great Dream Immortal Venerable was the plan of heaven’s will when fate Gu still existed.

Could such a person be used? Especially at such a crucial time?

The only miscalculation was that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not expect Fang Yuan to move so quickly.

“Since he moved this fast, he definitely has the strength to back himself up.” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable already expected this at the start of the battle.

So when Fang Yuan continued to reveal his strength in the battle, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was not as surprised as what she showed on the surface.

“Fang Yuan modified so many methods and has new killer moves, he has very likely obtained wisdom Gu again.” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable stood before the entrance of the Heavenly Court and faced Fang Yuan.

Starlight shone dazzlingly on this number one person in wisdom path, she said with a smile: ”Friend Fang Yuan, do you dare to come into Heavenly Court?”

Saying so, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable slowly floated backwards and entered Heavenly Court.

Heavenly Court’s entrance was still open.

Fang Yuan stood on the spot!

He snorted coldly as he activated killer moves one after the other. First was Arrival of Dragon Snake with Dust Fog and Explosive Soul Wind, then was Shocking Departure of Year Dream Wave and Dang Hun Sound, but both were easily blocked by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s strength surged with the help of Heavenly Court’s countless wisdom path dao marks!

Fang Yuan’s face was extremely dark as he sneered: ”You are really the number one person in wisdom path, it is truly amazing. How about we undergo a hostage exchange?”

“Fang Yuan, you don’t have anything now, what can you exchange with?”

Fang Yuan spread his arms and said loudly: ”Right now, every single person in Central Continent—be it man or woman, old or young, immortal or mortal, intelligent or stupid—is my hostage!”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable sighed.

She had already predicted this, her expression was a complex mix of helplessness, guilt, resolve, resentment, and others.

In the end, her expression turned cold as she said to Fang Yuan: ”Do what you want.”

Chapter 2324: Primordial Origin’s Grand Revival Plan

“Do what you want.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s words almost froze the atmosphere between the two venerables.

Fang Yuan could not help but laugh in ridicule: ”Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, you are truly the Immortal King of Heavenly Court, this is truly the number one super force, the leader of humanity — Heavenly Court!”

His eyes narrowed as his expression turned solemn: ”This is not normal, even if it was just for my mere clone, even if this is Qi Sea... Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, what is your true intention?!”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not speak, her figure flashed like starlight and disappeared from the entrance.

Fang Yuan’s expression was dark and his eyes shone coldly as some anxiety showed itself on his face.

Fang Yuan turned around and flew down from spectral heaven, arriving in Central Continent and entering the battlefield.

He was trying to take the Heavenly Court members as captives but these Gu Immortals had already suicided.

They could revive in Heavenly Court’s immortal graveyard.

With the destruction of fate Gu, there was a huge potential in the method of suicide and revival.

Heavenly Court had complete methods. On one hand, the Gu Immortals had phantom apertures, when they died, the phantom apertures returned, their losses were minimized. On the other hand, when the Gu Immortals suicided, their Immortal Gu could be transferred through treasure yellow heaven.

Now, this had already become a mature and excellent battle tactic of Heavenly Court.

Under the same cultivation level, stopping a Gu Immortal from escaping was extremely difficult. At the very least, one needed immortal formations or immortal battlefield killer moves to trap the target.

To prevent a Gu Immortal from suiciding was much more difficult than stopping them from escaping.

What could they do about if the other wanted to die?

But, with Zhan Bu Du and Wu Shuai pinning them down, some Gu Immortals were still stuck in the battle.

Fang Yuan’s main body descended, bringing complete despair to these Central Continent Gu Immortals. He directly waved his sleeve and suppressed all of these Gu Immortals.

He did not kill them and only took them as captives.

He captured over ten Central Continent Gu Immortals but there was not even one member of Heavenly Court; naturally, these captives included Li Xiao Bai.

Heavenly Court and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not show any movement, Fang Yuan’s expression became increasingly unsightly.

He thought for a bit and flew towards Fei He Mountain.

Central Continent’s Fei He Mountain was the base of Immortal Crane Sect, this mountain was not only a super resource point, the public blessed land of Immortal Crane Sect was also located on it.

Fang Yuan was currently at the center of the star array calculation formation and the nearest super force was Immortal Crane Sect.

But when he arrived at the location of Fei He Mountain, this floating mountain range had disappeared.

Fang Yuan’s expression turned darker, he then moved northwest towards Myriad Dragon Dock.

Myriad Dragon Dock was the same as Immortal Crane Sect, both belonged to the ten great ancient sects of Central Continent. Myriad Dragon Dock’s headquarters blessed land was on the island at the heart of dragon lake.

Fang Yuan arrived here, dragon lake and the central island were still around but the public blessed land was empty.

Fang Yuan went to Heavenly Lotus Sect, Spirit Butterfly Valley, Ancient Soul Sect, Heaven’s Envy Manor, Wind Cloud Manor, Combat Immortal Sect, Spirit Affinity House, and Black Heaven Temple, but all their headquarters were empty.

Clearly, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had already planned to give up on Central Continent and had made sufficient preparations to bring away the sect members.

Heavenly Court.

Within Qi Sea Ancestor’s mind.

Qi Sea Ancestor could not move, his thoughts were also being suppressed by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s method.

But Qi Sea Ancestor put up his final resistance with the remaining will in his mind: ”Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, you are really a good schemer.”

During this period of imprisonment, Qi Sea Ancestor already understood the situation.

Lin Jian Xing’s sword qi killer move was extremely effective on him; first, it was because the sword qi was concealed and also had qi path dao marks, Qi Sea Ancestor was not able to detect it with the vast qi currents surrounding him at that time.

But analyzing the situation deeper, Qi Sea Ancestor was certain that the main culprit ware the sword path dao marks!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable sensed Qi Sea Ancestor’s thoughts and said: ”You are not wrong, Lin Jian Xing is different from others, he is an otherworldly demon and in history, otherworldly demons carry otherworldly dao marks.”

“Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had otherworldly space path dao marks so his Thieving Heaven’s true inheritance space could block the future venerables. In Crazed Demon Cave, when the hole of chaos appeared, Thieving Heaven used his otherworldly space path dao marks as the main force to seal it.”

Qi Sea Ancestor understood at once: ”So Lin Jian Xing has otherworldly sword path dao marks. This move is probably effective against even venerables, isn’t it too much of a waste to use it on a clone like me?”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable then told the truth of the qi harvest fruit and Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s revival.

Qi Sea’s will shook fiercely: ”So it was like this! Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, you already planned a trap when you set up the star array calculation formation. Later, you used heaven path dream realms to create an environment to lure me into attacking the star array calculation formation. We actually fell for it!”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable: ”As a wisdom path Gu Immortal, I naturally researched deeply into Fang Yuan’s personality. Moreover, you are are his most capable clone, there was a high chance you would be sent to attack the star array calculation formation.”

Qi Sea’s will sneered: ”In that case, even though you went through such an elaborate charade to capture and imprison me, did you manage to deduce my main body’s actions? Your Central Continent is done for! Hahaha. It is such a regret, if you had refined all of the wisdom path dao marks of Central Continent, you might have had a chance to block my main body. A pity, a pity.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s tone became quiet and heavy: ”My Heavenly Court is the leader of the righteous path, over three million years had passed since it was established. Since then, countless Heavenly Court Gu Immortals had sacrificed themselves to protect the righteous path and the whole of humanity.”

“In the present situation, many venerables are confronting each other in utter chaos, it is much more terrifying and severe than when variant humans dominated the world in the Immemorial Antiquity Era.”

“Central Continent is bordered with four regions, I, Star Constellation, am starting to feel powerless after confronting the other venerables for so long. Right now, I can only pay attention to the key aspects and guard the overall situation.”

“Since I made such a plan, I obviously know what Fang Yuan’s reaction will be. The plan succeeded now, so the common people of my Central Continent and countless living beings are facing Fang Yuan’s terrifying revenge!”

“However...”

“As long as Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable revives from this, my Heavenly Court will have two venerables, the situation of the five regions will definitely undergo a great change.”

“Everyone knows that the demonic path is unrestrained and runs amok, but they do not know that it takes even more courage and sense of responsibility to defend the righteous path!”

“I, Star Constellation, have sinned to create an advantage for the righteous path. I am sinful for sacrificing countless people!”

“But I am willing to bear this heavy sin to create more hope for the future, for humanity, and for the righteous path.”

“In fact, Divine Emperor City has already stored the records of various human qi in it. By cooperating with Heavenly Court’s immortal graveyard, we will be capable of using more revival methods.”

“I solemnly swear now, regardless of how many humans Fang Yuan slaughters today, as long as I have a trace of strength left in the future, I will do everything I can to revive them! If I fail to keep my word, then I, Star Constellation, am not fit to be human!!”

These words stupefied Qi Sea Ancestor.

Even as her enemy, he could not help but admire Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s resolve, sense of responsibility, and decisiveness.

“Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable!”

“Sob, sob... we were too shallow, we even resented you before.”

“Everything is for righteousness!”

“How can we compromise because of Demon Venerable’s threat and revenge? This is not kindness but a form of weakness!”

“Right, if we compromise this time, we will do it again and again in the future. We are the backbone of Central Continent’s righteous path, how can we bend our backs in front of Fang Yuan?”

Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects’ Gu Immortals were gathered together, listening to the conversation between Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Qi Sea’s will.

Emotions surged in their hearts and many even cried.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used Qi Sea Ancestor to explain this situation to them personally.

The resentment, confusion, anger, and other negative feelings hiding in their hearts were swept away. Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects’ Gu Immortals were now filled with respect towards Star Constellation Immortal Venerable along with confidence and courage to protect the righteous path.

But at the next moment, a Gu Immortal shouted: ”Oh no, Heaven Refining Demon Venerable published news in treasure yellow heaven saying that we captured Qi Sea Ancestor to recreate the qi harvest fruit and revive Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable!”

The crowd went into a commotion immediately.

Many connected to treasure yellow heaven and some of them started cursing: ”Fang Yuan, this shameless, despicable scoundrel. He even recorded Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s previous nonchalance towards his threat in a video and is playing it on constant loop in treasure yellow heaven. He is trying to stir the hearts of Central Continent’s people and damage our Heavenly Court’s reputation!!”

“There is a spy, there is likely Fang Yuan’s spy hidden among us. Otherwise, why will he suddenly know the truth?!” Someone brought up the possibility of a spy, making the Gu Immortals feel even more at unease.

Many Gu Immortals openly requested Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to inspect everyone.

But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable shook her head slightly: ”Please don’t be rash. I escorted Qi Sea Ancestor personally, by putting such an emphasis on him, it had already created doubts in Fang Yuan’s mind.”

“Venerables are not easy to deceive, it is normal for him to see through it.”

“Although Fang Yuan cannot bring out any evidence and is probably not certain of it himself, he intentionally let out this information to gain the attention of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.”

“However, it doesn’t matter. I will be staying in Heavenly Court and won’t go out for the following time. Even if Giant Sun, Fang Yuan, and Spectral Soul get into an alliance, they won’t be able to hinder the plan of reviving Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable!”

“As long as we don’t waver and stay here, Fang Yuan and the rest won’t be able to do anything.”

The immortals’ gazes shone as they praised Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s unmatched wisdom.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was indeed an expert in using such tricks.

Even if there was Fang Yuan’s spy among the immortals, she did not intend to investigate it.

What was the point?

People were not united right now, with Fang Yuan causing a great massacre in Central Continent, it would stir their hearts even more. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could not even unite the people’s minds, why would she add more chaos to this?

Moreover, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not feel fear even if there were spies here. Even if Fang Yuan, Giant Sun, and Spectral Soul attacked together, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had the confidence to defend Heavenly Court.

This was the benefit of owning their own headquarters!

No matter how many people Fang Yuan killed, or how miserable Central Continent’s situation became, as long as Star Constellation Immortal Venerable revived Primordial Origin, it would be a huge victory!

It was similar to the earlier situation where Fang Yuan was beaten miserably by Giant Sun and Star Constellation, but as long as he absorbed the dream realms, he would be the true winner!

In fact, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was already preparing to revive Primordial Origin even back in Crazed Demon Cave.

When she was seizing the Primordial Domains, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable deliberately searched and gathered qi path and wood path Primordial Domains.

So, once Primordial Domain revived, he could absorb the qi path Primordial Domains. Even if he did not reach supreme grandmaster attainment level, he would not be far from it.

What Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was worried about were Immortal Gu.

Even if Primordial Origin revived, if he did not have Immortal Gu to use, he could not use his full strength.

This was the situation with Star Constellation and Giant Sun, they did not have suitable rank nine Immortal Gu and had completely new rank nine immortal aperture; their condition was far from their previous life’s peak state.

“Heaven qi Immortal Gu and earth qi Immortal Gu along with the secluded domain of heaven and earth Hu Land are with Qi Sea. Adding on Heavenly Court’s human qi Immortal Gu and other Gu, master’s qi path Gu worms are somewhat gathered now.”

“It is indeed a huge pity that there are no rank nine qi path Immortal Gu, but maybe, Primordial Origin Treasury has it?”

“When master revives, he can activate the treasury, I won’t need to search for clues to find the Primordial Origin Treasury.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable quietly planned internally.

Chapter 2325: Fang Yuan Plunders Central Continent!

Profound jade snake cave was a famous super resource point in Central Continent.

It belonged to one of the ten great ancient sects, Heaven’s Envy Manor. The scale of annual resource production of profound jade snake cave was among the top five in Central Continent, the resources it produced were of many types as well, including enslavement path, transformation path, earth path, dark path, space path, and poison path.

Profound jade snake cave was the breeding ground for countless poisonous creatures among which profound jade snakes were the overlords that countered poison. Every profound jade snake was an immemorial desolate beast, they were born from jade, had no scales, were light green resembling jade, and emitted fresh fragrance.

The most valuable resources in profound jade snake cave were the profound jade snakes but it was not easy to find them. It was not only because profound jade snakes were small and enjoyed silence, profound jade snake cave’s terrain was complex with thousands of caves in it. And because it had space path dao marks, small caves often contained large spaces and were nested upon each other.

Heaven’s Envy Manor might possess this super resource point and also set up an immortal formation here but had never grasped it completely. Every year, Heaven’s Envy Manor had to send many Gu Immortal experts to explore profound jade snake cave to capture profound jade snakes.

But for the current Fang Yuan, it was not much of a trouble.

“Rise.” After preparing for a while, Fang Yuan used a killer move.

At the next moment, the earth and mountains shook.

The whole profound jade snake cave rose slowly amidst billowing smoke, and under Fang Yuan’s methods, shrank and was placed into sovereign immortal aperture.

This was already the eleventh super resource point that Fang Yuan obtained.

“Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, if you don’t hand over my clone, I will take away all of Central Continent’s large resource points!” Fang Yuan did not forget to shout threats.

But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable showed no movement, she had clearly resolved herself to stay in Heavenly Court and revive Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable. She was not going to be shaken by the outside world.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly as he continued.

He arrived at the source of Falling Heavenly River.

This river was a boundless expanse of water that heavily crashed at the riverbed from an endless height. The rumbling noise of the waterfall was like the continuous crackling of thunder. Endless water vapor formed dense fog that shrouded a vast range of the surroundings.

The reason for the formation of this river was because of Bo Qing’s attempt to breakthrough to rank nine.

Falling Heavenly River smashed open an inland river that opened a channel that flowed through the entirety of Central Continent, towards the eastern side of central continent, and into eastern sea.

Even the merging of two heavens only reduced the size of Falling Heavenly River slightly, it was still a majestic sight to behold.

After taking profound jade snake cave, Fang Yuan arrived at the source of Falling Heavenly River.

Fang Yuan made his move.

After a while, Falling Heavenly River’s size shrank to sixty percent!

This sixty percent Falling Heavenly River was stored inside sovereign immortal aperture.

The water level of the inland river at the source of Falling Heavenly River fell by thousands of feet. The water surface at the middle and lower stream of Falling Heavenly River began to reduce rapidly and exposed the river bed, causing negative influences on the surrounding plants, crops, temperature, mortal habitats, and so on.

Fang Yuan left Falling Heavenly River and arrived at spirit bank spring.

This was a super resource point that belonged to Ancient Soul Sect, which had once sent Yang Feng to guard this place but was still plundered by Forgotten Daoist.

But now, Yang Feng had already followed Ancient Soul Sect to enter Heavenly Court.

Fang Yuan easily dismantled the immortal formation and took spirit bank spring away.

After spirit bank spring was pot river.

This river resembled a long jade belt, it was situated in the eastern area of Central Continent. The riverbank was filled with willow trees and gentle breeze. The water in pot river was smooth flowing, like a beautiful song, it was graceful and harmonious. There was a lot of pot grass growing in pot river.

Wind Cloud Manor was in charge of pot river and held a festival around pot river every year.

But not long later, pot river along with its river channel was moved into the immortal aperture by Fang Yuan. Even if there were to be pot river festivals in the future, they could only be held inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

After pot river was Hidden Dragon Cave.

Hidden Dragon Cave had once imprisoned the legendary immemorial desolate beast Di Zang Sheng. There were very large numbers of scale enslavement path and rule path dao marks here. There was also the remnants of the huge immortal Gu formation that Heavenly Court set up here, it had a huge reference value to most formation path Gu Immortals.

After Hidden Dragon Cave was put into the sovereign immortal aperture, Fang Yuan moved to Lake Heart Mountain.

This was Spirit Affinity House’s headquarters.

It was definitely an outstanding place to be chosen as the encampment of one of the ten great ancient sects.

Lake Heart Mountain was a super resource point by itself, not only did it contain secret inheritance peak, lesser cold peak, affection peak, fierce fire peak, heavenly flowers peak, and other peaks, it also had Fairy Life Tablet Hall, time path cultivation immortal formation, and other facilities.

Naturally, life tablet Gu was already taken from the Fairy Life Tablet Hall, the time path cultivation immortal formation’s Immortal Gu were also taken away. But these facilities were mostly intact, they could be used after repairing.

Soon, Lake Heart Mountain became a scenic spot within the sovereign immortal aperture.

After Lake Heart Mountain was Mountain Tortoise Valley, then Imprisonment Valley, red river beach, hundred segment forest, scale light river, earth qi rock forest, Quiet Rain Valley.....

Fang Yuan looted wantonly, he did not hold back at all!

Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects had left, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was holed up in Heavenly Court; Fang Yuan had no obstructions.

His looting efficiency was extremely high!

If Giant Sun Immortal Venerable wanted to relocate these resource points, he had to use luck path methods or blood path methods to imitate other paths and put in a lot of effort to move them.

Fang Yuan had the sovereign immortal body which had non-conflicting dao marks, so he could use methods of all paths. Earth path was more suitable to relocate caves and caverns. Wood path methods were appropriate to plunder forests.

Another point was that Fang Yuan had a lot of Immortal Gu in his reserves. Putting rank nine Immortal Gu aside, refining rank eight Immortal Gu was as easy as drinking water to him.

Resource points were looted one after the other, the essence of the whole Central Continent was being plundered by him and his appetite showed no signs of being full!

There were some resource points which Fang Yuan could not obtain completely for the moment.

For instance, Sorrowful Wind Mountain Range. The mountain range was extremely range, Fang Yuan could not relocate the whole mountain range in a short period. He could easily take one or two mountain peaks but the mountain range was a long stretch, it could not be compared to one or two mountain peaks.

Another example was Hairy Foot Mountain. Hairy Foot Mountain once held Infallible blessed land, Fang Yuan had came to this place first but it was already destroyed by Heavenly Court.

There was also Reincarnation Battlefield. This was the battlefield killer move that was personally set up by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable. It was famous in history and was publicly recognized as the number one battlefield killer move since ancient times! Fang Yuan had carefully observed it before leaving directly.

It was not that he could not take it but it required careful study and deductions. This required a lot of time and effort, moreover, the specific time required was difficult to be estimated.

Fang Yuan had a lot of experience in looting so his actions were extremely efficient.

He left forty percent of Falling Heavenly River, it was not because he was willing to leave it behind, but he would have to spend more time and effort to take it. And it was better to loot other places than waste time here!

Central Continent fell into an unprecedented state of unrest.

There was no such unrest and chaos even during the fate war.

The fate war was mainly the war of Gu Immortals, Heavenly Court and Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects defended their positions.

But now that the Gu Immortals of Heavenly Court and Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects were all holed up inside Heavenly Court, Central Continent became an unguarded place.

Fang Yuan did not conceal his action of looting and relocating resource points. Every time he moved, it would cause a huge commotion that was noticed by others, and his actions enticed others as well.

“The grand venerable is eating meat but we should be able to drink the remaining soup, right?”

“Even if it is just one mouthful, it is enough for us to be full.”

“This is Central Continent, the ten great ancient sects have all moved away! This opportunity won’t come again.”

The five regional walls were gone, so the other four regions’ Gu Immortals began to move. After them were Central Continent’s few demonic path Gu Immortals and lone immortals, then finally were Central Continent’s righteous path Gu Immortals.

Central Continent’s righteous path did not consist of just the ten great ancient sects, there were many other super forces, for instance, Great Heavenly Sword Sect, Lightning Information Sect, Demon Expelling Sect, and so on.

Naturally, these righteous path forces moved with the excuse of defending Central Continent and helping Heavenly Court.

These people did not dare to appear in front of Fang Yuan, but Central Continent was huge and had a lot of resource points. Many resource points could not catch Fang Yuan’s eye or were positioned towards the end of the looting plan, these areas became the target of the Gu Immortals.

The sovereign immortal aperture was also in chaos.

Gu Immortals were so busy that their heads were spinning.

There had never been such a moment when resource points were moved in on such a large scale.

This was simply like a flood of resources, unceasing and endless.

The most crucial point was that super resource points could be found everywhere and were the majority, even the sovereign immortal aperture’s Gu Immortals were shaken to the core.

“Master is mighty! He is looting the whole of Central Continent.”

“This is a venerable’s might, this is our Lord Fang Yuan!”

“Great, Lord Qi Sea was captured by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, even if Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable revives, they will only be welcomed by a barren Central Continent.”

“The first wind vein ring is completed!”

“The second light vein ring is finished.”

“Dark path has also completed the first ring!”

The sovereign immortal aperture’s time flow was very different from the five regions’ outside world. All kinds of dao veins were constructed rapidly, metal path, light path, dark path, poison path, rule path, enslavement path, transformation path...

Gu Immortals worked day and night, squeezing out all their energy and constantly visiting Liver Life Hall. Now and then, someone would reach the limits and their liver would explode, but it was not an issue, many healing halls were constructed around the sovereign immortal aperture.

In an instant, many of the sovereign immortal aperture’s Gu Immortals became like Yu Zi, choosing to use the salt-water liver plan.

As the saying went, humans needed windfalls to get rich, while horses needed extra grass to grow healthy.

Fang Yuan’s costless looting made his sovereign immortal aperture’s development achieve an unprecedented and terrifying efficiency!

Central Continent was surrounded by four regions but was also a region with rich resources, second only to Eastern Sea. Eastern Sea had more water path resources but Central Continent had resources of all kinds.

Central Continent was developed by Heavenly Court for over three million years, its development had reached the limits, almost all the immortal level resource points were developed to some extent.

These all became Fang Yuan’s targets.

Many dao veins were completed almost at one go in the sovereign immortal aperture. This was a huge boost to the stability of the sovereign immortal aperture!

Thus, even though the sovereign immortal aperture annexed so many resource points, because of the dao veins, it became much more stable instead.

With such a foundation, Fang Yuan could begin absorbing the Primordial Domain in treasure yellow heaven and annexing blessed lands everywhere.

He had stored the Primordial Domain in treasure yellow heaven all along. There was no need to lie low now and he could start absorbing it.

There were many blessed lands everywhere in Central Continent.

For instance, Flowing Silver blessed land that was revealed because of the qi tides, Hu Immortal blessed land that Fang Yuan gave up in the past, or Star Form blessed land, and so on.

Chapter 2326: Giant Sun Retreats

“Star Constellation, is the rumor in treasure yellow heaven true?” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable fought against Spectral Soul Demon Venerable while contacting Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and questioning.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable replied casually: ”This is Fang Yuan’s scheme to waver your determination.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable dodged Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s attack while probing: ”Right now, Fang Yuan is plundering Central Continent, why aren’t you stopping him? If you are willing to give up on Central Continent’s resources, why don’t you come and deal with Spectral Soul Demon Venerable alongside me? Aren’t you the one who wants to eradicate Spectral Soul the most?”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable gave an excuse: ”Since you are in a bind, I will come and help you after I heal myself.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable heaved a long sigh: ”Star Constellation, you are truly good at scheming. I am impressed.”

He was a venerable, after seeing that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable hid inside Heavenly Court without any intention of coming out after capturing Qi Sea Ancestor, even giving up Central Continent’s resources and recalling the Gu Immortals of the ten great ancient sects, he guessed the truth.

What could make the grand Heavenly Court and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable make such a sacrifice?

The revival of a venerable!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was silent, she did not respond.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had to retreat, he no longer fought against Spectral Soul Demon Venerable but transmitted to Fang Yuan instead: ”Fang Yuan, I can’t lure Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to come out. If Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable revives, it will be over. Sigh, thinking about it, there were signs alluding to this earlier.”

“Do you remember the battle in Crazed Demon Cave? Back then, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable cooperated with me to pressure you but she made a mistake and lost the opportunity. The reason was because you used Qi Sea Ancestor as a shield, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable held back.”

Fang Yuan snorted coldly, replying: ”Star Constellation Immortal Venerable is truly the number one wisdom path in the world throughout history! It is normal that my wisdom path attainment is inferior to her! But what is the point of saying that now? We need to ally now and attack Heavenly Court to have a chance of turning the situation around!”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did his best to withdraw, he only dodged Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s attacks as he pulled apart the distance between them while thinking to himself.

He frowned deeply and considered the situation rapidly.

It seemed that he was the biggest loser in the battle over the heaven path dream realms.

Fang Yuan obtained the heaven path dream realms and lost Qi Sea Ancestor, but he obtained a lot of resources plundered from Central Continent.

Although Star Constellation Immortal Venerable lost Central Continent’s resources, she obtained Qi Sea Ancestor, if she could revive Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable successfully, she would be the biggest winner. By then, even if all of Central Continent were to be slaughtered by Fang Yuan, they would still be the winner!

Another venerable would change the situation fundamentally. No matter how much manpower or resources Central Continent lost, it was only temporary.

They were completely different concepts.

Even a fool would know which choice was more important.

As long as Heavenly Court’s two venerables cooperated, they would easily suppress Fang Yuan, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, or Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

It would be basically impossible for Fang Yuan, Giant Sun, or Spectral Soul to refine natural dao marks. If Heavenly Court sent out both venerables to attack them, they would need to retreat, they could not undergo the process of natural dao mark refinement.

Conversely, as long as Heavenly Court sent out a venerable to stall them, the other person could refine natural dao marks using that time.

As time passes, Heavenly Court’s advantage would accumulate quicker, by the time they refine all the natural dao marks of the five regions, the other venerables would be cornered.

Of course, in this situation, Giant Sun, Fang Yuan, and Spectral Soul would have to work together.

But could their alliance match the cooperation of Heavenly Court’s venerables?

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was not sane now, the main cooperation would lie with Giant Sun and Fang Yuan.

But Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not trust either of them.

It would not work!

Be it their cooperation level or fundamental beliefs, such differences would be magnified in a battle of life and death.

Not only that, Heavenly Court even had a third venerable in history, Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable!

If two other venerables were alive, the third venerable, Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable, would have a much easier time reviving.

“Thus, Heavenly Court has finally reached its most crucial turning point.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was clear about this fact.

This was like the backlash Fang Yuan faced from the venerables when he refined rank nine Gu earlier. If he survived it, he would experience a qualitative change and obtain the upper hand, in the future, no matter what he did, the difficulty would be much smaller.

The reason why the venerables were in a deadlock was because they had all just revived and were at the same starting point, or rather, their differences were minuscule.

But if another venerable from Heavenly Court revived, this balance would be broken, even if Giant Sun and Fang Yuan worked together, they could not match Heavenly Court.

“If we can’t stop Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, this will be the crucial moment where Heavenly Court regains its domination of the world and defeats the other venerables.”

Knowing this, after learning that Qi Sea was captured in Heavenly Court, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s standpoint changed completely.

He contacted Fang Yuan and created a plan to pretend that he was still fighting against Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

“It is a pity that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable has a clear grasp of the human heart, I can’t lure her to come outside!”

If Star Constellation Immortal Venerable were in Central Continent, there would still be hope. After all, her advantage in Central Continent was not as large as being physically in Heavenly Court.

But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable hid inside and refused to come outside no matter what, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was helpless in this situation.

Truly, a top schemer could achieve victory without even participating in battle!

At the crucial moment, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not try to fight, she was unaffected by the burden of Heavenly Court’s reputation and other factors, bearing the huge pressure of sacrificing and giving up Central Continent’s people to make the right choice.

Luck inspection.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was indignant, he used his luck inspection method.

The results were disappointing.

Heavenly Court’s luck was above everyone else, it was still showing signs of rising. Be it Giant Sun, Fang Yuan, or Spectral Soul, they were all suppressed by Heavenly Court’s luck.

Other than that, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not see any huge variables that could influence the situation.

“Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, why are you still hesitating?!” Fang Yuan’s voice was transmitted again.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable sighed: ”Fang Yuan, we’ve lost, accept the fact. We will need to exert a lot of effort to enter Heavenly Court, even if we get in, we are unable to cooperate sincerely, how can we be Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s match? We won’t succeed even with Spectral Soul Demon Venerable!”

“Attacking rashly will cause us to fall into Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s trap, our strength will dwindle. In my opinion, we should preserve our strength for a future opportunity.”

Fang Yuan snorted coldly as he replied in displeasure: ”How can I accept this without even trying? Star Constellation Immortal Venerable is the number one wisdom path expert, she had such ease in plotting against us. If Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable revives, she will have an even easier time.”

“How can we deal with a wisdom path Gu Immortal? We need to exterminate them! We cannot give a wisdom path Gu Immortal any time to make arrangements. Our current situation is the best proof of this!”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable asked in response: ”Then in your opinion, what should we do now?”

Fang Yuan gritted his teeth: ”Plunder Central Continent and slaughter the people, I don’t believe that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable will let it happen! Even if she can, after Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable revives, he will only gain a barren region!”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable shook his head.

Such an act was too brutal and demonic, it did not suit his nature.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had his reservations.

If he did this, when Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable retaliate by slaughtering the Huang Jin tribes, what would he do?

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had another thought: ”Fang Yuan wants me to stand on the same side as him, if I participate in slaughtering the people of Central Continent, there will be no way of reconciling with Heavenly Court, my demonic path status will be permanent.”

Without any reconciliation, there would be no room for a truce.

The pressure of two venerables would weight on his shoulders. He was not like Fang Yuan, who was cold and unconcerned with his subordinates’ lives.

“I have Longevity Heaven as my base, even if all three venerables of Heavenly Court revive, I can still defend myself. This is my foundation for a negotiation!”

“But Fang Yuan is all alone, he has no such base.”

“This is a huge problem to him, thus, he wants me to join him.”

“If I do not participate in this, in the future, Heavenly Court will target Fang Yuan as their priority, I will have more time to cultivate. It is still not the time to go all-in now.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable thought of this and rejected Fang Yuan’s proposal.

But Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not want to offend Fang Yuan, he explained: ”I can’t bring myself to do such a thing like killing all the people. I’ll advise you not to do this personally, there’s a more suitable person. I’ll lure him to you now.”

“Coward!” Fang Yuan shouted: ”All you care about is useless reputation!”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not show any anger, he understood why Fang Yuan was feeling upset and angry after getting schemed against.

He lured Spectral Soul Demon Venerable to Fang Yuan, who landed in Central Continent in response.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was not like Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, he did not let Fang Yuan down. After leaving spectral heaven, he went into Central Continent and started his massacre.

This was within the expectations of Fang Yuan and Giant Sun.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s injuries were severe, but he could heal himself by slaughtering lifeforms and hunting soul beasts to increase his strength. He had done this in spectral heaven earlier, now, the situation was similar. Heavenly Court.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had been paying attention to the two venerables’ actions.

After seeing that Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was killing all the lifeforms in Central Continent, she sighed deeply. But after seeing that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable left Central Continent to return to Northern Plains, her eyes shone brightly as joy filled her heart.

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals could not understand why.

Even if Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not want to invade Heavenly Court, he would at least ransack Central Continent for some resources, right?

But he left directly.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was clear of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s intention.

She spoke to Golden Hooped Great Immortal: ”Your effort back then has finally paid off. This is the best result for us.”

In the past, Golden Hooped Great Immortal had invited Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to tour Heavenly Court and wanted to recruit him to become their fourth Immortal King.

His plan failed and even allowed Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to leave a luck path method as a backdoor to Heavenly Court, causing them huge losses during the fate war.

But in fact, the truth was that Golden Hooped Great Immortal’s action had a certain impact on Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. In his heart, Heavenly Court had once tried to recruit him, they even tried to make him their leader. In that case, there was a possibility of negotiating with them to come to a peaceful truce.

Chapter 2327: Primordial Origin’s Revival

After hearing Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s words, many of the Gu Immortals gained some realization.

“Now it seems that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable is still a righteous path person in essence.”

“He is indeed quite different from Fang Yuan, be it in terms of action or ideology. Fang Yuan is brutal and casually sacrifices his subordinates, he treats everything as his tool. But Giant Sun Immortal Venerable is different, he cares for his descendants and is someone with deep kinship.”

“Hmph, in my opinion, he has far greater foresight than Fang Yuan. If he acts like Fang Yuan, he will have no chance of appeasing Heavenly Court, he will be our mortal enemy. Thus, he has already started planning to express his goodwill towards Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable!”

“From what I see, this is all Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s plan. She did everything to defend Heavenly Court and allowed Fang Yuan to ransack Central Continent. The truth is, I was quite unhappy about it. But now, it seems that this was only part of her plan, it managed to make Giant Sun leave Central Continent of his own accord. This is an incredible outcome! Sigh, I should not have tried to evaluate Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s wisdom with my shallow view.”

Qi Sea Ancestor’s eyes were shut, he was motionless like a statue, floating quietly in Heavenly Court.

Above his head, Star Constellation Chessboard orbited and released a pale blue light that enveloped his body.

After some preparation, the entrance of Qi Sea Ancestor’s immortal aperture started to open, the immortals cheered loudly.

Afterwards, rank eight heaven qi Immortal Gu flew out of his immortal aperture first.

After that was earth qi Immortal Gu, followed by various qi path Immortal Gu.

The immortals were in a commotion.

“Even though Qi Sea Ancestor is strong, against Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, he is only meat on the chopping block.”

“Self-detonating Immortal Gu is so easy, but right now, the pseudo venerable Qi Sea Ancestor has been completely controlled by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, he can’t even do something as simple as self-detonating his Immortal Gu.”

“Once Lord Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable revives, these qi path Immortal Gu will allow him to recover a portion of his strength, Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable has truly planned it perfectly!”

The immortals praised in succession.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had clearly suppressed Qi Sea Ancestor completely, she controlled his mind and used her thoughts to replace his.

Thus, she was able to open the immortal aperture’s entrance and suppress all of the Gu worms inside.

Of course, these qi path Gu worms still belonged to Qi Sea Ancestor, they were filled with his will.

It was much more difficult for Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to get rid of his will than controlling Qi Sea Ancestor’s mind directly. These Immortal Gu did not have a mind, to get rid of their lingering will of Qi Sea, the best solution would be to directly refine these qi path Immortal Gu.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not plan to do that.

She only suppressed these Immortal Gu and prevented them from self-detonating, she kept them for her master, Primordial Origin, to deal with personally.

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable was a qi path Gu cultivator, it was better for him to deal with these qi path Immortal Gu.

After all the Immortal Gu were retrieved, it was time for the secluded domain of heaven and earth, Hu Land.

Once Hu Land appeared in front of everyone, Heavenly Court erupted with an intense wave of cheers.

This was a qi path secluded domain of heaven and earth!

It was spoils of battle comparable to rank nine Immortal Gu!!

Qi Sea Ancestor’s Hu elevation killer move used Hu Land as the core.

A secluded domain of heaven and earth was very hard to destroy, it was much easier to obtain than Immortal Gu. Since Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could even suppress Qi Sea Ancestor’s Immortal Gu, obtaining Hu Land was a natural thing.

“With this secluded domain of heaven and earth, even if master has no rank nine Immortal Gu in his treasury, he can still display the might of qi path.”

While feeling satisfied, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not forget to inspect these Immortal Gu and the secluded domain of heaven and earth.

Fang Yuan was vigilant, so was she.

Even in Heavenly Court, she was not being careless at all.

After using all her methods to inspect them over a hundred times, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable confirmed that these Immortal Gu and the secluded domain of heaven and earth were not tampered with.

Afterwards, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable placed these loot into the immortal formation and suppressed them.

This was her final step of precaution.

Fang Yuan was a refinement path venerable, he might have some methods that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could not decipher. But with these loot being suppressed in the immortal formation, even if Fang Yuan’s method activated, it would be detected by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable immediately, she would have time to counter them.

“Even if Fang Yuan has any method that I have not detected, it is not a big deal, I can suppress anything with the immortal formation.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was filled with confidence regarding this.

Back then, she had even used He Feng Yang to undergo Immortal Gu transactions with Fang Yuan.

Was she not afraid of Fang Yuan tampering with them?

Of course she had such worries.

But the concern was quite small, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was confident in noticing Fang Yuan’s methods. Other venerables like Giant Sun Immortal Venerable would also have such confidence.

Their confidence was not baseless.

Refinement path was too broadly cultivated in the whole world.

The advantage was that refinement path developed immensely, many refinement path Gu worms could advance to rank nine. The weakness was that everyone knew how to refine Gu, they had a certain understanding of refinement path.

Heavenly Court had existed for three million years, while Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was a wisdom path venerable, how could she not know the refinement method of fake Gu?

Such an action was common in the mortal Gu Master world!

If Fang Yuan made fake Gu, even if Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not cultivate refinement path, she would notice it.

Of course, if Fang Yuan had sufficient time to develop, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would not dare to take a risk in this aspect.

She would be incredibly cautious towards any Immortal Gu that Fang Yuan had contacted!

After Qi Sea Ancestor’s Immortal Gu and Hu Land were taken out, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable took out various resource points from Qi Sea’s immortal aperture.

Most of the qi path resource points were kept inside.

The ones that were taken out had one similarity, they all had a lot of non-qi path dao marks.

After finishing this, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable started to use her killer moves.

She had created these wisdom path killer moves herself, nobody else knew of them except her.

After more than ten killer moves were used, Qi Sea Ancestor’s immortal aperture and mind started to break down, all sorts of qi path resource points and his entire body started to turn into qi currents.

A massive number of qi currents were gathered together, forming into the vague shape of a qi harvest fruit.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s eyes shone with brilliance and wisdom, she used three killer moves consecutively, eliminating Qi Sea Ancestor’s will, thoughts, and remaining emotions in the qi harvest fruit.

Qi Sea Ancestor’s soul was taken out and kept in the Immortal Gu House Soul Suppression Hall. This Immortal Gu House was once used to hold Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, it was too easy to contain Qi Sea’s soul now.

The qi harvest fruit slowly stabilized.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable stopped her various wisdom path methods, carefully drawing Star Constellation Chessboard away from the location.

Even without Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s support, the qi harvest fruit was becoming clearer and more stable.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable inspected it carefully and relaxed. As she had expected, the qi harvest fruit was in sync with Primordial Origin’s methods now, she did not need to do anything else.

She could not interfere anymore or it could be an issue. After all, there were conflicting dao marks, she cultivated wisdom path and star path, not qi path.

The best situation was to allow Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s methods to activate and trigger his revival.

“After three million years, Lord Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s methods are still effective! I am truly in admiration.”

“There are no issues left, Lord Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s revival is imminent!”

“It was my fault.” The newly revived Qin Ding Ling came over and said with an expression of guilt: ”If I was not muddled and let Qi Sea Ancestor take Heavenly Court’s qi harvest fruit, the first venerable to revive would have been Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable!”

Everyone consoled her upon hearing this.

Even Star Constellation Immortal Venerable looked over at her: ”Qin Ding Ling, no need to blame yourself. You are not a wisdom path Gu Immortal, while Fang Yuan is extremely crafty and has even deceived the world, it was not your fault that you failed to deduce Qi Sea Ancestor’s true identity.”

“Even I would make mistakes sometimes. The important thing is that you learn from your mistakes and grow, you must continue to look forward bravely, that is the true behavior that we should follow.”

“We will remember Lady Immortal Venerable’s teachings!” The immortals responded in unison.

The qi harvest fruit soon grew to the size of a mountain.

Qi Sea Ancestor’s qi path foundation was converted into the qi harvest fruit. After it stabilized, it was even larger than the one that Fang Yuan made back then.

As time passed, the qi harvest fruit continued to grow stronger.

In the past, the Heavenly Court immortals would be terrified of this scene. But now, they looked towards the qi harvest fruit with anticipation and excitement.

Primordial Origin’s revival process, which had been interrupted by Fang Yuan in the past, was restarting now.

Not long after, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable frowned. She noticed that the qi harvest fruit’s growth was slowing down.

“Something is wrong.” She quickly inspected.

The entire inspection process was slow and careful, she did not want a powerful investigative method to affect Primordial Origin’s revival process.

The Heavenly Court wisdom path dao marks that she refined were very useful in this case, she soon found the reason.

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable had left many methods in Heavenly Court that were related to his revival. For example, the primordial qi wall.

“Master’s plan must have been to use the qi harvest fruit from the qi tides to revive himself. He arranged all sorts of qi path methods in Heavenly Court as a form of assurance. When the qi harvest fruit lacks nutrients, these qi path methods would be used to supplement it.”

However, because of the various battles that occurred, these qi path methods were greatly expended. Thus, its growth was slowed now.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had no way to make these qi path methods recover to their original state.

But after thinking about it, she quickly found a replacement method.

After all, these qi path methods were meant to support the qi harvest fruit’s growth.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable immediately ordered for all of Heavenly Court’s qi path immortal materials to be taken out while she made deductions.

Not long after, her expression turned pale, she was covered in perspiration, but she produced a qi path immortal formation.

The foundation of this qi path formation were the qi path methods from Primordial Origin, it was quickly completed under Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s arrangements.

Afterwards, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable placed a large number of qi path immortal materials into the immortal formation.

As the qi path immortal formation activated, it was quickly reduced into all sorts of qi currents that were condensed together, before being instilled into the qi harvest fruit through Primordial Origin’s arrangements.

After the boost of nutrients, the qi harvest fruit started to grow rapidly again.

But this did not last long, Heavenly Court’s storage of qi path immortal materials was quickly expended, they were about to run dry again.

Chapter 2328: Explosion!!!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable saw the issue, the qi path immortal materials were insufficient, her expression turned dim.

Heavenly Court’s foundation had finally hit rock-bottom!

In fact, when she set up the star array calculation formation and nurtured the immemorial star beasts, she had already expended all of Heavenly Court’s star path resources.

Recently, Heavenly Court’s members revived continuously, the remaining immortal graveyard was also consumed until only a small area was left, it could no longer allow any Gu Immortal to revive.

Heavenly Court had developed for three million years, it had incomparable foundation, but after several huge battles, the expenditure was severe. When Spectral Soul Demon Venerable escaped from Heavenly Court, he ransacked the immortal treasury. They had to use their secret storage and even subtly draw resources from the ten great ancient sects.

Until today, Heavenly Court was already showing signs of exhausting its foundation.

Of course, the main reason why they were out of qi path resources was because the immortal material expenditure was just too high.

In Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s original plan, the qi harvest fruit would primarily grow using the qi tides, the qi path methods he left behind would only be a failsafe in case any unexpected mishaps occurred.

The qi tides were crucial in growing the qi harvest fruit.

But now, the qi tides had ended and the qi paths methods were not completely intact, they had to expend qi path immortal materials instead.

It was obvious that the more qi path immortal materials they expended, the larger the qi harvest fruit would become, and the stronger Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable would be after reviving.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable made deductions again.

She used her full strength in doing this, countless thoughts collided in her mind until she felt a sharp headache, but she eventually deduced another killer move.

After testing it, she modified the killer move slightly.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s breathing was quite rough and her expression was pale, she opened the entrance of Heavenly Court at the next moment.

Before any other venerable reacted, she aimed her killer move at the entrance.

Heavenly Court’s entrance was immediately covered by a layer of profound light as it rapidly drew in heaven and earth qi from the outside world.

The heaven and earth qi were vast and boundless, they entered through the entrance with unceasing momentum and flowed into the immortal formation.

The heaven and earth qi were not of high quality but could compensate with quantity, with this supplement, the growth of the qi harvest fruit was no longer an issue.

The Heavenly Court immortals were shocked, they quickly discussed.

“Why did Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable open the entrance of Heavenly Court?”

“This is a good thing, the stronger the qi harvest fruit, the more powerful Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s qi path foundation will be after revival!”

“What if Fang Yuan attacks using this chance?”

“Hahaha, didn’t he try to attack earlier, losing to Lady Star Constellation’s divine might. Will he dare to come again?”

Fang Yuan did not show up indeed.

Not only that, even Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was not paying attention to them.

He ravaged Central Continent and slaughtered countless beings, his injuries recovered by a large extent.

Soul fog surged, wherever it went, verdant mountains turned grey and flowers wilted, wild beast corpses were lying all over the place.

As his soul howl was used, huge waves appeared on the lakes. Afterwards, corpses of aquatic animals like fish or shrimps floated to the surface.

A vast number of souls were devoured by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, he was like a huge black hole that devoured everything he slaughtered, his injuries were healed and his body expanded again.

During this process, a wild Immortal Gu was created in Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s body.

Rank eight Immortal Gu — Kill!

This caused a considerable commotion that drew the attention of Fang Yuan, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

At once, the three venerables had strange expressions.

They knew about a secret of the past.

Back then, Spectral Soul wanted to create killing path, but in the end, he failed after devouring black heaven’s heavenly spirit, he was forced to create soul path instead.

But to think that he showed signs of creating killing path now while he was not sane.

Immortal Gu Kill was clearly the core Immortal Gu of killing path, it was not formed so easily.

This was a Gu refinement undergone by the Heavenly Dao!

Most importantly, it was refined in Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s body, this meant that although he was currently not sane, he was quite close to creating killing path.

“Killing path is already showing signs of emerging.” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had already returned to Northern Plains, he immediately ordered the Huang Jin tribe Gu Immortals who were headed to Central Continent to not get near Spectral Soul Demon Venerable! They should not be greedy with super resource points, also avoiding Heaven Refining Demon Venerable.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not personally plunder Central Continent’s resource points but he did not give up, he sent his bloodline descendants.

This way, even if Heavenly Court pursued the matter, he had a degree of distance and could give excuses.

“Giant Sun, if you come and cooperate with me, I’ll give you half of the Central Continent resource points that I plunder!” Fang Yuan transmitted again, he did not give up on convincing Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable rejected with an increasingly firm attitude.

On one hand, he felt that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would not expose a weakness, this outcome was already decided, there was no point in joining hands with Fang Yuan.

On the other hand, he had his own reservations.

Firstly, his eldest son You Tian Guang was taken away by You Tian Guang in Longevity Heaven, he needed to look for his son.

Secondly, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had already used ’I reside in all living beings and heaven and earth’ twice in a short period, this move had a huge drawback, it would leave him in a weakened state for some time. He had to conceal himself and secretly get through this weakened period. If he exposed this weakness, the killer move’s value and usability would fall immensely in the future.

Heavenly Court.

The qi harvest fruit continued to grow larger.

The vast amount of heaven and earth qi, countless qi path immortal materials, as well as methods like the primordial qi wall, were all turned into qi path dao marks that were added into the qi harvest fruit.

At the core of the qi harvest fruit, a human shaped core was formed.

As time passed, the core’s features became clearer, it was increasingly human-like.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable saw this and immediately comprehended that Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s revival method contained the profundity of human path.

“To think that master’s human path attainment is even higher than I thought.”

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable smiled faintly as memories surfaced in her mind.

In his bed, Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable suddenly coughed out blood.

“Master, how are you?” Star Constellation quickly came over and used her methods to heal him.

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable had just blocked a chaotic disaster and fixed the hole in the world, he was heavily injured and could barely get up.

Star Constellation did her best to stabilize his injuries.

She had a look of surprise, she found that Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable aggravated the injuries purely as a result of his own actions!

Star Constellation frowned deeply: ”Master, you suffered such heavy injuries and can’t even walk now, yet you still took a risk to create a killer move!”

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable had a look of joy: ”These injuries are not an issue, my disciple, I succeeded. I grasped onto that inspiration and created a human path killer move.”

“Using this move, we can use the immortal aperture to extend the lifespan of Gu Immortals. Among all the existing lifespan extension methods, my newly created method is the most effective!”

Star Constellation looked at the content and had a gaze of surprise, light flickered in her eyes as she understood the true value of this killer move.

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable laughed loudly: ”With this method, we will not need to force human Gu Immortal experts to join our Heavenly Court. The temptation of lifespan extension is too great.”

“From now on, as long as they contribute their immortal aperture to Heavenly Court, they will become members of Heavenly Court. They will get to use this human path killer move to extend their lifespan.”

Star Constellation nodded, she was joyous as well: ”Master, what is the name of this killer move?”

“Cough, cough.” Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable coughed before saying nonchalantly: ”The name is not important, you can decide it for me, just make one up.”

Star Constellation quickly answered, she loved to name things, she added: ”We need to give it an awesome name, it should draw people’s attention! Hmm... let me think about it.”

“My good disciple, go and think of the name! I am too old now, I don’t have the creativity anymore. After you decide, let me know.” Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable rested in bed and waved his hand to Star Constellation.

Star Constellation nodded and said solemnly: ”Master, you must not take such risks again, your injuries are too severe this time!”

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable laughed to himself: ”These injuries are nowhere near my limit. I’ve once suffered even greater injuries, you know it too, there has been at least five of such instances.”

Star Constellation stared angrily: ”You are already twenty-five thousand years old, you need to admit you are old. You’ve already done enough for humanity, since you are injured, you need to recuperate. I will lead Heavenly Court!”

“Hahaha, with you around, what worries do I have?” Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable laughed as his voice became softer, he showed an expression of dejectedness: ”Maybe, I should really admit that I am too old...”

“You won’t.” Star Constellation shook her head, she showed an expression of knowing her master very well but being helpless against his antics.

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable laughed after seeing her expression, while she was taking her leave, he even winked at her playfully.

Star Constellation took care of Primordial Origin, who was recuperating while handling Heavenly Court’s affairs, in her free time, she thought of the name of the human path killer move to relax her mind.

Star Constellation was busy for three days, after that, she finally had some insight about the name of the human path killer move.

But she did not know that she would not have a chance to tell Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable about this name anymore.

When she freed herself from her busy work and went to visit Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, she saw that he was lying on the bed quietly, his eyes were shut and his expression was plain, there was only a faint smile at the corners of lips.

This legendary leader of humanity, the first generation Immortal King of Heavenly Court, the person who held up the banner of humanity’s retaliation and forced all the variant human forces to hide themselves, had passed away.

He died calmly.

Peacefully.

Relieved.

His disciple was the reason why he was relieved.

The moment Star Constellation saw Primordial Origin again, she realized.

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s injuries were extremely severe, he had only purposely concealed the fact.

He was making considerations for the big picture.

After all, although the variant humans retreated from Central Continent, they were still rampant in the other four regions. Even in Central Continent, many variant human forces hid in their blessed lands and grotto-heavens, they could not be found.

He knew his injuries could not be healed, using the last of his strength, he painstakingly created a human path killer move to aid the future development of Heavenly Court.

Star Constellation stood in front of Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s bed and kept silent for a long time.

Eventually, she spoke in a hoarse voice: ”Master, I’ve already thought of the name for this human path killer move. It suits this scenario quite well, I’ll name it — Lying in Bed.”

Lying in bed was able to turn the immortal aperture that a Gu Immortal contributed to Heavenly Court into a bed that was free from calamities and tribulations, it could also extend their lifespan to a great extent. Back in that era, it was the number one lifespan extension method besides lifespan Gu!

Afterwards, Star Constellation created another human path killer move on the foundation of this move, naming it — Others Sleep Soundly.

Others sleep soundly allowed the Heavenly Court members to sleep on their respective beds and reduce their body activity and time flow to the lowest possible limit. At the same time, their will would be extracted and converted into human nature[1. Opposite of heaven nature Spectral Soul is filled by, see 2265] to help Star Constellation Immortal Venerable resist heaven’s will after she assimilated with the Dao.

At the final moments of his life, Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable lay in bed and contributed his final moments to the future of Heavenly Court and all of humanity.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did the same, in order to protect Heavenly Court, she sacrificed herself and became one with the Dao.

This pair of master and disciple were truly of the same lineage!

Lying in bed and others sleep soundly became the foundation of Heavenly Court’s immortal graveyard.

Within the qi harvest fruit, the human shaped core had already grown to the size of a normal human adult.

There was a change in the qi harvest fruit’s skin as well, countless primordial qi walls formed and wrapped around the core of the qi harvest fruit.

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s revival was already reaching the final steps.

The methods displayed during this process made Star Constellation Immortal Venerable quite surprised, she gasped and sighed at the intricacy of Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s qi path methods.

As time passed, a wave of grand aura permeated the qi harvest fruit.

The qi path dao marks that were created from heaven and earth qi, along with the qi path immortal materials, were added to the qi harvest fruit continuously.

The human shaped qi harvest fruit was already showing Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s form.

Many Central Continent Gu Immortals were currently kneeling.

Heavenly Court’s members had tears in their eyes, they were incredibly excited.

He was the first venerable of the world, among them, he was also the one with the longest lifespan.

Without him, humanity would not have its current prosperity, he was the person who led the rise of the human race!

He was the creator of qi path and had left behind countless methods to defend Heavenly Court, including primordial qi wall, lying in bed, and others.

He had defeated countless variant human experts, he had suffered countless injuries, who knows how much blood he lost in the process.

He created Emperor City, which was the incomplete form of Divine Emperor City.

He was the first to contribute his immortal aperture, he gave up on the clan system and recruited disciples, he was the role model of Central Continent’s sect system.

He worked his hardest and gave his life to Heavenly Court and all of humanity.

Even the variant humans who hated him to the core had to admit that he was a grand existence.

He was Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable!

And today, he was going to return to this world.

The qi harvest fruit started to tremble as a grand aura leaked out, creating huge qi waves.

The entrance of Heavenly Court opened as this aura was exposed to the outside world.

At once, within spectral heaven, qi currents either fell, moved together like a storm, or even created all sorts of vortexes and whirlpools.

A peculiar phenomenon was formed as the five regions went into an uproar!

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s revival was almost completed.

Finally, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable let out a sigh of relief and knelt on one knee as she said: ”This disciple pays respects to master.”

Within Northern Plains, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable sighed, the outcome was decided.

Fang Yuan, however, stared at Heavenly Court. He frowned with a vague hint of anticipation and excitement in his eyes.

At the next moment.

Boom!!!!!!!

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable — exploded!

In Northern Plains, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable stood on the spot, he looked in the direction of Heavenly Court with uncontrollable shock on his face.

Meanwhile, Fang Yuan had a faint smile.

Chapter 2329: Fang Yuan’s Scheme To Blow Up Heavenly Court

This huge explosion was too sudden, it had occurred too fiercely!

At once, winds soared and clouds dispersed, heaven and earth changed colors.

Heavenly Court shattered!

A large number of grotto-heaven fragments flew everywhere like a volcanic explosion. Only half of the immortal aperture entrance remained, there were all sorts of holes and gaps everywhere, exposed in spectral heaven.

Dust and smoke rumbled, Heavenly Court could not be seen clearly now.

An unknown number of Gu Immortals had died.

The only thing that could be confirmed was that the mountain-like qi harvest fruit had dissipated entirely.

“I succeeded...” In Central Continent, Fang Yuan looked in the direction of Heavenly Court and let out a breath of air.

Long ago, he had already started to consider this issue.

At that time, he was in a predicament with danger all around him.

The sovereign immortal aperture’s time flow was too fast, this forced Fang Yuan to undergo tribulations. Although he had used endless trouble multiple times to delay his tribulations, the chaotic disaster could not be skipped by this method.

Once Fang Yuan underwent tribulation, he would need to place his sovereign immortal aperture in spectral heaven and open his immortal aperture’s entrance for some time.

This would expose a huge flaw and lure Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to attack him, even Spectral Soul Demon Venerable might come!

Other than the danger of tribulation, Fang Yuan also felt hunger.

This was the sovereign immortal body’s hunger.

The sovereign immortal body was created using sovereign immortal fetus Gu, the flaw was that it needed to consume an immortal aperture of the same rank as the Gu Immortal once in a while.

Now that Fang Yuan was a venerable, he would need to annex a rank nine immortal aperture!

These two crises made Fang Yuan extremely worried.

As the saying went: If one did not have big worries, they would worry about smaller things.

Fang Yuan had great foresight, he could also anticipate his future problems. Rather than leaving these issues to the future, he should start resolving them now!

Fang Yuan did not have a passive nature, he enjoyed taking the initiative to launch the first attack and control the situation!

Fang Yuan knew one of Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s revival methods.

The reason was simple.

The killer move stealing heavenly secret.

Back then, Fang Yuan used the immortal ascension of his Gu Immortal seeds to experience natural inspiration and use stealing heavenly secret to inspect all the secrets within Heavenly Court!

He knew the profundities contained in the qi harvest fruit were meant to revive Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable.

Even Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was unclear of the exact details regarding the qi harvest fruit revival method.

But Fang Yuan had a clear understanding of Heavenly Court, along with his qi path great grandmaster attainment level, he made deductions and research with wisdom Gu’s help.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable made arrangements within the star array calculation formation, her methods were precise and meticulous. The intention was to use both Embroidered Tower and Star Constellation Chessboard to capture a pseudo venerable.

This arrangement was done secretly, Fang Yuan did not know of it.

But he did not need to guess to know that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would definitely try to revive Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable!

If he were in her shoes, it was certain that he would prioritize in reviving the other two Immortal Kings of Heavenly Court.

Things were difficult to do openly, but easy to do secretly. Once Star Constellation Immortal Venerable made a move, her every action would expose her intention.

Heavenly Court had deep foundations, it was under the rule of three Immortal Kings. This was Heavenly Court’s greatest strength, but to Fang Yuan, it also was their greatest weakness.

Thus, Fang Yuan thought of sacrificing Qi Sea Ancestor to purposely lure Star Constellation Immortal Venerable into using the qi harvest fruit revival method.

Even if Qi Sea Ancestor was his clone, so what?

For the goal of eternal life, what could he not sacrifice?

For the sake of his grand ambition, would Fang Yuan be stingy on such a sacrifice?

The plan to give up Qi Sea Ancestor and use him as bait to revive Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable was quite likely to succeed.

But he needed a chance to send Qi Sea there.

He could not do it openly.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was the number one person in wisdom path, Fang Yuan had experienced her strength countless times, she often saw through his plans when they were still at their initial stage. There was a clear example previously with Fang clan.

If he did it in a way that was too obvious, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable would notice and use the plan against him, causing Fang Yuan huge losses.

Thus, he waited until the opportunity presented itself.

Undoubtedly, the heaven path dream realms appeared at the best timing!

For Fang Yuan’s case, although the heaven path dream realms could raise his heaven path attainment level, he was not anxious to get them.

As long as nobody could make use of these heaven path dream realms, he could continue to refine rank nine Immortal Gu secretly, to raise his strength and pull apart his distance from the other venerables.

The longer this dragged on, the stronger Fang Yuan would become.

But the contest over the heaven path dream realms became the best red herring to conceal his scheme to give up Qi Sea Ancestor to the enemy!

Fang Yuan thought a lot about this, he made difficult choices.

He could not act too willing, everything had to be logical.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s intelligence was unfathomable, she was too smart. But her wisdom was something that Fang Yuan could make use of!

Thus, Fang Yuan sent Qi Sea Ancestor into the star array calculation formation and did not do anything excessive. Afterwards, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable personally ’helped’ Fang Yuan and completed the arrangements for him, capturing Qi Sea Ancestor.

Throughout the process, Qi Sea Ancestor was kept in the dark by Fang Yuan, he was unaware.

Not just him, Wu Shuai and Zhan Bu Du did not know either.

It was like how Star Constellation Immortal Venerable deceived the five immortals from Heavenly Court regarding the plan to take Lin Jian Xing’s otherworldly sword path dao marks.

But Fang Yuan was even more ruthless, he even deceived himself.

Giving up the Qi Sea clone was not enough, to assure Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, he even gave up the qi path Immortal Gu and Hu Land.

So what if he had to give up these qi path Immortal Gu?

As long as he could achieve his goal, Fang Yuan could even give up rank nine Immortal Gu!

Hu Land... wasn’t it just a secluded domain of heaven and earth?

If it could deceive Star Constellation Immortal Venerable for some time, not to mention one secluded domain, he would even give up three if he had to.

In Fang Yuan’s eyes, the so-called Immortal Gu and secluded domain of heaven and earth, no matter how precious, were just tools for him to go after eternal life.

Since they were tools, if there was value in sacrificing them, he would do it!

Fang Yuan had no hesitation regarding this.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable only had a vague understanding of the qi harvest fruit revival method, but Fang Yuan knew it clearly.

He was a refinement path venerable, he was also proficient at revival methods.

From the perspective of refinement path, the qi harvest fruit revival method was just using the qi harvest fruit as the main material, along with Primordial Origin’s arrangements in Heavenly Court, to create a new body and soul.

Was it any different from Gu refinement in essence?

No!

In that case, Fang Yuan could make his arrangements.

He first treated Qi Sea Ancestor as a qi path immortal material and processed some steps in advance. Of course, the corresponding memories were already removed from Qi Sea Ancestor.

It was like how Star Constellation Immortal Venerable altered the memories of the Gu Immortals who entered the derivation formation.

Qi Sea Ancestor’s entire body was tampered with, but this was related to the peak profundities of refinement path, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could not detect anything even after checking many times.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had refinement path attainment too, but Qi Sea Ancestor looked normal on the surface, there would only be issues after he was used as an immortal material for the qi harvest fruit revival method.

And during the process of revival, the problem would intensify.

But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not completely understand or control the qi harvest fruit revival process.

This gave Fang Yuan many chances to take advantage of the situation!

“My plan succeeded, as for the gains, it will depend on future developments.” Fang Yuan did not rush to attack Heavenly Court.

He continued to plunder Central Continent while contacting Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

“Giant Sun, we are so lucky! A problem happened during Primordial Origin’s revival, Heavenly Court blew up instead. This is our best opportunity to strike, if we miss this and Heavenly Court recovers, we will regret not taking action for life.”

After seeing Heavenly Court’s explosion, after a momentary shock, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable immediately thought of attacking Heavenly Court.

After getting Fang Yuan’s transmission, he became even more tempted.

But he was hesitant now.

“Should I really attack Heavenly Court now?”

“Did they really make a mistake? Is Fang Yuan behind this?” Giant Sun Immortal Venerable thought of Fang Yuan’s mysterious defensive method, he really could not see through this person. It was possible that Fang Yuan was behind this all along.

“Strange, why did I not sense this huge variable earlier when I used luck inspection on Heavenly Court?”

“Unless, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used a method to conceal Heavenly Court and it stopped my luck inspection from working? That would really be ironic.”

The last thing that made Giant Sun Immortal Venerable hesitate was Light Emperor.

His eldest son.

As well as the wild rank nine light Gu in his immortal aperture!

Light Emperor was kidnapped by the two legendary immemorial beasts, You Tian Guang and Zuo Ye Hui, if Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not go to save him, he would be in danger.

Of course, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable thought of his own Blood Sea.

Since he could revive Light Emperor once, he could definitely do so again.

“Giant Sun is still hesitating, did he notice anything?” Fang Yuan saw that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was not taking any action, he started to ponder.

Fang Yuan did not know about the secret behind Giant Sun and his son, he also did not know about the drawback of using the killer move, I reside in all living beings and heaven and earth.

But he soon thought of a reason.

“With the explosion, Heavenly Court’s losses cannot be assessed now. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s injuries are unclear as well. She has a huge territorial advantage inside Heavenly Court, she must not have gotten too injured, so she is still a threat.”

“This may be Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s concern.”

“In his opinion, my Qi Sea clone was captured and Heavenly Court suddenly exploded, which caused Primordial Origin’s revival to fail, so I am the most suspicious one. At the same time, I should be the most nervous person.”

“I do not have my own stronghold, if Heavenly Court’s two venerables join hands, I will be in an even worse predicament.”

“Giant Sun Immortal Venerable said the situation is unclear, he is hinting to me that I should make a move first!”

“If Heavenly Court is truly weakened, he will come and join in the fight to steal some benefits himself.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable chose to wait and observe, this made Fang Yuan’s plan fall short.

In fact, attacking Heavenly Court now was abrupt and contained risks.

Even Fang Yuan did not know what condition Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was currently in.

But since Fang Yuan had already planned this far, would he not have backup solution?

He casted his gaze at Spectral Soul Demon Venerable who was far away.

After this period of killing, his injuries had mostly recovered.

“He is the best vanguard that we can have.” Fang Yuan smiled as he used his method.

Totem killer moves flew out and provoked the insane Spectral Soul Demon Venerable continuously, he was successfully lured into Heavenly Court!

Chapter 2330: Almost Suffering Amnesia From The Explosion

With a soft grunt, Zhao Lian Yun woke up in an area of ruins and rubble.

All she saw were qi currents in front of her, the entire place was covered in white, in all directions.

Her ears were buzzing, she felt dizzy and lightheaded.

“What... what happened to me?”

Zhao Lian Yun breathed roughly as she inspected her body.

She was originally wearing a white dress, she had light skin and white teeth, as refreshing as lilies in the morning. But now, her face was blackened like soot, her white dress was torn and tattered. She was like a refugee living in a famine, having a wretched appearance.

After checking, she found that her body was intact but she had no strength at all, her limbs felt weak and powerless.

“What happened? Why am I like this?”

Primordial Origin’s explosion occurred too suddenly and abruptly, Zhao Lian Yun suffered a huge impact and almost experienced amnesia!

But soon, her dizziness faded away and Zhao Lian Yun slowly regained her memories.

An unprecedented and terrifying explosion had occurred!!!!

Her pupils contracted, this scene was etched in her mind and would not be forgotten in her entire life.

It was too terrifying!

A moment ago, the many Gu Immortals around her were watching the mountain-like qi harvest fruit with immense anticipation for Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s revival.

But at the next moment, Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable exploded!

Among all of the Gu Immortals, Zhao Lian Yun was standing near the periphery, but she was still affected by the explosion.

This explosion was too intense, the whole of Heavenly Court was in ruins, Zhao Lian Yun naturally could not escape.

“Why did it explode all of a sudden?!” As her memories cleared up, Zhao Lian Yun’s breathing became rougher.

“I can’t believe it, I am practically unharmed. Did love Gu protect me?”

“Wait... I need to save the rest!”

Zhao Lian Yun’s heart jumped, she realized what she should be doing.

She might have had love Gu’s protection, but others did not have a rank nine Immortal Gu like her.

Zhao Lian Yun quickly set off as she went into the vast field of qi currents, searching for other surviving Gu Immortals.

Before the explosion occurred, the Gu Immortals of the ten great ancient sects were all at the periphery, they were far apart and watched the qi harvest fruit in small groups. The people who were closer to the center were the members of Heavenly Court.

White qi rumbled like a vast fog, Zhao Lian Yun tried many investigative methods but none worked.

These white qi were remnants of the qi harvest fruit, the aftermath of the explosion! With the area being filled with qi path dao marks, it was not strange that a mere rank six Gu Immortal like Zhao Lian Yun was unable to use investigative methods, unless she could use love Gu now.

But love Gu was not just a rank nine Immortal Gu, it was very special. Even a venerable could not refine it forcefully, even though it was wisdom path, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had not been able to use it. Thus, it continued to live in Zhao Lian Yun’s body.

Zhao Lian Yun did not refine love Gu but received its acknowledgement instead. Thus, she could not activate it freely, sometimes, she wanted it to attack but it would escape with her. If she wanted it to defend, it might heal instead.

Furthermore, each time love Gu was used, it would take something away from Zhao Lian Yun, sometimes, it would even take lifespan!

Zhao Lian Yun flew into the white qi and looked around for people using her memories of the location.

After a while, she gasped as she found Bu Zhen Zi.

When the explosion occurred, he was standing beside her, they were talking.

But after the explosion, they were sent flying and left their original spot.

But he was still the first person she found.

Bu Zhen Zi’s injuries were terrifying.

Half his body was blown away, only his fragile skeleton was left protecting his heart. He only had two internal organs left, the rest were blown to smithereens.

The remaining half of Bu Zhen Zi’s body had turned into a phantom state, his limbs, chest, and internal organs were linked by a translucent thread, he seemed to be in a stable condition.

Zhao Lian Yun wanted to save him but found that she was helpless to do anything.

The injuries were just too severe!

The missing half of his body was not important, forget about Heavenly Court, even Spirit Affinity House had many ways to regrow his bones, organs, and flesh.

But the issue was the large number of qi path dao marks that were carved on his body.

The remaining half of his body emitted dense white smoke made of white qi, his remaining organs and bones were also slowly turning into qi.

What kept him alive was the phantom state that half of his body was currently in.

“When the explosion occurred, Bu Zhen Zi used a phantom path method, but even with this semi-invulnerable state, he could not avoid the injuries caused by this explosion.”

Zhao Lian Yun deduced the situation that happened and sighed deeply, worry and frustration could be seen on her face.

Bu Zhen Zi was kept alive by his half phantom body, but this would not last long. The qi path dao marks were going to affect it soon, slowly turning everything into qi.

“Bu Zhen Zi can’t last much longer...” Zhao Lian Yun was helpless, she felt increasingly anxious.

She tried to wake him up but Bu Zhen Zi remained unconscious.

Zhao Lian Yun did not even dare to move Bu Zhen Zi, she was afraid that he would die from the smallest impact.

She had to temporarily abandon him and remember this spot, before going back into the white qi fog to look for others.

“Is anyone here? Please help!”

Zhao Lian Yun moved around in the vast white qi fog.

She called out continuously, the feeling of loneliness and helplessness soon assaulted her in this situation.

She was still in disbelief.

When she came earlier, she looked at the layers of buildings and saw how grand and majestic Heavenly Court was, she felt surprise and admiration from the depths of her heart. Heavenly Court’s immense foundation was accumulated through countless years of history, she felt tiny and insignificant, while also having a sense of security in this place.

When she witnessed the gradual revival of Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, she felt that Heavenly Court was regaining its former glory!

But then, Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable exploded.

It was too sudden and too abrupt!

“What happened? Did Fang Yuan or the other venerables attack?”

“What are Heavenly Court’s losses?”

“Can anyone come to help me? At least respond with a word!”

Zhao Lian Yun suddenly stopped moving, there was an intense suction force coming from in front of her, the surrounding white qi currents were sucked in.

Zhao Lian Yun barely stabilized her footing as she slowly got close.

The suction force was becoming gradually weaker.

After Zhao Lian Yun reached the source, her pupils contracted as she saw an immortal aperture’s entrance!

The entrance was open and drawing in white qi from outside, after stabilizing, a blessed land was formed.

Zhao Lian Yun stood before the immortal aperture’s entrance in a daze, motionless.

She saw the scenery inside the entrance, there were rivers and flower trees. Under the waves of qi currents, petals fell from the trees and fell into the rivers, flowing downstream where the carps waited to eat the petals as food.

This was the scene of Fairy Liu Fang’s immortal aperture, it was extremely beautiful and valuable, it was quite famous in Spirit Affinity House.

Fairy Liu Fang was in charge of the secret inheritance peak, she was a neutral faction supreme elder in Spirit Affinity House.

Zhao Lian Yun remembered that the first time she went to secret inheritance peak, Fairy Liu Fang did not attend to her personally which was the rule as she was the current generation fairy.

Afterwards, their relationship had always been plain.

However, no matter how distant they were, seeing this immortal aperture entrance, Zhao Lian Yun’s eyes turned red, she felt an intense feeling of sorrow in her heart.

She was dead.

Fairy Liu Fang died during the explosion.

Although she had rank seven cultivation level, she did not have the defensive power of phantom path, she did not have love Gu either.

Not a single trace of her remained, her immortal aperture landed in Heavenly Court. Because Heavenly Court was filled with heaven’s will and had no heavenly spirit, Liu Fang blessed land was formed by taking in heaven and earth qi from outside to stabilize itself.

Zhao Lian Yun barely managed to control her emotions, she continued to look around for help.

Along the way, she saw many immortal aperture entrances which were currently taking in heaven and earth qi.

There were too many deaths!

“Not mentioning the Heavenly Court members, Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects sent more than ten Gu Immortals each. Not counting the captives in the star array calculation formation, there are over a hundred Gu Immortals from the ten sects in Heavenly Court now.”

“This explosion killed eighty percent of the Gu Immortals!”

Zhao Lian Yun calculated, she felt her heart turning cold.

The ten great ancient sects of Central Continent had many Gu Immortals, before the five regions became one, Immortal Crane Sect alone had twelve Gu Immortals, and this was one of the weakest sects among the ten.

After the five regions became one, the earth veins moved while qi tides appeared, producing countless immortal materials. This caused many Gu Immortals within the sects to become stronger, the Gu Immortal seeds also had deeper foundations.

During the wave of immortal ascension, many Gu Immortal seeds in the ten great ancient sects succeeded in becoming Gu Immortals. Aside from them, there were also other Gu Immortals recruited from outside.

For example, supreme elder Wu Zhang from Heavenly Lotus Sect recruited the Wood Virtue Elder Mu Huai from the Five Virtues Sect. After the latter became an immortal, because he was a higher-up of the Five Virtues Sect that Wu Zhang created, he was qualified to enter Heavenly Lotus Sect.

This was the advantage of Central Continent’s sect system.

Earlier, to ensure Primordial Origin’s revival, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable gave up everything else in the process. To prevent Fang Yuan’s retaliation, she brought all the elites of Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects into Heavenly Court.

But to think that Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable would explode upon revival, like this, many of Central Continent’s Gu Immortals died, the pillars of Central Continent’s righteous path collapsed.

Such a terrifying loss made Zhao Lian Yun’s arms and legs turn weak.

“Doomed, Central Continent is doomed.”

“Maybe Heavenly Court can still revive them?” Zhao Lian Yun was hopeful.

But she was not stupid, the more she thought about it, the more she sensed that there was a huge scheme behind this explosion!

Central Continent was plotted against.

Heavenly Court fell into a trap!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable also fell for a scheme!

Although Zhao Lian Yun had rank nine love Gu, she was only rank six, what could she do?

She could only get help, she shouted loudly.

Zhao Lian Yun started walking slower and slower.

At this moment, she felt that she was so weak!

“Don’t be dejected, current generation fairy of Spirit Affinity House, Heavenly Court is still around, we are also still alive.” Right at this moment, there was a lantern that brightened inside the vast white qi.

The lantern was not bright but it was stubborn, it forced its way out of the white qi and arrived before Zhao Lian Yun.

It was an elderly Gu Immortal, his body was bloodstained from head to toe.

One of his arms was gone from the explosion, his remaining arm was carrying a small fire in his palm.

Zhao Lian Yun recognized him, it was Immortal Crane Sect’s Old Lord Can Yang.

Chapter 2331: Pitiful Survivors

Old Lord Can Yang was a famous expert in Central Continent, his reputation was long established.

Zhao Lian Yun looked at him, some information surfaced in her mind. After becoming the current generation fairy of Spirit Affinity House, because she could not undergo tribulations, her cultivation level could not rise. She could only spend her time on other things, thus, she had a clear understanding of most characters in Central Continent’s Gu Immortal world.

Zhao Lian Yun knew that that Old Lord Can Yang had the Immortal Gu Flickering Flame, he created an amazing immortal killer move called life chasing fire, it was renowned in Central Continent.

Old Lord Can Yang rarely moved around these last years, he had been staying in seclusion.

The most significant thing he did recently was to investigate the truth behind the fall of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building in Northern Plains with Feng Jiu Ge, they fought against Shadow Sect there.

And recently, Old Lord Can Yang won the contest against Zhang Ji.

Zhang Ji was a Gu Immortal from Black Heaven Temple, although he was a relatively unknown expert, he had a unique method to counter flames. In the end, he still lost to the fire path cultivator Old Lord Can Yang.

Although the lantern in Old Lord Can Yang’s hand was weak, it produced a warm feeling in Zhao Lian Yun’s heart instantly.

Many people were like this, they were often fragile and weak when they were lonely.

But if a companion appeared, even if this person was useless, the company they provided would still create a sense of warmth and safety in their heart.

Zhao Lian Yun was such a person.

She was an otherworldly demon who was not originally from this world. Her nature was already like this before she came here, that was one of the reasons why she felt so attached to Ma Hong Yun after receiving his care and concern.

Zhao Lian Yun breathed in deeply, the look of dejectedness on her face quickly faded away as she asked Old Lord Can Yang for help, she explained Bu Zhen Zi’s condition.

But Old Lord Can Yang shook his head slowly: ”I cultivate fire path, my understanding of phantom path is very shallow, I am not skilled in healing methods. There is nothing I can do.”

Once he said that, Old Lord Can Yang’s body started to shiver at an observable level.

His face turned pale as paper.

At the same time, white qi appeared on his body, it was most dense around the wound on his arm that was cut off.

“Cough cough.”

Old Lord Can Yang continued to cough, each time, blood was coughed out.

The blood fell to the ground and turned into white qi, quickly dissipating.

Old Lord Can Yang gritted his teeth and activated his method, this situation lasted for over ten breaths of time before he suppressed his wounds again, color returned to his face and his coughing stopped.

His methods were only usable on himself, or rather, only fire path Gu Immortals, they would not work on Bu Zhen Zi. In fact, they could make his condition worse.

Next, Old Lord Can Yang and Zhao Lian Yun moved together.

Along the way, they saw more immortal aperture entrances, which were open and absorbing white qi wildly.

They also saw some people who were alive.

There was a giant monkey lying on the ground, he was like a small mountain.

The monkey was originally covered in golden hair, like there was armor on the body. But now, half the body was blackened, he was like a fallen general who had lost his armor.

His muscles were originally strong and tough, he looked very powerful and brave, but now, his body was covered in mushy flesh and blood, bones could be seen on his deeper wounds, he sprawled on the ground and could not get up.

The monkey had a pair of golden eyes that were shining with pressuring brilliance, but now, his gaze was scattered and lost, he only regained some spirit after seeing Zhao Lian Yun and Old Lord Can Yang.

“What? He is Combat Immortal Sect’s Immortal Monkey King Shi Lei. He cultivates earth path and transformation path, he is currently using his signature killer move — Rock Mountain Immortal Monkey King Transformation!” Zhao Lian Yun was stunned, having recognized the monkey’s identity instantly.

Shi Lei was the publicly known number one rank seven Gu Immortal in Central Continent, his battle strength was even higher than Old Lord Can Yang!

But he was even closer to the explosion than Old Lord Can Yang, after it happened, he did not have time to activate his rock mountain immortal monkey king transformation.

This was a compound killer move of two paths, it expended a lot of thoughts.

Shi Lei did not have wisdom path foundation, he needed a lot of preparation to use this move.

He used other methods to survive the explosion, afterwards, because he could not heal himself, he had to use this move to turn himself into an ancient desolate beast. Using the physique of an ancient desolate beast, its self-recovery allowed him to endure these injuries and barely survive.

After seeing Old Lord Can Yang and Zhao Lian Yun, Shi Lei blinked at them with his golden eyes as a greeting.

He did not even dare to breathe heavily now, it would be a problem if his injuries were worsened.

Evidently, Shi Lei could only protect himself now, he could not help others.

“Cough, cough.” Old Lord Can Yang coughed again, blood could be seen again. A moment later, he suppressed his injuries again.

Zhao Lian Yun and Old Lord Can Yang continued on their journey.

Not long after, they met Yang Feng.

He was a rank seven Gu Immortal of Ancient Soul Sect, he cultivated transformation path. Like Shi Lei, he had also turned himself into an ancient desolate beast.

The originally majestic giant wolf was lying on the ground like a beaten dog.

But his injuries were less severe than those of Shi Lei, he could still talk to Zhao Lian Yun.

He was not stronger than Shi Lei, but during the explosion, he subconsciously used the transformation killer move that he was most familiar with and turned into an ancient desolate beast.

He cultivated transformation path solely, he was most familiar with this giant wolf transformation, it was almost like his instinct. Thus, it could be used rapidly, almost activating in an instant.

“My greatest injury is my spine, if I exert it even a little, my spine will break.”

After Yang Feng explained his situation, he joined Zhao Lian Yun and Old Lord Can Yang’s group.

The three of them continued to search, soon, they found Vicious Lightning Fiend.

Vicious Lightning Fiend also had rank seven cultivation level, his body was covered in lightning as he floated in the air, three Lightning Deities surrounded his body and assisted in healing him.

While healing, lightning crackled around him as sparks were created, causing quite a commotion.

“I was fortunate.”

“Right before the explosion occurred, I watched while having my Lightning Deities revolve around me to leave a good impression on Lord Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable.”

After the explosion, although there were more than ten Lightning Deities earlier, only four remained. To save his life, Vicious Lightning Fiend sacrificed another Lightning Deity to heal himself. Now, only three were left.

This was a huge loss for him.

“The killer move Lightning Deity was created by Vicious Lightning Fiend using the incomplete Immortal Gu recipe of Blood Deity. When the qi tides swept the world and the five regions became one, immortal materials appeared, which allowed Vicious Lightning Fiend to receive a lot of funding from Myriad Dragon Dock, he quickly accumulated many Lightning Deities. With more than ten Lightning Deities which had rank seven Gu Immortal battle strength each, he was known as a top expert among rank seven Gu Immortals in Central Continent, only being inferior to Shi Lei.”

Zhao Lian Yun recalled as she greeted Vicious Lightning Fiend.

Vicious Lightning Fiend’s bad temper was famous, but now, he was very polite to Zhao Lian Yun.

Seeing that her injuries were the lightest, he acknowledged her strength.

This explosion killed most of Central Continent’s Gu Immortals, the remaining ones were either lucky or sufficiently strong!

But there was an awkward thing.

Gu Immortals with greater battle strength often did not excel in healing. They were adept at healing themselves but not others.

Thus, even though Vicious Lightning Fiend joined this group, they still had no way to help Bu Zhen Zi or Shi Lei.

As time passed, the white qi fog that obscured everyone’s vision became less dense.

These white qi were qi path immortal materials, but nobody had the mood to collect them.

The blessed lands or even grotto-heavens left behind by the Central Continent Gu Immortals who died were absorbing a large amount of white qi. At the same time, white qi also flowed out of Heavenly Court through the gaps that formed.

In any case, the vision of the immortals was returning.

“Wait.” Yang Feng, who had turned into a giant wolf and needed to rest every few steps, suddenly spoke.

Everyone was used to it.

Along the way, he had been asking for them to stop once in a while to lie down and recover his strength.

His waist injury was too severe, the wound was huge as well, one could see his kidney from the exposed wound.

White qi was flowing out of his kidney.

“Yang Feng, is your waist hurting again?” Zhao Lian Yun cast a concerned gaze at him.

Yang Feng nodded: ”Of course my waist hurts, but more importantly, there are people coming from behind us.”

“Indeed, there are three of them.” Old Lord Can Yang’s gaze flickered as he noticed.

“Cough, cough.” After saying that, he started coughing blood again.

“Our allies?” Vicious Lightning Fiend asked while mobilizing his thoughts, the three Lightning Deities quickly spread out towards the sky behind them.

Zhao Lian Yun and the rest stopped moving, they started at the stirring white qi.

The three Lightning Deities waited solemnly, but suddenly, one spun around on the spot, one flew up into the sky, while the final one twisted its body around like it was having a spasm from a lightning shock!

Chapter 2332: Heavenly Court’s Resolve

Zhao Lian Yun and the others quickly cast a look of surprise at Vicious Lightning Fiend.

Vicious Lightning Fiend’s face turned red, this was a rarely seen expression, he explained: ”The Lightning Deities are damaged from the explosion, due to the qi path dao marks carved on them, they are hard to control. If my concentration falls, they will go berserk.”

Everyone gasped in realization.

They were slightly anxious earlier as they thought the Lightning Deities were being attacked by a mysterious method.

A few breaths of time later, Old Lord Can Yang relaxed and said: ”They are our comrades.”

Soon, two rank eight Gu Immortals appeared before the group.

They were rank eight supreme elders from Heaven’s Envy Manor and Spirit Butterfly Valley.

The immortals saw them and became joyous.

These were rank eight Gu Immortals after all, the supreme elders had countless methods in their possession, they managed to stabilize Yang Feng and Old Lord Can Yang’s injuries, but the effect was not great.

While the group of immortals discussed how they would continue saving others, white qi surged and moved like it was pushed aside by a huge blood-red beast.

Soon after, the vague figure of blood appeared from within the white qi, it was the rank eight Immortal Gu House — Demon Judgment Board!

Gu Yue Fang Zheng was controlling it from within, after seeing the immortals, he stopped.

Rays of blood-red light shot out of Demon Judgment Board and landed on everyone.

They did not resist and let Gu Yue Fang Zheng heal them.

Their injuries healed to an extent, but heavy injuries could not become small injuries.

Although Demon Judgment Board was a rank eight Immortal Gu House, it specialized in investigation, its combat prowess and healing ability were far weaker.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng thought about it and said to the ten children of human path inside the Immortal Gu House: ”The situation is dire, friends, may I ask you to go around to help heal the rest?”

“Lord Fang Zheng, please don’t say that, the ten great ancient sects are all subsidiaries of Heavenly Court, we are all of the same faction. We will do our best to help the rest!” The ten children of human path quickly responded.

They were lucky to have avoided the explosion as they had entered Divine Emperor City earlier.

Divine Emperor City was damaged by Shen Shang and Lu Wei Yin earlier, afterwards, it flew into Heavenly Court along with Fei He Mountain and others.

There was no helping it, if it remained in Central Continent, Fang Yuan’s main body would destroy it.

Genesis Lotus’ will controlled Divine Emperor City, he was confident in blocking Shen Shang and Lu Wei Yin, but against Fang Yuan’s main body, the outcome would be different.

Divine Emperor City was the sacred land of human path, it had a large number of mortals and Gu Masters. The painting worlds were the best places to develop human path, during this period of time, there were many new results.

The ten children of human path were all rank six human path Gu Immortals now, they were ordered by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to enter the painting worlds of Divine Emperor City and cultivate.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng was also deployed by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to enter Divine Emperor City. He was not there to comprehend human path, he interacted with Genesis Lotus’ will to learn painting path instead.

Earlier, Fang Zheng had entered the derivation formation and comprehended the essence of painting path, he could use the style of painting path to unleash various blood path killer moves through Demon Judgment Board, causing his strength to rise greatly. This caused Gu Yue Fang Zheng’s interest in painting path to increase greatly, because Star Constellation Immortal Venerable noticed his talent and prospect in painting path, she did not stint on nurturing him.

Although Gu Yue Fang Zheng was from Southern Border, due to Fang Yuan, he was nurtured by various leaders of Heavenly Court like Qin Ding Ling and even Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. Thus, his cultivation level had been rising explosively the entire time.

The ten children of human path felt admiration and closeness to Fang Zheng.

Fang Zheng’s strength was greater than them, he was also the current generation Demon Judgment Board Lord. Although he only had rank seven cultivation level, he was already a member of Heavenly Court and had won many battles. With his status and identity, the ten children of human path who wanted to join Heavenly Court admired him.

As for closeness, Fang Zheng’s age meant that he and the ten children of human path were of the same generation.

Thus, after Fang Zheng made the arrangements, the ten children of human path accepted the task and flew out of Demon Judgment Board to help Zhao Lian Yun and the rest.

“It was really fortunate that you juniors with only rank six cultivation level stayed in Divine Emperor City and managed to survive.”

“Oh? So this is a human path method.”

“It is truly... profound beyond words!”

“No wonder Heavenly Court is putting all its effort into developing human path, it truly has unlimited potential.”

Old Lord Can Yang and the rest knew who the ten children of human path were. Initially, they still put up airs and acted like seniors, but soon, their expressions and attitude changed as they started to praise in amazement.

Human path was very unique, the healing methods of the ten children of human path were human path methods, but they were still effective on Zhao Lian Yun and the others.

Their injuries were originally quite severe and had only been suppressed, even with the help of two rank eight Gu Immortals and Demon Judgment Board’s healing, they did not recover by a large extent.

But now, with the human path killer moves, their conditions improved rapidly with immediate effect.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng nodded as he saw that the immortals were recovering with the help of the ten children of human path, he quickly went to the inner area using Demon Judgment Board.

Along the way, he saw many immortal aperture entrances, Fang Zheng’s expression was solemn as his heart sank, he felt worried: ”Most of the Gu Immortals in Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects are dead, but the immortal graveyard is almost completely expended, how are we going to revive them?”

“Recalling the situation, the qi harvest fruit exploded too suddenly, there must be a huge scheme behind it.”

“I wonder what happened to the Heavenly Court seniors?”

“The most important person is still Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. Her current condition will determine the future of Heavenly Court and the whole of humanity!”

Gu Yue Fang Zheng had undergone many ordeals, his foresight was sharpened and he had a clear understanding of the situation.

The inner area had much denser white qi than the outside.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng was very anxious, under his control, Demon Judgment Board moved even faster by thirty percent now.

Soon, he saw the immortals of Heavenly Court.

Fang Zheng’s eyebrows first eased before frowning again.

He found that many of Heavenly Court’s Gu Immortals were around, but some were missing, it was unknown if they had died.

Heavenly Court’s Gu Immortals were strong after all, ten people had already gathered here.

They were standing around Qin Ding Ling.

Fang Zheng quickly left Demon Judgment Board and greeted the immortals.

Qin Ding Ling nodded at him before looking around and starting to hand out instructions.

She had a haggard expression, there was still bloodstains on her lips, but when she spoke now, there was a hint of authority.

The white qi fog obscured everyone’s vision and investigative methods, with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable missing now, Qin Ding Ling had no choice but to take the role of leader.

After the immortals discussed this, she split them into three groups.

One group was led by Ruan Dan, they searched for surviving Gu Immortals while collecting information to collate data of Heavenly Court’s losses.

One group was led by Duke Mei, they ventured into the center of the white qi zone to search for Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

The final group was led by her, there were Che Wei, Wan Zi Hong, Red Heart Traveler, Nine Spiritual Fairy, and other Heavenly Court Gu Immortals with outstanding battle strength. Because Fang Zheng had Demon Judgment Board, he was in this group as well.

Their group would leave Heavenly Court and guard the vicinity to defend against any possible attacking foes!

“Master.” Gu Yue Fang Zheng brought Red Heart Traveler into Demon Judgment Board and said respectfully: ”Let me heal your injuries!”

Red Heart Traveler nodded and sat down, floating in the air.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng utilized Demon Judgment Board to fly out of Heavenly Court while using its methods to heal Red Heart Traveler.

Red Heart Traveler was originally pale as paper, but with the help of Gu Yue Fang Zheng, he quickly recovered, his aura stabilized.

He was a blood path Gu Immortal, the former Demon Judgment Board Lord, Gu Yue Fang Zheng also cultivated blood path, their dao marks did not conflict so the healing effect was outstanding.

While Red Heart Traveler was healing, Gu Yue Fang Zheng informed him of everything that he saw.

Red Heart Traveler nodded with a solemn expression: ”Heavenly Court suffered huge losses, there are gaps everywhere now, even during the fate war, there had not been such a severe damage.”

Gu Yue Fang Zheng asked the question that he wanted to know about: ”Master, was this explosion an accident or... the scheme of someone?”

Red Heart Traveler shook his head: ”I can’t say for sure. Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s revival methods have already existed for over three million years, it may not have an issue but Heavenly Court went through countless battles, these methods are no longer complete. Furthermore, the five regions unified and the world went through huge changes...”

“But if someone did this, then Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Heaven Refining Demon Venerable are the most suspicious. Between them, Heaven Refining Demon Venerable is the most likely culprit!”

Saying so, Red Heart Traveler looked at Gu Yue Fang Zheng.

Fang Zheng gritted his teeth but did not speak.

Heaven Refining Demon Venerable was his brother.

“Regardless of whether this is a scheme or not, we are going to have an intense battle now! Fang Zheng, you need to prepare yourself.” Red Heart Traveler did not continue the topic, he started to inform Fang Zheng with concern.

Fang Zheng nodded as his expression turned stern. Now that Heavenly Court had such huge damage, it was likely that Heaven Refining Demon Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable would attack, they would not let this chance slip by.

One could say that Heavenly Court was in immense danger now.

Red Heart Traveler told him to prepare himself, Fang Zheng knew that it meant the preparation to sacrifice his life!

Regarding this, Fang Zheng was resolved.

Not only him, the other Heavenly Court Gu Immortals also had the same resolve.

Suddenly, Demon Judgment Board shook as red lights shone, it was an alert.

Red Heart and Fang Zheng’s expressions changed.

Demon Judgment Board excelled in investigation, it was the first to obtain the new information.

A series of totems flew around and provoked a huge mountain-like monster to approach Heavenly Court.

“The enemy appeared!” Fang Zheng shouted: ”It’s Spectral Soul Demon Venerable!”

Soon, the other Gu Immortals also noticed this, Qin Ding Ling and others gathered.

“Damn it, Fang Yuan did this!”

“This shameless and unscrupulous person!!”

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was completely insane, but the totem killer moves were Fang Yuan’s signature method. The situation was very clear, the Heavenly Court immortals looked with bloodshot eyes, they were extremely furious.

Qin Ding Ling contacted Duke Mei, but as the white qi was too thick, communication was tough.

The center of the huge explosion was filled with qi path dao marks, Duke Mei and the rest moved with difficulty, but they did not find any trace of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Qin Ding Ling had a cold expression but her stable tone had a sense of patriotism: ”Although spectral heaven is huge, Heavenly Court is right behind us, we cannot retreat! Everyone, we must use all our effort to destroy the totems and lure Spectral Soul Demon Venerable away!”

Before she finished her words, she charged forward without any regard for her life!

There was no shouting or screaming, Wan Zi Hong, Che Wei, and Demon Judgment Board followed after her.

Bam bam bam...

A huge battle soon erupted, it got intense immediately.

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals gave it their all, they were injured to begin with, this battle caused their injuries to become more severe as blood spewed everywhere.

The totems were destroyed by them.

The results were outstanding!

However, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable sensed the aura of Heavenly Court and roared loudly as he took the initiative to attack Heavenly Court.

Qin Ding Ling and the rest resisted with all their might but they were completely helpless against the advancement of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

At once, the Heavenly Court immortals fell into despair.

Author’s Note: For the following battle, there will be many characters involved, it will be more exciting after including them. The interaction of these characters will make the Gu world more vibrant and lively. Fang Yuan’s following actions will also create huge fatal danger for them, they will experience great unforgettable changes in their lives.

Chapter 2333: Three Venerables Attack Heavenly Court!

“One step more, just one small step!” Duke Mei shouted in his heart.

He was surrounded by surging white qi, the qi path dao marks were so dense that the Heavenly Court expert Duke Mei could barely move a single step!

He had to use all his effort to move forward by a small step.

The immortal essence expenditure was huge, Duke Mei not only had to resist the pressure of the white qi, he also had to block the corrosion of the qi path dao marks.

“Senior Duke Mei, I’ll take over!” A Heavenly Court Gu Immortal shouted from behind.

Duke Mei gritted his teeth but he still made a small advancement of a tiny step before stopping and fixing his position desperately.

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortal behind quickly used a killer move to get around Duke Mei and become the new vanguard of the group.

By the time this group reached the original location of the qi harvest fruit, they found Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Her clothes were messy and her hair was disheveled, there was blood flowing out of her lips and eyes, she seemed to be in a daze?

Duke Mei and the rest were shocked, they had never seen such an expression on Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s face.

“Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable!” Duke Mei shouted and used an immortal method to transmit to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable shook as she showed a reaction.

At the next moment, starlight burst out and suppressed the surrounding white qi with ease.

Duke Mei and the rest immediately felt the pressure lifting off their bodies, it was as if a mountain had been lifted away from their backs.

Starlight continued to sweep through the white qi, after a few breaths of time, the white qi rampaging in Heavenly Court were all suppressed by the starlight!

“This is the might of a venerable!” Duke Mei and the rest saw this as they felt internally shaken.

“When the explosion occurred, I remember seeing a rapidly rising star veil that protected us. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable must have taken action to block most of the force of this explosion.” Several immortals recalled.

Next, they stared with wide eyes as they saw the human shaped qi harvest fruit core.

Although the qi harvest fruit exploded, the core was still around!

However, despite the qi harvest fruit core having a human shape, it was no longer as lively as before, it was blurry and unstable, with qi path dao marks leaking out at all times.

The white qi that covered Heavenly Court were produced by the leaking qi path dao marks of the qi harvest fruit core.

Right now, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable displayed the power of a venerable and forcefully pushed these qi path dao marks back into the qi harvest fruit.

Because of this, the qi harvest fruit core stabilized, its appearance became clearer again.

“We still have a chance!”

“Yes, we can still revive Lord Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable!!”

After noticing this, Duke Mei and the rest were excited.

In just a short period, starlight gathered and turned into a soft stardust cloth, it wrapped around the human shaped qi harvest fruit core like a bandage.

After a few breaths of time, there was over a hundred layers of bandage, the core could no longer be seen.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable let out a breath of air as she stopped the killer move.

Drip drop.

At this time, blood flowed out of her nose.

The bleeding did not stop, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s face turned increasingly pale.

When the qi harvest fruit exploded, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable activated several killer moves.

The advantage of wisdom path was an abundance of thoughts to allow the user to use more complex killer moves.

Just by looking at this, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was truly the number one person in wisdom path, her status could not be threatened by anyone.

On one hand, she protected herself and the other Gu Immortals to ensure their safety, on the other hand, she directly suppressed the qi harvest fruit core.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had blocked most of the force of the explosion, otherwise, Heavenly Court’s Gu Immortals would have all perished.

And most importantly, she retained some hope.

Without her, the qi harvest fruit core would have exploded, Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s revival would have failed completely.

Immortal killer move — Luck Slicing Golden Blade!

Qin Ding Ling chased after Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, she shot out a small golden blade.

The golden blade was only the size of a thumb, it flew into the air and grew larger as it moved, quickly reaching the size of a horse carriage.

Swish swish swish.

The golden blade swung down, in an attempt to slice off Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s luck.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable ignored the attack, he only focused on entering Heavenly Court.

The horse carriage-sized golden blade danced above his head, it was simply like an ant compared to Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s colossal black mountain-like body.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s massive luck was reduced by the luck slicing golden blade.

Of course, the effect was insignificant compared to the sheer size of his luck!

Qin Ding Ling felt a sense of helplessness.

Che Wei, Red Heart Traveler, and Gu Yue Fang Zheng all had the same feeling.

Despite Demon Judgment Board shooting out beams of blood-red light continuously, it only managed to fracture a few of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s arms, in just a few breaths of time, they recovered completely.

The difference between rank nine and eight was too massive, even with the full strength of Qin Ding Ling and the others, they could not affect Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

After the huge massacre, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had already recovered by a large extent.

During normal times, if Qin Ding Ling and the rest provoked Spectral Soul Demon Venerable like this, he would definitely attack them. But now, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s only goal was Heavenly Court!

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was filled with heaven’s will, he had once devoured black heaven’s heavenly spirit, so after the two heavens fused, he became the ruler of spectral heaven.

Before that, he had destroyed the heavenly chasm, heavenly pillars, and the various white heaven grotto-heavens (like Flickering Light grotto-heaven), he even went as far as to destroy the sun, it was all to unify the two heavens.

Heavenly Court was a grotto-heaven situated in immemorial white heaven, it had also annexed countless nine heavens fragments in the past, it was the greatest tumor in the immemorial nine heavens in the first place.

The existence of Heavenly Court itself was the greatest provocation to Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, he would not allow its existence!

Rumble...

With a loud rumble, the mountain-like Spectral Soul Demon Venerable created a huge gap and broke into Heavenly Court by force.

The whole of Heavenly Court was shaking!

The Central Continent Gu Immortals who were still in Heavenly Court looked up and saw Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s colossal body, they all gasped in shock.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was flying above them now, he cast a huge shadow on everyone.

Thousands or even tens of thousands of arms formed a terrifying forest of limbs, they were raised up or lowered, some were tucked in while others were straight, it showed the stance of grasping the sun and moon, it had the potential to catch stars and whip up storms.

Qin Ding Ling and the rest chased him from behind like tiny mosquitoes. Even the rank eight Immortal Gu House Demon Judgment Board was merely a mouse in front of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

Roar—!

One of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s three heads started to roar.

Immortal killer move — Soul Howl!

He used a soul path killer move, boundless sound waves started to spread.

Wherever the sound waves reached, a tornado blew the tiles of Heavenly Court away. Zhao Lian Yun and others felt like a disaster was approaching, many of them quickly took out their Immortal Gu Houses.

At once, there was a display of Immortal Gu Houses.

Scattered Stars Camp, Thin Willow Camp, Wind Sweeping Building, Cloud Passing Building, Sun and Moon Temple, Spirit Affinity House, Myriad Dragon Dock, Heaven’s Envy Manor, Ancient Soul Sect, Heavenly Pool, Illusion Garden, Canary Pavilion, Yue Yang Palace, Immortal Crane Sect...

Central Continent’s ten great ancient sects all had their own Immortal Gu Houses to defend them, their respective names were derived from their strongest Immortal Gu Houses[1. Sect in these names also is read as gate which refers to the Gu Houses being buildings with large gates.].

Among them, Heavenly Lotus Sect was the most unique one, because it was created by Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable, it had a total of five Immortal Gu Houses, the highest among the ten ancient sects.

When the Immortal Gu Houses were not in use normally, the respective sects’ first supreme elders would keep them inside their immortal apertures. If the first supreme elders were unavailable, other authoritative experts would undertake the responsibility.

These people had all basically survived.

Immortal Gu Houses of all shapes and sizes shook intensely from the huge impact of the soul howl sound waves, they were like ships in a storm, about to capsize at any moment.

Within some of the Immortal Gu Houses, low growling noises could be heard from the Gu Immortals. These Immortal Gu Houses had weak defenses against soul path.

Boom boom boom.

With a series of explosions, several Gu Immortals’ souls exploded from the force of the sound waves, dying on the spot.

These Central Continent Gu Immortals were not in their peak condition, they were all injured. Some of the ones with severe injuries survived the earlier explosion but could not endure the soul howl, they lost their lives.

Qin Ding Ling and the rest were wavering in the air, being on the brink of life and death.

They had suffered huge injuries to begin with, they had even taken a risk earlier to quickly destroy Fang Yuan’s totem killer moves, it was already a miracle that they were still alive now!

At the moment of crisis, starlight shone brightly like the boundless sea, pressing towards Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

The soul howl stopped at once, it was like someone was strangling Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

“Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, don’t be too brazen.” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had a cold expression as she flew towards Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable opened his mouth as black smoke gathered, he spat out a grand soul river.

There were countless vengeful souls in the soul river, they flowed towards Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

At the same time, his countless arms grabbed towards her, many monstrous claws gathered to firm sharp spear tips that pierced the air, the attack was fast and brutal, shocking deities and devils!

The starlight only suppressed Spectral Soul Demon Venerable for a few breaths of time before breaking apart.

But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not dodge, she snorted coldly as star fog appeared, permeating the black smoke that quickly dissipated, while the fog continued to break apart the soul river.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s claws extended into the star fog but failed to catch anything.

Even though he grabbed Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, the latter shattered like a star illusion.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable did not give up, he continued to rampage in the star fog and growled continuously, echoing in the whole of Heavenly Court.

Qin Ding Ling and the rest quickly landed on the ground, they hid themselves in the Immortal Gu Houses and used their time to heal.

Zhao Lian Yun and the other Central Continent Gu Immortals watched with palpitating hearts.

The battle of two venerables was too ferocious. The aftermath of any single move could topple Immortal Gu Houses and cause many Gu Immortals inside to die.

Thankfully, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had been suppressing Spectral Soul Demon Venerable during the entire fight, she held firm control over the situation.

“This is the might of a Dao Lord!”

“Heavenly Court is still around, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable has a huge amplification when she fights in here, thus, she can easily suppress Spectral Soul Demon Venerable.”

“Of course, the crucial factor is that Spectral Soul Demon Venerable has lost his sanity.”

“Unless the rank nine fire Gu in his body activates, he will not break out of this predicament.”

Fang Yuan watched from afar and contacted Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

“Giant Sun, what are you hesitating for?”

“Primordial Origin’s revival had a hitch, but hope remains. Right now, we must join hands and work with Spectral Soul Demon Venerable to destroy Heavenly Court, it is our best chance!”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable hesitated: ”We should observe further.”

Fang Yuan snorted coldly: ”If you still want to stall for time, you must have allied with Star Constellation Immortal Venerable secretly. In that case, I won’t be able to stop Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s revival. I will fight my way into Northern Plains and slaughter all the Huang Jin tribes.”

“You dare?!”

“Why won’t I? You have Longevity Heaven while Star Constellation has Heavenly Court. If you want to drive me to desperation, will I just give up and die? I will not let either of you off!” Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, showing a look of insanity and desperation.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable snorted coldly: ”Fine, I’ll ally with you, we must destroy the qi harvest fruit core!”

Fang Yuan let out a breath of air, praising: ”This is a wise choice, please act quickly, I’ll wait for you to enter the battlefield.”

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable gritted his teeth and set off from Northern Plains.

Fang Yuan was calm and composed, he slowly rose into spectral heaven from Central Continent.

“Oh no, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Heaven Refining Demon Venerable are approaching Heavenly Court!” Within Heaven Overseeing Tower, a Gu Immortal spoke with a trembling voice, transmitting the information.

At once, Qin Ding Ling, Gu Yue Fang Zheng, Che Wei, Zhao Lian Yun, Old Lord Can Yang, and the rest had changes in their expressions.

Although they had expected this, when it truly happened, they could not help but be flustered and feel fear.

“Three venerables are attacking Heavenly Court at once! Can we... stop them?” The immortals had such a question in their mind.

Chapter 2334: Fang Yuan and Giant Sun Fight Star Constellation

Intense wind blew as Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s hair fluttered behind her.

She frowned slightly as the image of Heavenly Court was reflected in her dark pupils.

In her memory, Heavenly Court had never been in such a distressed state.

The star fog got denser as Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, who was trapped inside, growled and roared, he was increasingly furious and insane, but he could not escape from the star fog.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was bullying Spectral Soul Demon Venerable’s lack of sanity, if he was conscious, he would not do such a thing.

She was currently inside Heavenly Court, with the amplification of the wisdom path dao marks, she was completely above Spectral Soul Demon Venerable in power.

If Spectral Soul Demon Venerable fought without any intention to retreat, it was likely for Star Constellation Immortal Venerable to use the territorial advantage to kill him!

But Star Constellation Immortal Venerable showed no joy on her face.

Ever since the qi explosion, she knew that Heavenly Court’s greatest danger was not the insane Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, but Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Heaven Refining Demon Venerable.

Between the two, Heaven Refining Demon Venerable was the most threatening.

Although Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had no evidence regarding the explosion of the qi harvest fruit, she was clear that Fang Yuan was the most suspicious one.

He would not let this chance slip by.

Neither would Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

If Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable revived, the balance of the three venerables would be overturned, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable would not want this to happen. Earlier, he withdrew because there was no hope.

But now, the situation changed after the explosion, Heavenly Court was covered in holes, it was basically defenseless.

The only concern that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had was Star Constellation Immortal Venerable herself.

But in order to protect the qi harvest fruit core, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable endured most of the force of the explosion, she was currently injured.

Furthermore, she could not defeat Spectral Soul Demon Venerable in a short period of time, this gave Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Heaven Refining Demon Venerable sufficient time to probe her current condition.

As expected, once Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used her star fog to trap Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Heaven Refining Demon Venerable arrived.

In the battle regarding the dream realms in spectral heaven earlier, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had allied with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, but now, she was all alone against the assault three venerables.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable floated in the sky quietly, she watched as Fang Yuan and Giant Sun arrived.

Her gaze swept past Giant Sun and fixed on Fang Yuan, she said: ”Heaven Refining Demon Venerable, you are worthily a refinement path venerable, you tampered with the qi harvest fruit to cause the explosion. But I have one question, how are you so clear of my master’s revival arrangements in Heavenly Court?”

Fang Yuan was first stunned before laughing: ”Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, you are overestimating me. Remember, the current world is no longer like ancient times, the five regions have become one while the two heavens became spectral heaven. Isn’t it normal for revival methods made three million years ago by Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable to fail?”

“You can think whatever you want, that is none of my concern, but I won’t give you any time to stall further, take this!”

Fang Yuan knew that he was the culprit but he had to make Giant Sun Immortal Venerable stand on his side, so he was not going to let Star Constellation Immortal Venerable talk anymore.

Once he stepped into Heavenly Court, Fang Yuan unleashed a powerful offensive method.

Immortal killer move — Shocking Departure of Year Dream Wave and Dang Hun Sound!

Meng Qiu Zhen was already placed into the sovereign immortal aperture, now that he regained dream armor Immortal Gu, this move could be used once again.

At the next moment, waves of pink fog emerged from Fang Yuan’s mouth and ears, gathering above Fang Yuan’s head and turning into a small image of Dang Hun Mountain.

The small Dang Hun Mountain shook intensely.

Ding——！

Ding——！

Ding——！

Sounds of clear crystals colliding resounded in the battlefield, and soon, waves of pink sound waves spread throughout the area.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable who was trapped in the star fog also suffered the attack of the pink sound waves.

However, the star fog managed to stabilize after weakening by thirty percent. It rumbled intensely, seemingly adapting and enduring the assault of the powerful pink sound waves.

Seeing this, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable helped out from the side.

Immortal killer move — Soft Gold Crashing Pillar!

Golden light flowed and turned into tens of crashing pillars that slammed into the star fog.

The strong impact of the soft gold crashing pillars made the luck of the star fog shake intensely.

Everything in heaven and earth contained luck, even grass and rocks were no exception.

This was the profundity of heaven and earth luck.

The luck of the star fog was attacked, it influenced the star fog itself, this penetrative force started to disrupt the operations of the star fog.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had once used this move on Fang Yuan, at that time, it was not completed yet but it still gave Fang Yuan significant trouble. Now, the move was already in a completed state.

However, under Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s control, although the star fog shook for a while, it still survived the waves of attacks.

This scene made Fang Yuan’s and Giant Sun’s hearts sink.

In any other location, these two moves would have succeeded. But in Heavenly Court, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had the amplification of Heavenly Court’s vast number of wisdom path dao marks, her strength rose to a terrifying level.

The star fog was not her strongest killer move, but using it, she resisted Fang Yuan’s compound killer move and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable’s new method.

“With me here, Heavenly Court will not lose.” Star Constellation Immortal Venerable said plainly, but her tone was filled with confidence and resolve.

“Star Constellation Immortal Venerable suppressed the two Demon Venerables, Giant Sun and Fang Yuan, on her own!”

“That’s right, all of Heavenly Court’s wisdom path dao marks have been refined by Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.”

“Hmph, no matter how much damage Heavenly Court has taken, these demonic path scoundrels cannot take us down.”

“After Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable died, she left behind three measures to block the attack of three Demon Venerables for Heavenly Court. Now that she is alive and is personally stopping them, she can definitely defend Heavenly Court, these Demon Venerables will not succeed.”

The Gu Immortals of the ten great ancient sects were excited, the Heavenly Court members also showed expressions of joy.

Everyone knew about the details of the battle over spectral heaven’s dream realms.

The immortals saw that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s strength had risen, they were joyous and felt more confident now.

But at the next moment, the immortals heard Fang Yuan’s cold voice: ”Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, Heavenly Court is your strongest territory, but it is also your weakness! Take this!”

Immortal killer move — Arrival of Dragon Snake with Dust Fog and Explosive Soul Wind!

Soul fog spread out as dragons and snakes roared.

At the same time, the small Dang Hun Mountain above Fang Yuan’s head shot out countless pink sound waves again.

Fang Yuan used two moves at once, but he did not target Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, instead, he aimed at the qi harvest fruit core.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable’s expression changed, she quickly used methods to block them.

Fang Yuan’s two moves worked together but were stopped by her midway, however, he laughed, he held the initiative now.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable moved like lightning, he quickly went to one side and aimed at the qi harvest fruit core as he attacked.

After the earlier test, they realized that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was too powerful here, Giant Sun and Fang Yuan could not defeat her even if they worked together.

But it did not matter.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was most worried about Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable’s revival.

As long as he destroyed the qi harvest fruit core and successfully retreated, his goal would be achieved, he would win this fight.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable fell into a passive spot indeed.

She had to concentrate on defending the qi harvest fruit core, although she was strongest while in Heavenly Court, she could only defend now.

After seeing this, the Central Continent Gu Immortals gritted their teeth and scolded continuously.

“They are so shameless!”

“To think that the grand Giant Sun would act like this.”

“Sigh, I really want to help Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, but I am just too weak.”

The battle of venerables caused huge aftermath effects, the various Immortal Gu Houses retreated time and again.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng was situated in Demon Judgment Board, he frowned deeply as he locked his gaze on Fang Yuan.

Zhao Lian Yun was doing the same.

The Ma Hong Yun that she loved had died in Fang Yuan’s arms. Fang Yuan was currently in possession of Ma Hong Yun’s soul, so even with fate Gu destroyed, Zhao Lian Yun could not revive him.

She had to get back Ma Hong Yun from Fang Yuan.

“Maybe, I can use the power of love Gu to steal his soul from Fang Yuan’s immortal aperture. After all, love Gu is a rank nine Immortal Gu, it has countless effects and is capable of doing almost anything!”

Zhao Lian Yun thought of this and felt increasingly moved.

“Now is not the time. I need to wait patiently until Fang Yuan is at his weakest, when he cannot afford to distract himself, I will make a move!”

Qin Ding Ling was waiting to strike.

She had the killer move luck gamble, it was created to counter Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

She could not do anything against Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, but she could deal with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

She was waiting for a chance.

“Fang Yuan, what other methods do you still have? Hurry up and use them.” After attacking for a long time with no results, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable started to get anxious, he shouted towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan looked down at the Heavenly Court below him.

He saw many Immortal Gu Houses and also huge areas of ruins.

He laughed ruthlessly as he said: ”Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, I am going to kill all of Heavenly Court’s Gu Immortals now. Come stop me if you can!”